<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Waze on Development Data Partnership</title><link>/partner/waze/</link><description>Recent content in Waze on Development Data Partnership</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/partner/waze/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Buenos Aires Transport Demand Planning</title><link>/updates/buenos-aires-transport-demand-planning/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/buenos-aires-transport-demand-planning/</guid><description>Challenge The COVID-19 pandemic and the lockdown measures implemented in 2020 had a significant impact on mobility in the Metropolitan Area of Buenos Aires (AMBA), adding new constrains to the travel behaviours of residents and businesses.</description></item><item><title>A Data-Driven Framework to Support Bogota’s Barrios Vitales Project</title><link>/updates/barrios_vitales_bogota/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/barrios_vitales_bogota/</guid><description>A data-driven framework to support the design, implementation, and evaluation of a superblock model in Bogotá from a speed management perspective and inform street design alternatives in the urban space.</description></item><item><title>Visualizing Millions of Waze Traffic Alerts with BigQuery, H3 and Dask</title><link>/updates/visualizing-millions-of-waze-traffic-alerts-with-google-bigquery-and-dask/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/visualizing-millions-of-waze-traffic-alerts-with-google-bigquery-and-dask/</guid><description>Waze for Cities, a Data Partner of the Development Data Partnership, connects government partners to high quality, frequent and granular traffic data extremely valuable in informing public sector, transport and urban planning as well as addressing the United Nations&amp;rsquo;s Sustainable Development Goals.</description></item><item><title>Improving Road Safety in Nairobi</title><link>/updates/improving-road-safety-in-nairobi/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 20:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/improving-road-safety-in-nairobi/</guid><description>“Data Partnership brings domain expertise. Google brings data expertise. Together we impact real world problems.”
&amp;ndash;Google’s Bailey-Galvis noted at a Data Partnership event in early February 2019</description></item></channel></rss>