<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Case Study on Development Data Partnership</title><link>/post_type/case-study/</link><description>Recent content in Case Study on Development Data Partnership</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/post_type/case-study/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Inferring COVID-19 Vaccine Attitudes from X</title><link>/updates/inferring-covid-attitudes-from-x/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/inferring-covid-attitudes-from-x/</guid><description>Social media has become a platform for the public to openly advocate and express their opinions on various issues including health.</description></item><item><title>Insights from Leveraging Big Data to Track the Impact of the COVID-19 Pandemic on Mobility in Buenos Aires</title><link>/updates/covid-mobility-buenos-aires/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/covid-mobility-buenos-aires/</guid><description>How did the COVID-19 pandemic and the lockdown measures affect mobility in cities around the globe? To inform transport mobility planning, congestion data provided by Waze for Cities was used for a World Bank study on how travel patterns in Buenos Aires changed as a result of pandemic-related restrictions and changing travel preferences.</description></item><item><title>Empowering Female Entrepreneurs to Cross Over into Male-Dominated Sectors</title><link>/updates/empowering-female-entrepreneurs-to-cross-over-into-male-dominated-sectors/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/empowering-female-entrepreneurs-to-cross-over-into-male-dominated-sectors/</guid><description>Female entrepreneurship is on the rise globally. However, factors such as social norms and unconscious biases are holding women back from entering more profitable male-dominated sectors.</description></item><item><title>For Reduced Exposure to COVID-19, the Quality of Your Internet Matters</title><link>/updates/covid19-internet-speed-impact/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/covid19-internet-speed-impact/</guid><description>During the height of the COVID-19 pandemic, governments-imposed movement restrictions to curb the spread of the disease. With access to the internet, people could work or study remotely, therefore making it easier for them to adhere to pandemic-related movement restrictions.</description></item><item><title>Understanding the Post COVID-19 Labor Market in Latin America and the Caribbean</title><link>/updates/covid19-labor-markets-observatory/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 13:02:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/covid19-labor-markets-observatory/</guid><description>Challenge The Covid-19 Labor Markets Observatory, managed by the Inter-American Development Bank Labor Markets Division, aimed to understand how COVID-19 has affected labor markets in Latin America and the Caribbean.</description></item><item><title>Digitalization and Resilience to COVID-19 Shocks: Evidence from Sub-Saharan Africa</title><link>/updates/imf-digitalization-in-sub-saharan-africa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/imf-digitalization-in-sub-saharan-africa/</guid><description>Challenge The COVID-19 pandemic has brought major disruption to economic activities and human welfare across the world. Despite the pandemic&amp;rsquo;s late arrival, Sub-Saharan African countries were faced with unprecedented challenges to contain the spread of the pandemic and mitigate the damage to the economy.</description></item><item><title>Facebook’s Covid-19 Trends and Impact Survey</title><link>/updates/facebook-covid-19-trends-and-impact-survey/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/facebook-covid-19-trends-and-impact-survey/</guid><description>With as many as 8 vaccines approved for use around the world the most urgent need now to control the spread of the novel coronavirus is increasing vaccination rates.</description></item><item><title>Unlocking Mobility: TapTap Maps in Cap-Haïtien</title><link>/updates/unlocking-mobility-taptap-maps-in-cap-haitien/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 13:02:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/unlocking-mobility-taptap-maps-in-cap-haitien/</guid><description>Challenge Haitian cities suffer from poor transportation services, and the lack of data from existing services limits improvement efforts. Tap Taps are the most popular motorized transportation mode employed across Haiti, yet there is not enough data on them as they are informal, private, and marginally regulated.</description></item><item><title>Improving Public Space and Market Design During COVID-19</title><link>/updates/improving-public-space-and-market-design-during-covid-19/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 13:02:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/improving-public-space-and-market-design-during-covid-19/</guid><description>Lima’s Central Market has always been one of the busiest and liveliest in Lima, Peru. Before the pandemic, some hundreds of people gathered there to buy and sell groceries, clothes, electronics&amp;ndash;you name it.</description></item><item><title>The IMF's New Climate Change Indicators Dashboard: Experimental Data for Economic and Financial Analysis</title><link>/updates/imf-climate-change-dashboard/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/imf-climate-change-dashboard/</guid><description>To develop the right measures to tackle climate change, governments need robust and comparable data. The new IMF Dashboard will help fill data gaps, so policymakers can undertake the macroeconomic and financial analysis that underpins effective policies</description></item><item><title>Examining the Economic Impact of COVID-19 in India through Daily Electricity Consumption and Nighttime Light Intensity</title><link>/updates/examining-the-economic-impact-of-covid-19-in-india-through-daily-electricity-consumption-and-nighttime-light-intensity/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/examining-the-economic-impact-of-covid-19-in-india-through-daily-electricity-consumption-and-nighttime-light-intensity/</guid><description>Challenge The COVID-19 pandemic has disrupted economic activity in India. When COVID-19 started to spread in India through domestic contagion, the authorities enacted a series of measures to combat the pandemic, including a strict national lockdown from March 25 to May 4 that strongly disrupted economic activity.</description></item><item><title>Optimizing Tourism Investments: Identifying Chokepoints and Underperforming Minor Roads in Sri Lanka</title><link>/updates/optimizing-tourism-investments-identifying-chokepoints-and-underperforming-minor-roads-in-sri-lanka/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/optimizing-tourism-investments-identifying-chokepoints-and-underperforming-minor-roads-in-sri-lanka/</guid><description>Challenge Connected and maintained transportation infrastructure are critical to sustainable economic development, but most current estimation methods of road quality are labor, time, and cost intensive.</description></item><item><title>Socioeconomic Impact of COVID-19 in Indonesia</title><link>/updates/covid-19-observatory/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/covid-19-observatory/</guid><description>Challenge Although there is a widespread awareness of the pandemic, there is a lack of understanding from citizens’ perspective, especially behaviors it triggers, sentiments towards government as well as rising concerns.</description></item><item><title>Estimating High-speed Broadband Coverage in Ukraine</title><link>/updates/estimating-high-speed-broadband-coverage-in-ukraine/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/estimating-high-speed-broadband-coverage-in-ukraine/</guid><description>Challenge Ukraine, Europe’s biggest country, has over 1,192 operators and providers, of which close to three quarters operate under a special preferential tax regime, allowing them not to report their coverage/subscription data to the national telecom regulatory authority.</description></item><item><title>Economic Anxiety and COVID-19 in Southeast Asia</title><link>/updates/economic-anxiety-and-covid-19-in-southeast-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/economic-anxiety-and-covid-19-in-southeast-asia/</guid><description>Challenge The COVID-19 pandemic has affected the global economy through lockdowns, disrupted supply chains and uncertain economic outlooks. Swift reaction by policy makers are required to prevent a deep recession.</description></item><item><title>Analyzing Spatial Accessibility of Health Facilities in Indonesia and Philippines</title><link>/updates/planning-for-equitable-access-to-health-infrastructure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/planning-for-equitable-access-to-health-infrastructure/</guid><description>Challenge: Indonesia and the Philippines are archipelagos, where geographic and administrative boundaries are similar. The collection of islands is home to different concentrations of ethnic, cultural, linguistic, and socioeconomic groups, with an imbalanced distribution of health facilities and physicians.</description></item><item><title>Tackling COVID-19 Second Wave using Facebook Mobility Data in Vietnam</title><link>/updates/tackling-covid19-second-wave-using-facebook-mobility-data-in-vietnam/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/tackling-covid19-second-wave-using-facebook-mobility-data-in-vietnam/</guid><description>Challenge: On July 24, after 99 days of zero community-transmitted COVID-19 infections, a 57 year-old man tested positive in Danang, a major city in central Vietnam with close to 1.</description></item><item><title>Assessing Social Inequality and Lockdown Policies using Mobile Location Data in Indonesia</title><link>/updates/social-inequality-and-lockdown-policies/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 13:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/social-inequality-and-lockdown-policies/</guid><description>Challenge Lockdown policies such as stay-at-home orders and non-essential business closures are central to fighting the novel coronavirus. However, policy makers are having a hard time answering key questions about their efficacy.</description></item><item><title>A New Predictive Model for More Accurate Electrical Grid Mapping</title><link>/updates/more-accurate-electrical-grid-mapping/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 21:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/more-accurate-electrical-grid-mapping/</guid><description>Challenge: When planning connectivity deployments in emerging markets, it is important to have a clear picture of where existing power lines are placed.</description></item><item><title>Estimating Access to Employment Opportunities in Dhaka, Bangladesh</title><link>/updates/employment-opportunities-in-bangladesh/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 21:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/employment-opportunities-in-bangladesh/</guid><description>Challenge: Poor transport facilities and infrastructure are a major hindrance to Bangladesh’s economic development. The road network in Dhaka is severely congested.</description></item><item><title>Tackling the Global Profitarchy–Gender and the Choice of Business Sector</title><link>/updates/tackling-the-global-profitarchy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 21:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/tackling-the-global-profitarchy/</guid><description>Challenge: Despite significant progress in women’s educational attainment and higher female labor force participation rates in many countries, progress in closing the gender pay gap, which takes the ratio of median earnings of all women to all men, has been slow.</description></item><item><title>Improving Road Safety in Nairobi</title><link>/updates/improving-road-safety-in-nairobi/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 20:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/improving-road-safety-in-nairobi/</guid><description>“Data Partnership brings domain expertise. Google brings data expertise. Together we impact real world problems.”
&amp;ndash;Google’s Bailey-Galvis noted at a Data Partnership event in early February 2019</description></item></channel></rss>