<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Gender on Development Data Partnership</title><link>/tags/gender/</link><description>Recent content in Gender on Development Data Partnership</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/gender/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Examining Gender Disparities in Skills within the Energy Sector: Insights from LinkedIn Data</title><link>/updates/examining-gender-disparities-in-skills-within-the-energy-sector-insights-from-linkedin-data/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/examining-gender-disparities-in-skills-within-the-energy-sector-insights-from-linkedin-data/</guid><description>Analyzing gender differences in skills in the energy sector offers insights into disparities and facilitates better future planning. The International Energy Agency (IEA), a sister entity to the Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development, utilized LinkedIn data for the Gender and Energy Data Explorer, a platform which provides information on gender gaps in the energy sector related to employment, wages, senior management, entrepreneurship, and innovation.</description></item><item><title>Empowering Female Entrepreneurs to Cross Over into Male-Dominated Sectors</title><link>/updates/empowering-female-entrepreneurs-to-cross-over-into-male-dominated-sectors/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/empowering-female-entrepreneurs-to-cross-over-into-male-dominated-sectors/</guid><description>Female entrepreneurship is on the rise globally. However, factors such as social norms and unconscious biases are holding women back from entering more profitable male-dominated sectors.</description></item><item><title>Green Jobs for Women and Diverse Groups Help Promote Equality and Climate Resilience</title><link>/updates/green-jobs-for-women-and-diverse-groups-help-promote-equality-and-climate-resilience/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/green-jobs-for-women-and-diverse-groups-help-promote-equality-and-climate-resilience/</guid><description>The role of women and diverse populations, including indigenous peoples, persons of African descent, persons with disabilities, and LGBTQ+ persons, is crucial in driving the decarbonization process and developing climate change resilience strategies.</description></item><item><title>Social Norms and Gender Equality in South Asia</title><link>/social-norms-and-gender-equality/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/social-norms-and-gender-equality/</guid><description>This blog highlights recent work from a larger body of research on gender equality carried out at the World Bank. The blog itself relies on Chapter 3 of this report South Asia Economic Focus Reshaping Norms: A New Way Forward.</description></item><item><title>Tackling the Global Profitarchy–Gender and the Choice of Business Sector</title><link>/updates/tackling-the-global-profitarchy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 21:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/tackling-the-global-profitarchy/</guid><description>Challenge: Despite significant progress in women’s educational attainment and higher female labor force participation rates in many countries, progress in closing the gender pay gap, which takes the ratio of median earnings of all women to all men, has been slow.</description></item></channel></rss>