<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Health on Development Data Partnership</title><link>/tags/health/</link><description>Recent content in Health on Development Data Partnership</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/health/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Facilitating Inter-Municipal Cooperation in Lithuania to Provide Better Access to Healthcare and Long-Term Care Services to Citizens</title><link>/updates/facilitating-inter-municipal-cooperation-in-lithuania/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/facilitating-inter-municipal-cooperation-in-lithuania/</guid><description>Lithuania is experiencing rapid demographic change, with the population both aging and significantly shrinking in recent decades. This trend has put pressure on the provision of public services such as health care, especially at the municipal level, and is expected to continue in the coming years.</description></item><item><title>Exploring the crucial role of traffic-related emissions on air pollution in Tbilisi</title><link>/updates/role-of-traffic-related-emissions-on-air-pollution-in-tbilisi/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/role-of-traffic-related-emissions-on-air-pollution-in-tbilisi/</guid><description>With financial support from Sweden, the World Bank’s Poverty and Equity Team working in the South Caucasus was seeking to understand how exposure to pollution varies within Tbilisi, Georgia across income groups and occupations to aid policy makers in developing solutions that benefit those who are most vulnerable to pollution.</description></item><item><title>Assessing the Impact of Extreme Temperatures on Sentiments through Social Media Data in Argentina</title><link>/updates/assessing-the-impact-of-extreme-temperatures-on-sentiments-through-social-media-in-argentina/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/assessing-the-impact-of-extreme-temperatures-on-sentiments-through-social-media-in-argentina/</guid><description>How do extreme weather events affect people&amp;rsquo;s sentiments? Leveraging X (formerly known as Twitter) data, the World Bank&amp;rsquo;s Regional Direction of Sustainable Development for Latin America and the Caribbean worked with researchers from Argentina universities to study how extreme temperatures impact people&amp;rsquo;s moods in Argentina.</description></item><item><title>Inferring COVID-19 Vaccine Attitudes from X</title><link>/updates/inferring-covid-attitudes-from-x/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/inferring-covid-attitudes-from-x/</guid><description>Social media has become a platform for the public to openly advocate and express their opinions on various issues including health.</description></item><item><title>Understanding the Economic Impact of Vaccination</title><link>/updates/economic-impact-vaccination/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/economic-impact-vaccination/</guid><description>The World Bank East Asia and the Pacific Economic Update April 2022 analyzed challenges and opportunities facing the East Asia and the Pacific (EAP) region.</description></item><item><title>Is El Salvador's health care system ready for telemedicine?</title><link>/updates/el-salvador-telemedicine/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/el-salvador-telemedicine/</guid><description>The World Bank&amp;rsquo;s Digital Economy for Latin America (DE4LAC) initiative leveraged data from Ookla for Good™ to analyze El Salvador&amp;rsquo;s telecommunication network to understand to what extent the national healthcare system could leverage the existing digital infrastructure and develop e-health applications.</description></item><item><title>For Reduced Exposure to COVID-19, the Quality of Your Internet Matters</title><link>/updates/covid19-internet-speed-impact/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/covid19-internet-speed-impact/</guid><description>During the height of the COVID-19 pandemic, governments-imposed movement restrictions to curb the spread of the disease. With access to the internet, people could work or study remotely, therefore making it easier for them to adhere to pandemic-related movement restrictions.</description></item><item><title>Communicating for Health: How Did Indians Get Informed about COVID-19 during the Pandemic?</title><link>/updates/communicating-for-health-in-india.md/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/communicating-for-health-in-india.md/</guid><description>The COVID-19 pandemic saw an unprecedented amount of scientific information disseminated: throughout 2020, 11 research articles on COVID-19 were published every hour.</description></item><item><title>Understanding Societal Responses to Policies Undertaken During Emergencies: Lessons from COVID-19’s Second Wave in Maharashtra</title><link>/updates/lessons-from-covid-19-second-wave-in-maharashtra/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/lessons-from-covid-19-second-wave-in-maharashtra/</guid><description>Maharashtra, one of the wealthiest states in India, was among the worst hit by COVID-19, registering nearly 140,000 COVID-19 deaths since the start of the pandemic.</description></item><item><title>Facebook’s Covid-19 Trends and Impact Survey</title><link>/updates/facebook-covid-19-trends-and-impact-survey/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/facebook-covid-19-trends-and-impact-survey/</guid><description>With as many as 8 vaccines approved for use around the world the most urgent need now to control the spread of the novel coronavirus is increasing vaccination rates.</description></item><item><title>Socioeconomic Impact of COVID-19 in Indonesia</title><link>/updates/covid-19-observatory/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/covid-19-observatory/</guid><description>Challenge Although there is a widespread awareness of the pandemic, there is a lack of understanding from citizens’ perspective, especially behaviors it triggers, sentiments towards government as well as rising concerns.</description></item><item><title>Analyzing Spatial Accessibility of Health Facilities in Indonesia and Philippines</title><link>/updates/planning-for-equitable-access-to-health-infrastructure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/planning-for-equitable-access-to-health-infrastructure/</guid><description>Challenge: Indonesia and the Philippines are archipelagos, where geographic and administrative boundaries are similar. The collection of islands is home to different concentrations of ethnic, cultural, linguistic, and socioeconomic groups, with an imbalanced distribution of health facilities and physicians.</description></item><item><title>Assessing Social Inequality and Lockdown Policies using Mobile Location Data in Indonesia</title><link>/updates/social-inequality-and-lockdown-policies/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 13:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/social-inequality-and-lockdown-policies/</guid><description>Challenge Lockdown policies such as stay-at-home orders and non-essential business closures are central to fighting the novel coronavirus. However, policy makers are having a hard time answering key questions about their efficacy.</description></item><item><title>Addressing COVID-19 through Public-Private Data Partnerships: Where Do We Put New Testing Facilities?</title><link>/updates/covid19-and-public-private-data-partnerships/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 20:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/covid19-and-public-private-data-partnerships/</guid><description>Background
As the COVID-19 pandemic evolves, the World Bank is ramping up its response to help countries around the world. The Bank recently announced $14 billion emergency support program, for which a key pillar is to help countries strengthen their capacity to monitor and respond to the spread of the virus.</description></item></channel></rss>