<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Health on Development Data Partnership</title><link>/tags/health/</link><description>Recent content in Health on Development Data Partnership</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/health/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Communicating for Health: How Did Indians Get Informed About COVID-19 During the Pandemic?</title><link>/updates/communicating-for-health-indian-covid-19/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/communicating-for-health-indian-covid-19/</guid><description>The COVID-19 pandemic saw an unprecedented amount of scientific information disseminated: throughout 2020, 11 research articles on COVID-19 were published every hour.</description></item><item><title>Understanding Societal Responses to Policies Undertaken During Emergencies: Lessons from COVID-19’s Second Wave in Maharashtra</title><link>/updates/lessons-from-covid-19-second-wave-in-maharashtra/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/lessons-from-covid-19-second-wave-in-maharashtra/</guid><description>Maharashtra, one of the wealthiest states in India, was among the worst hit by COVID-19, registering nearly 140,000 COVID-19 deaths since the start of the pandemic.</description></item><item><title>Facebook’s Covid-19 Trends and Impact Survey</title><link>/updates/facebook-covid-19-trends-and-impact-survey/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/facebook-covid-19-trends-and-impact-survey/</guid><description>With as many as 8 vaccines approved for use around the world the most urgent need now to control the spread of the novel coronavirus is increasing vaccination rates.</description></item><item><title>Socioeconomic Impact of COVID-19 in Indonesia</title><link>/updates/covid-19-observatory/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/covid-19-observatory/</guid><description>Challenge: Although there is a widespread awareness of the pandemic, there is a lack of understanding from citizens’ perspective, especially behaviors it triggers, sentiments towards government as well as rising concerns.</description></item><item><title>Analyzing Spatial Accessibility of Health Facilities in Indonesia and Philippines</title><link>/planning-for-equitable-access-to-health-infrastructure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/planning-for-equitable-access-to-health-infrastructure/</guid><description>Challenge: Indonesia and the Philippines are archipelagos, where geographic and administrative boundaries are similar. The collection of islands is home to different concentrations of ethnic, cultural, linguistic, and socioeconomic groups, with an imbalanced distribution of health facilities and physicians.</description></item><item><title>Assessing Social Inequality and Lockdown Policies using Mobile Location Data in Indonesia</title><link>/updates/social-inequality-and-lockdown-policies/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 13:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/social-inequality-and-lockdown-policies/</guid><description>Challenge: Lockdown policies such as stay-at-home orders and non-essential business closures are central to fighting the novel coronavirus. However, policy makers are having a hard time answering key questions about their efficacy.</description></item><item><title>Addressing COVID-19 through Public-Private Data Partnerships: Where Do We Put New Testing Facilities?</title><link>/updates/covid19-and-public-private-data-partnerships/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 20:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/covid19-and-public-private-data-partnerships/</guid><description>Background
As the COVID-19 pandemic evolves, the World Bank is ramping up its response to help countries around the world. The Bank recently announced $14 billion emergency support program, for which a key pillar is to help countries strengthen their capacity to monitor and respond to the spread of the virus.</description></item></channel></rss>