<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Facebook on Development Data Partnership</title><link>//datapartnership.org/partner/facebook/</link><description>Recent content in Facebook on Development Data Partnership</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//datapartnership.org/partner/facebook/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Analyzing Spatial Accessibility of Health Facilities in Indonesia and Philippines</title><link>//datapartnership.org/planning-for-equitable-access-to-health-infrastructure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//datapartnership.org/planning-for-equitable-access-to-health-infrastructure/</guid><description>Challenge: Indonesia and the Philippines are archipelagos, where geographic and administrative boundaries are similar. The collection of islands is home to different concentrations of ethnic, cultural, linguistic, and socioeconomic groups, with an imbalanced distribution of health facilities and physicians.</description></item><item><title>Tackling COVID-19 Second Wave using Facebook Mobility Data in Vietnam</title><link>//datapartnership.org/updates/tackling-covid19-second-wave-using-facebook-mobility-data-in-vietnam/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//datapartnership.org/updates/tackling-covid19-second-wave-using-facebook-mobility-data-in-vietnam/</guid><description>Challenge: On July 24, after 99 days of zero community-transmitted COVID-19 infections, a 57 year-old man tested positive in Danang, a major city in central Vietnam with close to 1.</description></item><item><title>How to Find Population Movement Data for Your Country: The Mobile Location Data Inventory</title><link>//datapartnership.org/updates/find-population-movement-data-for-your-country/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//datapartnership.org/updates/find-population-movement-data-for-your-country/</guid><description>As the COVID-19 pandemic continues, so have measures to mitigate its spread. Physical distancing and movement restrictions – such as school and workplace closures, public event cancellations, stay-at-home orders, and international and domestic travel bans – vary considerably across countries.</description></item><item><title>Google, Apple, and Facebook: Understanding Mobility during Social Distancing with Private Sector Data</title><link>//datapartnership.org/updates/understanding-mobility-during-social-distancing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//datapartnership.org/updates/understanding-mobility-during-social-distancing/</guid><description>As countries around the world work to contain the spread and impact of COVID-19, the World Bank Group is moving quickly to provide fast, flexible responses to help developing countries strengthen their pandemic response and health care systems.</description></item><item><title>Addressing COVID-19 through Public-Private Data Partnerships -- Where Do We Put New Testing Facilities?</title><link>//datapartnership.org/updates/covid19-and-public-private-data-partnerships/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 20:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>//datapartnership.org/updates/covid19-and-public-private-data-partnerships/</guid><description>Background
As the COVID-19 pandemic evolves, the World Bank is ramping up its response to help countries around the world. The Bank recently announced $14 billion emergency support program, for which a key pillar is to help countries strengthen their capacity to monitor and respond to the spread of the virus.</description></item><item><title>A New Predictive Model for More Accurate Electrical Grid Mapping</title><link>//datapartnership.org/updates/more-accurate-electrical-grid-mapping/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 21:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>//datapartnership.org/updates/more-accurate-electrical-grid-mapping/</guid><description>Challenge: When planning connectivity deployments in emerging markets, it is important to have a clear picture of where existing power lines are placed. This information helps us make better decisions about where to focus our efforts, how we design the network, and how we source the equipment we’ll need.</description></item><item><title>Tackling the Global Profitarchy–Gender and the Choice of Business Sector</title><link>//datapartnership.org/updates/tackling-the-global-profitarchy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 21:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>//datapartnership.org/updates/tackling-the-global-profitarchy/</guid><description>Challenge: Despite significant progress in women’s educational attainment and higher female labor force participation rates in many countries, progress in closing the gender pay gap, which takes the ratio of median earnings of all women to all men, has been slow.</description></item></channel></rss>