<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Development Data Partnership</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on Development Data Partnership</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Legal Foundation</title><link>/pillars/legal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/pillars/legal/</guid><description>Template data license agreements and MOUs between international organizations saves time and resources.</description></item><item><title>Partnership Data License Agreements</title><link>/how-it-works/step-1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 21:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/how-it-works/step-1/</guid><description>Master data license agreements are signed between Data Partners and Development Partners.</description></item><item><title>Short Term Impact</title><link>/impact/short-term/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 21:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/impact/short-term/</guid><description>Since launching, there are more than 150 development projects have been completed or are under implementation, covering all Sustainable Development Goals.</description></item><item><title>Data Marketplace</title><link>/pillars/data-partnership-management/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 21:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/pillars/data-partnership-management/</guid><description>A web-based proposal management portal facilitates seamless interactions between Data and Development Partners.</description></item><item><title>Data Partner</title><link>/how-to-engage/data-partner/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 21:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/how-to-engage/data-partner/</guid><description>The Partnership unlocks public good opportunities from proprietary data in a secure, responsible manner. Through partnership, Data Partners can open markets in emerging economies, discover new data methods that inform future products, and increase staff skills through collaboration and secondment opportunities.</description></item><item><title>Development Partner</title><link>/how-to-engage/consortium/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 21:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/how-to-engage/consortium/</guid><description>The Partnership is open to donors and entities engaged in international development work. Members have access to the Data Partnership Portal and are invited to participate in exchanges and training activities.</description></item><item><title>Long Term Impact</title><link>/impact/long-term/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 21:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/impact/long-term/</guid><description>By learning through real project implementation, the Partnership transforms proprietary datasets into sustainably generated, sharable insights for improving public sector services and infrastructure in emerging economies.</description></item><item><title>Project Proposals</title><link>/how-it-works/step-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 21:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/how-it-works/step-2/</guid><description>Data Partners use the Partnership Portal to vet project proposals submitted by staff of international organizations (Development Partners).
Submit a Proposal Documentation Hub</description></item><item><title>Why Partnership</title><link>/business-case/why-data-partnerships/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 21:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/business-case/why-data-partnerships/</guid><description>Public policy and provision of public infrastructure and services are heavily dependent on data – higher quality, timely data translates into more effective sector and program prioritization, design, implementation, monitoring, and evaluation.</description></item><item><title>Shared Secure IT Architecture</title><link>/pillars/it-architecture/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/pillars/it-architecture/</guid><description>Centralized IT architecture and processes for ingesting, storing, and pre-processing data, as well as for coding collaboration, lower costs and facilitate secure data use.</description></item><item><title>Data Management</title><link>/how-it-works/step-3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 21:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/how-it-works/step-3/</guid><description>Upon project approval, data are securely and responsibly ingested, stored, and managed through the Partnership IT architecture and procedures.</description></item><item><title>Data Goods</title><link>/how-it-works/step-4/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 21:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/how-it-works/step-4/</guid><description>Data Partners are kept in the loop about derived data products and new methods.</description></item><item><title>Data Goods</title><link>/pillars/derived-data-products/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 21:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/pillars/derived-data-products/</guid><description>Accessible code repositories for derived data products and algorithms broaden Partnership impact.</description></item><item><title>Data Governance</title><link>/pillars/access/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/pillars/access/</guid><description>A robust data governance system guides best practices for responsible and ethical data use.</description></item><item><title>Analyzing the Adoption of Artificial Intelligence in Capital Market Activities</title><link>/updates/analyzing-the-adoption-of-artificial-intelligence-in-capital-market-activities/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/analyzing-the-adoption-of-artificial-intelligence-in-capital-market-activities/</guid><description>The analytical chapter (Chapter 3) of the October 2024 Global Financial Stability Report aims to assess the potential impact of Artificial Intelligence (AI) on capital markets.</description></item><item><title>Facilitating Inter-Municipal Cooperation in Lithuania to Provide Better Access to Healthcare and Long-Term Care Services to Citizens</title><link>/updates/facilitating-inter-municipal-cooperation-in-lithuania/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/facilitating-inter-municipal-cooperation-in-lithuania/</guid><description>Lithuania is experiencing rapid demographic change, with the population both aging and significantly shrinking in recent decades. This trend has put pressure on the provision of public services such as health care, especially at the municipal level, and is expected to continue in the coming years.</description></item><item><title>Assessing Flood Risks in Peru</title><link>/updates/assessing-flood-risks-in-peru/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/assessing-flood-risks-in-peru/</guid><description>The Inter-American Development Bank (IDB) Water and Sanitation division leveraged data from JBA&amp;rsquo;s Global Flood Maps as supporting information to identify areas of exposure to flooding risk prior to the implementation of &amp;ldquo;Proyecto Para la Ampliación Y Mejoramiento de Los Servicios de Agua Potable Y Alcantarillado de la Ciudad de Juliaca-Puno&amp;rdquo; (in Spanish) to design and build a resilient water and sanitation infrastructure in Peru’s Puno region.</description></item><item><title>Understanding Internet Connectivity to Tackle the Digital Divide</title><link>/updates/understanding-internet-connectivity-to-tackle-the-digital-divide/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/understanding-internet-connectivity-to-tackle-the-digital-divide/</guid><description>The Internet offers great potential for contributing to more prosperous societies. For instance, it enables small businesses to overcome the challenges of entering worldwide markets.</description></item><item><title>Understanding Socioeconomic Disparities in Mobility Behavior During the COVID-19 Pandemic in Developing Countries</title><link>/updates/understanding-socioeconomic-disparities-in-mobility-behavior-during-covid-in-developing-countries/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/understanding-socioeconomic-disparities-in-mobility-behavior-during-covid-in-developing-countries/</guid><description>The COVID-19 pandemic profoundly disrupted global mobility, but how did it affect different socioeconomic groups, particularly in developing and middle-income countries?</description></item><item><title>Nature-Based Solutions for Climate-Resilient Urban Development in Itahari, Nepal</title><link>/updates/nbs-for-climate-resilient-urban-development-in-nepal/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/nbs-for-climate-resilient-urban-development-in-nepal/</guid><description>Cities across Nepal are increasingly vulnerable to natural disasters and climate change impacts. Rapid, unplanned urbanization and the country&amp;rsquo;s unique topography make major cities particularly prone to floods, landslides, and heat stress.</description></item><item><title>Examining the Prevalence of Technology Skills in Central America and the Dominican Republic</title><link>/updates/prevalence-of-technology-skills-in-cadr/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/prevalence-of-technology-skills-in-cadr/</guid><description>Technological advancements like artificial intelligence (AI) have the potential to shape labor markets in Central America and the Dominican Republic (CADR).</description></item><item><title>Using Mobility Data for Resilient Transport Planning and Investments</title><link>/updates/using-mobility-data-for-resilient-transport-planning-and-investments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/using-mobility-data-for-resilient-transport-planning-and-investments/</guid><description>Chennai has been facing various challenges like changes in land use patterns and urban population stress, and a growing risk from events like floods and heavy rains, which all put pressure on its transport infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Examining the Impact of Social Distancing on Household-Level Economic Performances in Vietnam</title><link>/updates/social-distancing-on-household-level-economic-performances-in-vietnam/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/social-distancing-on-household-level-economic-performances-in-vietnam/</guid><description>During the COVID-19 pandemic, governments implemented social distancing measures to curb the spread of the virus. However, these measures also impacted people’s socioeconomic well-being.</description></item><item><title>Exploring the crucial role of traffic-related emissions on air pollution in Tbilisi</title><link>/updates/role-of-traffic-related-emissions-on-air-pollution-in-tbilisi/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/role-of-traffic-related-emissions-on-air-pollution-in-tbilisi/</guid><description>With financial support from Sweden, the World Bank’s Poverty and Equity Team working in the South Caucasus was seeking to understand how exposure to pollution varies within Tbilisi, Georgia across income groups and occupations to aid policy makers in developing solutions that benefit those who are most vulnerable to pollution.</description></item><item><title>Studying Service Accessibility in Towns and Villages</title><link>/updates/studying-service-accessibility-in-towns-and-villages/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/studying-service-accessibility-in-towns-and-villages/</guid><description>Settlements – cities, towns and villages – provide jobs and access to services for their own residents and other people living nearby.</description></item><item><title>Assessing the Impact of Extreme Temperatures on Sentiments through Social Media Data in Argentina</title><link>/updates/assessing-the-impact-of-extreme-temperatures-on-sentiments-through-social-media-in-argentina/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/assessing-the-impact-of-extreme-temperatures-on-sentiments-through-social-media-in-argentina/</guid><description>How do extreme weather events affect people&amp;rsquo;s sentiments? Leveraging X (formerly known as Twitter) data, the World Bank&amp;rsquo;s Regional Direction of Sustainable Development for Latin America and the Caribbean worked with researchers from Argentina universities to study how extreme temperatures impact people&amp;rsquo;s moods in Argentina.</description></item><item><title>Evaluar El Impacto De Las Temperaturas Extremas En Los Sentimientos a Través De Datos De Redes Sociales En Argentina</title><link>/updates/impacto_temperaturas_argentina_redes_sociales/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/impacto_temperaturas_argentina_redes_sociales/</guid><description>¿Cómo afectan los fenómenos meteorológicos extremos a los sentimientos de las personas? A partir de los datos de la red social X (antes conocido como Twitter), la Dirección Regional de Desarrollo Sostenible para América Latina y el Caribe del Banco Mundial trabajó con investigadores de universidades argentinas para estudiar cómo las temperaturas extremas impactan sobre el estado de ánimo de las personas en Argentina.</description></item><item><title>Cultivating Human Capital and Skills in Argentina for Sustainable Long-Term Economic Growth</title><link>/updates/cultivating-human-capital-and-skills-in-argentina/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/cultivating-human-capital-and-skills-in-argentina/</guid><description>Argentina holds immense potential to achieve sustained and inclusive economic growth. However, the country is facing structural challenges to growth, including the gradually declining quality of human capital.</description></item><item><title>Monitoring and Simulating Trade Disruptions through Satellite-Based Vessel Data and Big Data Analytics</title><link>/updates/monitoring-and-simulating-trade-disruptions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/monitoring-and-simulating-trade-disruptions/</guid><description>Global supply chains are increasingly vulnerable to the impacts of climate change, natural hazards and geopolitical trade tensions. The International Monetary Fund and the Environmental Change Instituteat the University of Oxford established PortWatch to help people assess the domestic and international trade impact of actual and future disruptions.</description></item><item><title>Uncovering the Digital Divide in Brazil: Data Reveals Internet Inequality Across Income Groups</title><link>/updates/uncovering-digital-divide-in-brazil/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/uncovering-digital-divide-in-brazil/</guid><description>Leveraging data from Ookla for Good™, the World Bank&amp;rsquo;s Digital Development Global Practice has analyzed the relationship between internet speed and income inequality within a sample of Brazilian cities.</description></item><item><title>Macroeconomic Monitoring with Google Trends</title><link>/updates/macroeconomic-monitoring-with-google-trends/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/macroeconomic-monitoring-with-google-trends/</guid><description>Challenges such as a lack of timely high-frequency data make it difficult to monitor and evaluate changing economic situations. Google&amp;rsquo;s weekly search volume index (SVI) helped the International Monetary Fund provide more timely response and assessment of economic activity especially in Labor Markets and Tourism.</description></item><item><title>Partnership Day 2024: Harnessing Data and Technology and Private-Public Sector Collaboration to Tackle Development Challenges</title><link>/updates/partnership_day_recap_2024/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/partnership_day_recap_2024/</guid><description>The Development Data Partnership Day shed light on the significant roles of technology and private-public sector collaboration in helping international organizations and countries address development challenges for a more sustainable future.</description></item><item><title>Understanding people mobility in Amazonia</title><link>/updates/understanding-people-mobility-in-amazonia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/understanding-people-mobility-in-amazonia/</guid><description>Amazonia has many small and remote communities but also some big and influential urban centers. At the Inter-American Development Bank (IDB), in our efforts towards a sustainable development in Amazonia through the Amazonia Forever program, we leveraged movement data from Meta to shed light on the relationships between cities in each country within Amazonia, as well as the connection between the region&amp;rsquo;s urban areas and other parts of the countries as we understand that there is a constant movement of people and merchandise between areas.</description></item><item><title>Development Data Partnership Day 2024</title><link>/updates/partnership-day-2024/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/partnership-day-2024/</guid><description>Join us for Development Data Partnership Day, which will be live-streamed from the OECD Headquarters &amp;amp; Conference Centre in Paris, France.</description></item><item><title>Implications of the Green Transition for the Labor Market</title><link>/updates/implications-of-the-green-transition/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/implications-of-the-green-transition/</guid><description>The global shift towards a low-carbon economy is essential to address environmental challenges but will leave no area of economic and social life untouched.</description></item><item><title>A Greener Labor Market: Employment, Policies, and Economic Transformation</title><link>/updates/greener-labor-market/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/greener-labor-market/</guid><description>How green is the labor market? Do workers have the skills needed for greener employment? The International Monetary Fund&amp;rsquo;s Research Department utilized LinkedIn data to analyze global green employment trends.</description></item><item><title> Understanding the Impact of Digitalization During COVID-19</title><link>/updates/impact-of-digitalization-during-covid/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/impact-of-digitalization-during-covid/</guid><description>COVID-19 has disrupted almost every aspect of people&amp;rsquo;s work activities, inducing a digitalization push in the demand for certain types of skills and labor.</description></item><item><title>How Digitalization Can Enhance Economic Resilience</title><link>/updates/how-digitalization-can-enhance-resilience/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/how-digitalization-can-enhance-resilience/</guid><description>The COVID-19 crisis has opened deep economic scars, leading to significant output losses. Can digitalization improve economic resilience to shocks such as the pandemic?</description></item><item><title>Using Mobility Data to Improve Lives in Lima</title><link>/updates/mobility-data-lima/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/mobility-data-lima/</guid><description>Improving traffic flow and enhancing road safety are critical to Lima which was ranked the fourth most congested metropolitan area in the world in 2022.</description></item><item><title> Assessing Traffic Congestion and Accessibility to Jobs Using Waze for Cities and Mapbox Data</title><link>/updates/traffic-congestion-argentina/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/traffic-congestion-argentina/</guid><description>Traffic congestion and suburbanization are becoming increasingly significant factors affecting urban mobility and limiting access to jobs and opportunities in most mid-sized cities worldwide.</description></item><item><title>Development Data Partnership 2023 Year in Review</title><link>/updates/year-in-review-2023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/year-in-review-2023/</guid><description>It has been an extraordinary year for the Development Data Partnership. Before we start the new year, we wanted to take a moment to reflect and look back on what we have accomplished in 2023.</description></item><item><title>Assessing Digital Transformation in Firms in Latin America and the Caribbean</title><link>/updates/digital-transformation-lac/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/digital-transformation-lac/</guid><description>Are firms in Latin America and the Caribbean lagging in terms of their adoption of digital technologies? The Inter-American Development Bank&amp;rsquo;s Competitiveness, Technology, and Innovation Division leveraged LinkedIn data on the penetration of digital skills as part of an assessment on the adoption of technologies in the region.</description></item><item><title>Analyzing Digital Skills Gap in MENA Countries to Inform An Upskilling Initiative</title><link>/updates/digital-skills-gap-mena/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/digital-skills-gap-mena/</guid><description>Digital technologies are reshaping work and traditional jobs. It is essential for workers across all sectors to acquire and strengthen their digital skills to stay competitive in the job market.</description></item><item><title>Inferring COVID-19 Vaccine Attitudes from X</title><link>/updates/inferring-covid-attitudes-from-x/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/inferring-covid-attitudes-from-x/</guid><description>Social media has become a platform for the public to openly advocate and express their opinions on various issues including health.</description></item><item><title>Understanding Informal Trade Dynamics in Benin</title><link>/updates/understanding-informal-trade-dynamics-in-benin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/understanding-informal-trade-dynamics-in-benin/</guid><description>Benin&amp;rsquo;s trade performance has been improving gradually in the past decade. Notably, informal trade, smuggling and small-scale cross border trade (SSCBT) are part of the large unrecorded trade dynamics in this African country.</description></item><item><title>Understanding the Economic Impact of Vaccination</title><link>/updates/economic-impact-vaccination/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/economic-impact-vaccination/</guid><description>The World Bank East Asia and the Pacific Economic Update April 2022 analyzed challenges and opportunities facing the East Asia and the Pacific (EAP) region.</description></item><item><title>Maldives Development Update (April 2021): A Digital Dawn</title><link>/updates/maldives-development-update/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/maldives-development-update/</guid><description>Authors for the special focus topic (Part B) on digital development: Gohar Malumyan, Junko Narimatsu and Pui Shen Yoong, with guidance from Siddhartha Raja and Fernando Im.</description></item><item><title>Is El Salvador's health care system ready for telemedicine?</title><link>/updates/el-salvador-telemedicine/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/el-salvador-telemedicine/</guid><description>The World Bank&amp;rsquo;s Digital Economy for Latin America (DE4LAC) initiative leveraged data from Ookla for Good™ to analyze El Salvador&amp;rsquo;s telecommunication network to understand to what extent the national healthcare system could leverage the existing digital infrastructure and develop e-health applications.</description></item><item><title>LinkedIn Data Reveals How Labor Markets Have Been Changing in Latin America and the Caribbean Since the Pandemic</title><link>/updates/labor-markets-lac/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/labor-markets-lac/</guid><description>Despite the devastating economic impacts of the COVID-19 pandemic, labor markets in Latin America and the Caribbean (LAC) are on the verge of recovery.</description></item><item><title>Insights from Leveraging Big Data to Track the Impact of the COVID-19 Pandemic on Mobility in Buenos Aires</title><link>/updates/covid-mobility-buenos-aires/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/covid-mobility-buenos-aires/</guid><description>How did the COVID-19 pandemic and the lockdown measures affect mobility in cities around the globe? To inform transport mobility planning, congestion data provided by Waze for Cities was used for a World Bank study on how travel patterns in Buenos Aires changed as a result of pandemic-related restrictions and changing travel preferences.</description></item><item><title>Analyzing the Evolution of Telework Adoption in Latin America and the Caribbean</title><link>/updates/telework-adoption-in-lac/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/telework-adoption-in-lac/</guid><description>Due to the COVID pandemic, the use of telework increased rapidly in Latin America and the Caribbean (LAC) region, as it did globally.</description></item><item><title>Empowering Female Entrepreneurs to Cross Over into Male-Dominated Sectors</title><link>/updates/empowering-female-entrepreneurs-to-cross-over-into-male-dominated-sectors/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/empowering-female-entrepreneurs-to-cross-over-into-male-dominated-sectors/</guid><description>Female entrepreneurship is on the rise globally. However, factors such as social norms and unconscious biases are holding women back from entering more profitable male-dominated sectors.</description></item><item><title>Green Jobs for Women and Diverse Groups Help Promote Equality and Climate Resilience</title><link>/updates/green-jobs-for-women-and-diverse-groups-help-promote-equality-and-climate-resilience/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/green-jobs-for-women-and-diverse-groups-help-promote-equality-and-climate-resilience/</guid><description>The role of women and diverse populations, including indigenous peoples, persons of African descent, persons with disabilities, and LGBTQ+ persons, is crucial in driving the decarbonization process and developing climate change resilience strategies.</description></item><item><title>How Big Data and Machine Learning Can Strengthen Road Safety</title><link>/updates/detecting-urban-clues-for-road-safety/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/detecting-urban-clues-for-road-safety/</guid><description>High-quality and reliable data is necessary to gain useful, actionable insights and enhance road safety conditions. However, collecting data on road safety through manual detection can be expensive, time-consuming, and complex.</description></item><item><title>Why We Should Accelerate the Use of Digital Technologies in Africa</title><link>/updates/africa-digital-transformation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/africa-digital-transformation/</guid><description>As Africa’s population grows, digital technologies are becoming increasingly important for the continent’s economic transformation and job creation. From computers to apps to machine learning, digital technologies offer new opportunities for people and businesses across Africa.</description></item><item><title>Reaching Digital Deserts – Extending Access to Broadband Has Never Been So Important</title><link>/updates/reaching-digital-deserts/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/reaching-digital-deserts/</guid><description>The internet is crucial for us to access information, services, job opportunities, education, and more. However, while urban communities flourish in the online world, many rural communities have been left behind when it comes to ensuring fast and reliable internet access.</description></item><item><title>Development Data Partnership Day 2023</title><link>/updates/partnership-day-2023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/partnership-day-2023/</guid><description>Join us for the Development Data Partnership Day on Wednesday, May 10, 2023, from 9:00 a.m. to 12:30 p.m. US ET in person at the World Bank HQ in Washington, DC.</description></item><item><title>For Reduced Exposure to COVID-19, the Quality of Your Internet Matters</title><link>/updates/covid19-internet-speed-impact/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/covid19-internet-speed-impact/</guid><description>During the height of the COVID-19 pandemic, governments-imposed movement restrictions to curb the spread of the disease. With access to the internet, people could work or study remotely, therefore making it easier for them to adhere to pandemic-related movement restrictions.</description></item><item><title>The Effects of City Growth on Traffic and Urban Mobility</title><link>/updates/city-growth-on-traffic-and-urban-mobility/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/city-growth-on-traffic-and-urban-mobility/</guid><description>The Romanian city of Cluj-Napoca has been deeply affected by urban sprawl, which has strained the city’s traffic system and caused increased congestion on roadways.</description></item><item><title>Heatwaves Data Collaborative</title><link>/updates/heatwavescollaborative/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/heatwavescollaborative/</guid><description>The Heatwaves Data Collaborative knits together efforts by international organizations, private firms, and researchers to develop standard datasets and methodologies for identifying and mitigating the urgent socio-economic impacts of heatwaves.</description></item><item><title>Development Data Partnership Day 2022</title><link>/updates/partnership-day-2022/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/partnership-day-2022/</guid><description>This day is dedicated to addressing global climate, health, and food security challenges through public-private data science collaboration. Speakers from LinkedIn, Google, Data for Good at Meta, Spectus (formerly Cuebiq), Ookla for Good, and Mapbox will share their latest experiences on data science collaboration for public good, while leadership and colleagues from the IDB, UNDP, IMF, and the World Bank will introduce project impacts.</description></item><item><title>Social Norms and Gender Equality in South Asia</title><link>/social-norms-and-gender-equality/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/social-norms-and-gender-equality/</guid><description>This blog highlights recent work from a larger body of research on gender equality carried out at the World Bank. The blog itself relies on Chapter 3 of this report South Asia Economic Focus Reshaping Norms: A New Way Forward.</description></item><item><title>Buenos Aires Transport Demand Planning</title><link>/updates/buenos-aires-transport-demand-planning/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/buenos-aires-transport-demand-planning/</guid><description>Challenge The COVID-19 pandemic and the lockdown measures implemented in 2020 had a significant impact on mobility in the Metropolitan Area of Buenos Aires (AMBA), adding new constrains to the travel behaviours of residents and businesses.</description></item><item><title>Where Did Everyone Go? Potential of Digital Movement Data for Natural Hazards Management</title><link>/updates/potential-of-digital-movement-data-for-natural-hazards-management/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/potential-of-digital-movement-data-for-natural-hazards-management/</guid><description>Every September 19th since the great earthquake of 1985, Mexico City conducts a major drill: people filing out of buildings in an orderly fashion.</description></item><item><title>A Data-Driven Framework to Support Bogota’s Barrios Vitales Project</title><link>/updates/framework-to-support-bogota-barrios-vitales-project/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/framework-to-support-bogota-barrios-vitales-project/</guid><description>A data-driven framework to support the design, implementation, and evaluation of a superblock model in Bogotá from a speed management perspective and inform street design alternatives in the urban space.</description></item><item><title>Communicating for Health: How Did Indians Get Informed about COVID-19 during the Pandemic?</title><link>/updates/communicating-for-health-in-india.md/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/communicating-for-health-in-india.md/</guid><description>The COVID-19 pandemic saw an unprecedented amount of scientific information disseminated: throughout 2020, 11 research articles on COVID-19 were published every hour.</description></item><item><title>Understanding Societal Responses to Policies Undertaken During Emergencies: Lessons from COVID-19’s Second Wave in Maharashtra</title><link>/updates/lessons-from-covid-19-second-wave-in-maharashtra/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/lessons-from-covid-19-second-wave-in-maharashtra/</guid><description>Maharashtra, one of the wealthiest states in India, was among the worst hit by COVID-19, registering nearly 140,000 COVID-19 deaths since the start of the pandemic.</description></item><item><title>Visualizing Millions of Waze Traffic Alerts with BigQuery, H3 and Dask</title><link>/updates/visualizing-millions-of-waze-traffic-alerts-with-google-bigquery-and-dask/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/visualizing-millions-of-waze-traffic-alerts-with-google-bigquery-and-dask/</guid><description>Waze for Cities, a Data Partner of the Development Data Partnership, connects government partners to high quality, frequent and granular traffic data extremely valuable in informing public sector, transport and urban planning as well as addressing the United Nations&amp;rsquo;s Sustainable Development Goals.</description></item><item><title>Understanding the Post COVID-19 Labor Market in Latin America and the Caribbean</title><link>/updates/covid19-labor-markets-observatory/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 13:02:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/covid19-labor-markets-observatory/</guid><description>Challenge The Covid-19 Labor Markets Observatory, managed by the Inter-American Development Bank Labor Markets Division, aimed to understand how COVID-19 has affected labor markets in Latin America and the Caribbean.</description></item><item><title>Digitalization and Resilience to COVID-19 Shocks: Evidence from Sub-Saharan Africa</title><link>/updates/imf-digitalization-in-sub-saharan-africa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/imf-digitalization-in-sub-saharan-africa/</guid><description>Challenge The COVID-19 pandemic has brought major disruption to economic activities and human welfare across the world. Despite the pandemic&amp;rsquo;s late arrival, Sub-Saharan African countries were faced with unprecedented challenges to contain the spread of the pandemic and mitigate the damage to the economy.</description></item><item><title>Facebook’s Covid-19 Trends and Impact Survey</title><link>/updates/facebook-covid-19-trends-and-impact-survey/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/facebook-covid-19-trends-and-impact-survey/</guid><description>With as many as 8 vaccines approved for use around the world the most urgent need now to control the spread of the novel coronavirus is increasing vaccination rates.</description></item><item><title>Unlocking Mobility: TapTap Maps in Cap-Haïtien</title><link>/updates/unlocking-mobility-taptap-maps-in-cap-haitien/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 13:02:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/unlocking-mobility-taptap-maps-in-cap-haitien/</guid><description>Challenge Haitian cities suffer from poor transportation services, and the lack of data from existing services limits improvement efforts. Tap Taps are the most popular motorized transportation mode employed across Haiti, yet there is not enough data on them as they are informal, private, and marginally regulated.</description></item><item><title>Improving Public Space and Market Design During COVID-19</title><link>/updates/improving-public-space-and-market-design-during-covid-19/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 13:02:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/improving-public-space-and-market-design-during-covid-19/</guid><description>Lima’s Central Market has always been one of the busiest and liveliest in Lima, Peru. Before the pandemic, some hundreds of people gathered there to buy and sell groceries, clothes, electronics&amp;ndash;you name it.</description></item><item><title>The IMF's New Climate Change Indicators Dashboard: Experimental Data for Economic and Financial Analysis</title><link>/updates/imf-climate-change-dashboard/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/imf-climate-change-dashboard/</guid><description>To develop the right measures to tackle climate change, governments need robust and comparable data. The new IMF Dashboard will help fill data gaps, so policymakers can undertake the macroeconomic and financial analysis that underpins effective policies</description></item><item><title>Mapping Entrepreneurs' Response to COVID-19 in Latin America and the Caribbean</title><link>/updates/mapping-entrepreneurs-response-to-covid-19-in-latin-america-and-the-caribbean/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 13:02:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/mapping-entrepreneurs-response-to-covid-19-in-latin-america-and-the-caribbean/</guid><description>Challenge The social and economic disruption caused by Covid-19 led to numerous challenges to conduct businesses, provide essential services, and attend to the most basic well-being needs around the globe.</description></item><item><title>The Effect of COVID-19 Lockdown Measures on Internet Speed</title><link>/updates/covid-19-digital-divide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/covid-19-digital-divide/</guid><description>COVID-19 and the related lockdown measures to prevent the virus’ spread have highlighted how important it is for everyone to have access to reliable and resilient digital infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Examining the Economic Impact of COVID-19 in India through Daily Electricity Consumption and Nighttime Light Intensity</title><link>/updates/examining-the-economic-impact-of-covid-19-in-india-through-daily-electricity-consumption-and-nighttime-light-intensity/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/examining-the-economic-impact-of-covid-19-in-india-through-daily-electricity-consumption-and-nighttime-light-intensity/</guid><description>Challenge The COVID-19 pandemic has disrupted economic activity in India. When COVID-19 started to spread in India through domestic contagion, the authorities enacted a series of measures to combat the pandemic, including a strict national lockdown from March 25 to May 4 that strongly disrupted economic activity.</description></item><item><title>Optimizing Tourism Investments: Identifying Chokepoints and Underperforming Minor Roads in Sri Lanka</title><link>/updates/optimizing-tourism-investments-identifying-chokepoints-and-underperforming-minor-roads-in-sri-lanka/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/optimizing-tourism-investments-identifying-chokepoints-and-underperforming-minor-roads-in-sri-lanka/</guid><description>Challenge Connected and maintained transportation infrastructure are critical to sustainable economic development, but most current estimation methods of road quality are labor, time, and cost intensive.</description></item><item><title>Socioeconomic Impact of COVID-19 in Indonesia</title><link>/updates/covid-19-observatory/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/covid-19-observatory/</guid><description>Challenge Although there is a widespread awareness of the pandemic, there is a lack of understanding from citizens’ perspective, especially behaviors it triggers, sentiments towards government as well as rising concerns.</description></item><item><title>A Light Primer to Spark / Databricks</title><link>/updates/light-primer-to-spark-databricks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/light-primer-to-spark-databricks/</guid><description>Databricks is a powerful platform for using Spark, a powerful data technology.
If you&amp;rsquo;re reading this, you&amp;rsquo;re likely a Python or R developer who begins their Spark journey to process large datasets.</description></item><item><title>Estimating High-speed Broadband Coverage in Ukraine</title><link>/updates/estimating-high-speed-broadband-coverage-in-ukraine/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/estimating-high-speed-broadband-coverage-in-ukraine/</guid><description>Challenge Ukraine, Europe’s biggest country, has over 1,192 operators and providers, of which close to three quarters operate under a special preferential tax regime, allowing them not to report their coverage/subscription data to the national telecom regulatory authority.</description></item><item><title>2020 Inspire Challenge Finalist - The ClimaCell Locust Project</title><link>/updates/inspire-challenge-finalist-the-climacell-locust-project/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/inspire-challenge-finalist-the-climacell-locust-project/</guid><description>Ag Observatory in collaboration with the World Bank Data Lab guided and facilitated Climacell&amp;rsquo;s entry into the CGIAR Big Data Inspire Challenge 2020.</description></item><item><title>Economic Anxiety and COVID-19 in Southeast Asia</title><link>/updates/economic-anxiety-and-covid-19-in-southeast-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/economic-anxiety-and-covid-19-in-southeast-asia/</guid><description>Challenge The COVID-19 pandemic has affected the global economy through lockdowns, disrupted supply chains and uncertain economic outlooks. Swift reaction by policy makers are required to prevent a deep recession.</description></item><item><title>Analyzing Spatial Accessibility of Health Facilities in Indonesia and Philippines</title><link>/updates/planning-for-equitable-access-to-health-infrastructure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/planning-for-equitable-access-to-health-infrastructure/</guid><description>Challenge: Indonesia and the Philippines are archipelagos, where geographic and administrative boundaries are similar. The collection of islands is home to different concentrations of ethnic, cultural, linguistic, and socioeconomic groups, with an imbalanced distribution of health facilities and physicians.</description></item><item><title>Mapbox Releases a New Movement Dataset for Mobility Insights</title><link>/updates/introducing-mapbox-movement-data/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/introducing-mapbox-movement-data/</guid><description>Following the Development Data Partnership launch event at the World Bank-IMF Annual Meetings, Mapbox announced a new dataset on movement data for mobility insights.</description></item><item><title>Data Partnership: Bridging the Data Gap for Public Good</title><link>/annualmeetings2020/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/annualmeetings2020/</guid><description>Download Event Program High frequency, timely, and granular information &amp;ndash; which is routinely collected by the private sector&amp;ndash;can help inform public policy and service delivery.</description></item><item><title>Tackling COVID-19 Second Wave using Facebook Mobility Data in Vietnam</title><link>/updates/tackling-covid19-second-wave-using-facebook-mobility-data-in-vietnam/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/tackling-covid19-second-wave-using-facebook-mobility-data-in-vietnam/</guid><description>Challenge: On July 24, after 99 days of zero community-transmitted COVID-19 infections, a 57 year-old man tested positive in Danang, a major city in central Vietnam with close to 1.</description></item><item><title>Assessing Social Inequality and Lockdown Policies using Mobile Location Data in Indonesia</title><link>/updates/social-inequality-and-lockdown-policies/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 13:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/social-inequality-and-lockdown-policies/</guid><description>Challenge Lockdown policies such as stay-at-home orders and non-essential business closures are central to fighting the novel coronavirus. However, policy makers are having a hard time answering key questions about their efficacy.</description></item><item><title>Introducing the Data Partnership on GitHub</title><link>/updates/introducing-the-development-data-partnership-on-github/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/introducing-the-development-data-partnership-on-github/</guid><description>After launching in 2019, when the Inter-American Development Bank and the International Monetary Fund joined the initiave, the Development Data Partnership has scaled up fast, with more than 100 projects having been brought to life supported by partnerships with more than 20 companies.</description></item><item><title>Leveraging New Data Methods to Address an Ancient Challenge: Locusts</title><link>/updates/climacell-24-hour-hackathon-to-help-address-the-locust-spread-in-africa-and-beyond/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 13:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/climacell-24-hour-hackathon-to-help-address-the-locust-spread-in-africa-and-beyond/</guid><description>Challenge: The worst locust upsurge in at least 25 years is hitting parts of Africa, the Arabian Peninsula and Western Asia, and over 40 million people who are already food insecure find their food supply and livelihoods threatened.</description></item><item><title>How to Find Population Movement Data for Your Country: The Mobile Location Data Inventory</title><link>/updates/find-population-movement-data-for-your-country/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/find-population-movement-data-for-your-country/</guid><description>As the COVID-19 pandemic continues, so have measures to mitigate its spread. Physical distancing and movement restrictions – such as school and workplace closures, public event cancellations, stay-at-home orders, and international and domestic travel bans – vary considerably across countries.</description></item><item><title>Google, Apple, and Facebook: Understanding Mobility during Social Distancing with Private Sector Data</title><link>/updates/mobility-during-social-distancing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/mobility-during-social-distancing/</guid><description>As countries around the world work to contain the spread and impact of COVID-19, the World Bank Group is moving quickly to provide fast, flexible responses to help developing countries strengthen their pandemic response and health care systems.</description></item><item><title>Addressing COVID-19 through Public-Private Data Partnerships: Where Do We Put New Testing Facilities?</title><link>/updates/covid19-and-public-private-data-partnerships/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 20:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/covid19-and-public-private-data-partnerships/</guid><description>Background
As the COVID-19 pandemic evolves, the World Bank is ramping up its response to help countries around the world. The Bank recently announced $14 billion emergency support program, for which a key pillar is to help countries strengthen their capacity to monitor and respond to the spread of the virus.</description></item><item><title>A New Predictive Model for More Accurate Electrical Grid Mapping</title><link>/updates/more-accurate-electrical-grid-mapping/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 21:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/more-accurate-electrical-grid-mapping/</guid><description>Challenge: When planning connectivity deployments in emerging markets, it is important to have a clear picture of where existing power lines are placed.</description></item><item><title>Estimating Access to Employment Opportunities in Dhaka, Bangladesh</title><link>/updates/employment-opportunities-in-bangladesh/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 21:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/employment-opportunities-in-bangladesh/</guid><description>Challenge: Poor transport facilities and infrastructure are a major hindrance to Bangladesh’s economic development. The road network in Dhaka is severely congested.</description></item><item><title>Tackling the Global Profitarchy–Gender and the Choice of Business Sector</title><link>/updates/tackling-the-global-profitarchy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 21:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/tackling-the-global-profitarchy/</guid><description>Challenge: Despite significant progress in women’s educational attainment and higher female labor force participation rates in many countries, progress in closing the gender pay gap, which takes the ratio of median earnings of all women to all men, has been slow.</description></item><item><title>Improving Road Safety in Nairobi</title><link>/updates/improving-road-safety-in-nairobi/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 20:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/improving-road-safety-in-nairobi/</guid><description>“Data Partnership brings domain expertise. Google brings data expertise. Together we impact real world problems.”
&amp;ndash;Google’s Bailey-Galvis noted at a Data Partnership event in early February 2019</description></item><item><title>On Responsible Data Use</title><link>/updates/responsible-data-use/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 21:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/responsible-data-use/</guid><description>As we develop the Data Partnership, we have a responsibility to the people impacted by our initiative &amp;ndash; to local governments and partners, and to our own organizations &amp;ndash; to think about how we are collecting, using, storing, and sharing information.</description></item><item><title>Mapping Freetown Transit for Resiliency</title><link>/updates/mapping-freetown-transit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 20:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/mapping-freetown-transit/</guid><description>Challenge: The resiliency of a transport network is a critical component to the stability and prosperity of a city. Freetown, prone to flooding and landslides, struggles to maintain services throughout the year.</description></item><item><title>Why Data Partnership?</title><link>/updates/why-datacollaboratives/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/why-datacollaboratives/</guid><description>Should the private sector ever share data with the public sector, even if for public good? Well, it depends.
Most of us are in agreement that when companies collect our data as a natural by-product of providing a service – like our movement data or spending patterns – the company shouldn’t sell these data to a third party for profit, especially without transparency.</description></item><item><title>Data Partner Lightning Talks</title><link>/updates/data-day/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 21:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/data-day/</guid><description>On February 13, 2019, the Data Partnership (formerly Data Collaboratives), for the first time, brought together Partners and staff. More than 200 colleagues joined the standing-room-only event, in person and online, learning about how private data partnerships can be made to work for public good.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>The Development Data Partnership is a collaboration between international organizations and technology companies, facilitating the efficient and responsible use of third-party data in international development.</description></item><item><title>African Development Bank</title><link>/development-partners/afdb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/development-partners/afdb/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Asian Develpment Bank</title><link>/development-partners/adb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/development-partners/adb/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Atlas AI</title><link>/partners/atlasai/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/atlasai/</guid><description/></item><item><title>constellr</title><link>/partners/constellr/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/constellr/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Development Bank of Latin America and the Caribbean</title><link>/development-partners/caf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/development-partners/caf/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Earth Genome</title><link>/partners/earthgenome/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/earthgenome/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Earthmetry</title><link>/partners/earthmetry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/earthmetry/</guid><description/></item><item><title>ESA</title><link>/partners/esa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/esa/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Esri</title><link>/partners/esri/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/esri/</guid><description/></item><item><title>European Bank for Reconstruction and Development</title><link>/development-partners/ebrd/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/development-partners/ebrd/</guid><description/></item><item><title>European Investment Bank</title><link>/development-partners/eib/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/development-partners/eib/</guid><description/></item><item><title>GitHub</title><link>/partners/github/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/github/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Google</title><link>/partners/google/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/google/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Homebase</title><link>/partners/homebase/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/homebase/</guid><description/></item><item><title>IDB Invest</title><link>/development-partners/idb_invest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/development-partners/idb_invest/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Inter-American Development Bank</title><link>/development-partners/iadb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/development-partners/iadb/</guid><description/></item><item><title>International Monetary Fund</title><link>/development-partners/imf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/development-partners/imf/</guid><description/></item><item><title>JBA</title><link>/partners/jba/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/jba/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Khalti</title><link>/partners/khalti/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/khalti/</guid><description/></item><item><title>LinkedIn</title><link>/partners/linkedin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/linkedin/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Mapbox</title><link>/partners/mapbox/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/mapbox/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Mapillary</title><link>/partners/mapillary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/mapillary/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Meta</title><link>/partners/meta/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/meta/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Microsoft</title><link>/partners/microsoft/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/microsoft/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Ookla</title><link>/partners/ookla/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/ookla/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Orbital Insight</title><link>/partners/orbitalinsight/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/orbitalinsight/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development</title><link>/development-partners/oecd/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/development-partners/oecd/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Planet</title><link>/partners/planet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/planet/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Plume Labs</title><link>/partners/plumelabs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/plumelabs/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Premise</title><link>/partners/premise/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/premise/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Quadrant</title><link>/partners/quadrant/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/quadrant/</guid><description/></item><item><title>QuantCube</title><link>/partners/quantcube/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/quantcube/</guid><description/></item><item><title>SpaceKnow</title><link>/partners/spaceknow/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/spaceknow/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Spectus</title><link>/partners/spectus/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/spectus/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Startlink</title><link>/partners/starlink/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/starlink/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Tomorrow.io</title><link>/partners/tomorrowio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/tomorrowio/</guid><description/></item><item><title>UNICEF</title><link>/development-partners/unicef/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/development-partners/unicef/</guid><description/></item><item><title>United Nations Development Programme</title><link>/development-partners/undp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/development-partners/undp/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Waze</title><link>/partners/waze/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/waze/</guid><description/></item><item><title>World Bank Group</title><link>/development-partners/worldbank/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/development-partners/worldbank/</guid><description/></item><item><title>World Data Lab</title><link>/partners/wdl/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/wdl/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>