<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Development Data Partnership</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on Development Data Partnership</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 13:02:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation</title><link>/donors/bmgf/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/donors/bmgf/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Legal Foundation</title><link>/pillars/legal/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 21:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/pillars/legal/</guid><description>Template data license agreements and MOUs between organizations save time and resources.</description></item><item><title>Partnership</title><link>/how-it-works/step-1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 21:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/how-it-works/step-1/</guid><description>Standard data licenses are signed between the data partner and each participating organization (e.g., World Bank, IMF, IDB).</description></item><item><title>Responsible data use</title><link>/news/responsible-data-use/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 21:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/news/responsible-data-use/</guid><description>USAID and Data Collabortives co-corganized an interactve workshop on approaches to responsible data use in international development.</description></item><item><title>Short Term Impact</title><link>/impact/short-term/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 21:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/impact/short-term/</guid><description>Since the World Bank launched the beta Data Partnership platform in April 2018 (then called &amp;ldquo;Data Collaboratives&amp;rdquo;), more than 100 development projects are now under implementation.</description></item><item><title>WHY PARTNERSHIP</title><link>/business-case/why-data-sharing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 21:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/business-case/why-data-sharing/</guid><description>Public policy and provision of public infrastructure and services are heavily dependent on data – higher quality, timely data translates into more effective sector and program prioritization, design, implementation, monitoring, and evaluation.</description></item><item><title>Data Partner</title><link>/how-to-engage/data-partner/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 21:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/how-to-engage/data-partner/</guid><description>The Partnership unlocks public good opportunities from proprietary data in a secure, responsible manner. Partnerships can be leveraged to open markets in emerging economies, receive new data methods and algorithms, and increase staff skills through collaboration and secondment opportunities.</description></item><item><title>Development Partner</title><link>/how-to-engage/consortium/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 21:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/how-to-engage/consortium/</guid><description>The Partnership is open to donors and entities engaged in international development work. Members have access to the Data Partnership web platform and IT infrastructure and are invited to participate in exchanges and training activities.</description></item><item><title>KEY CHALLENGES</title><link>/business-case/why-data-partnerships/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 21:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/business-case/why-data-partnerships/</guid><description>Despite the potential benefits, there are challenges in linking the supply of proprietary data and the demand for these data for public benefit.</description></item><item><title>Long Term Impact</title><link>/impact/long-term/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 21:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/impact/long-term/</guid><description>By learning through real project implementation, the Partnership aims to transform proprietary datasets into sustainably generated, sharable insights for improving public sector services and infrastructure in emerging economies.</description></item><item><title>Project Proposals</title><link>/how-it-works/step-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 21:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/how-it-works/step-2/</guid><description>Data partner uses the Partnership web platform to evaluate proposals for using their data in a project or produce a &amp;ldquo;data good&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Responsible Data Use</title><link>/pillars/access/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 21:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/pillars/access/</guid><description>Data governance principles guide best practices for responsible and ethical data use.</description></item><item><title>Data Management</title><link>/how-it-works/step-3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 21:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/how-it-works/step-3/</guid><description>Upon project approval, data are securely and responsibly managed on behalf of all staff through the Partnership IT architecture and procedures.</description></item><item><title>Multi-Disciplinary Teams</title><link>/pillars/multi-disciplinary-teams/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 21:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/pillars/multi-disciplinary-teams/</guid><description>Working groups comprised of data engineers, data scientists, sector domain experts, legal counsel, communications specialists, procurement specialists, and others across the member organizations make a complete platform possible.</description></item><item><title>OPPORTUNITY</title><link>/business-case/opportunity/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 21:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/business-case/opportunity/</guid><description>The Development Data Partnership has been designed to overcome these supply and demand challenges at scale. Specifically, the Partnership: (a) coordinates and aggregates demand on behalf of public actors; (b) links public sector challenges and domain expertise to relevant proprietary data; (c) significantly reduces the transaction costs associated with data sharing; (d) reduces duplication of effort and facilitates collaboration on development of solutions; and (e) increases transparency and accountability for integrating use of proprietary data in public good analytics.</description></item><item><title>Data Goods</title><link>/how-it-works/step-4/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 21:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/how-it-works/step-4/</guid><description>Data partners are kept updated through the Partnership web platform of derived data products and produced code.</description></item><item><title>Secure IT Architecture</title><link>/pillars/it-architecture/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 21:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/pillars/it-architecture/</guid><description>Centralized IT architecture and processes for ingesting, storing and processing data, as well as for coding collaboration, create economies of scale amongst partners and facilitate secure data use.</description></item><item><title>Data Partnership Management</title><link>/pillars/data-partnership-management/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 21:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/pillars/data-partnership-management/</guid><description>A web-based partnership management platform ensures the value proposition for data partners is met.</description></item><item><title>Data Goods</title><link>/pillars/derived-data-products/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 21:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/pillars/derived-data-products/</guid><description>Managed, accessible repositories for derived data products and algorithms broaden Partnership impact.</description></item><item><title>Mapping entrepreneurs' response to COVID-19 in Latin America and the Caribbean</title><link>/updates/mapping-entrepreneurs-response-to-covid-19-in-latin-america-and-the-caribbean/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 13:02:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/mapping-entrepreneurs-response-to-covid-19-in-latin-america-and-the-caribbean/</guid><description>Challenge: The social and economic disruption caused by Covid-19 led to numerous challenges to conduct businesses, provide essential services, and attend to the most basic well-being needs around the globe.</description></item><item><title>The Effect of COVID-19 Lockdown Measures on Internet Speed</title><link>/covid19-lockdown-measures-internet-speed-africa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/covid19-lockdown-measures-internet-speed-africa/</guid><description>COVID-19 and the related lockdown measures to prevent the virus’ spread have highlighted how important it is for everyone to have access to reliable and resilient digital infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Examining the Economic Impact of COVID-19 in India through Daily Electricity Consumption and Nighttime Light Intensity</title><link>/economic-impact-covid-19-in-india-through-daily-electricity-consumption-and-nighttime-light-intensity/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/economic-impact-covid-19-in-india-through-daily-electricity-consumption-and-nighttime-light-intensity/</guid><description>Challenge: The COVID-19 pandemic has disrupted economic activity in India. When COVID-19 started to spread in India through domestic contagion, the authorities enacted a series of measures to combat the pandemic, including a strict national lockdown from March 25 to May 4 that strongly disrupted economic activity.</description></item><item><title>Optimizing Tourism Investments: Identifying Chokepoints and Underperforming Minor Roads in Sri Lanka</title><link>/updates/optimizing-tourism-investments-identifying-chokepoints-and-underperforming-minor-roads-in-sri-lanka/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/optimizing-tourism-investments-identifying-chokepoints-and-underperforming-minor-roads-in-sri-lanka/</guid><description>Challenge: Connected and maintained transportation infrastructure are critical to sustainable economic development, but most current estimation methods of road quality are labor, time, and cost intensive.</description></item><item><title>Examining the Economic Impact of India’s Zone Classification to contain COVID-19</title><link>/india-zone-classification-impact-of-covid19/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/india-zone-classification-impact-of-covid19/</guid><description>Challenge: The COVID-19 pandemic has disrupted economic activity in India. When COVID-19 started to spread in India through domestic contagion, the Indian authorities enacted a series of measures to combat the pandemic, including a strict national lockdown from March 25 to May 4.</description></item><item><title>Socioeconomic Impact of COVID-19 in Indonesia</title><link>/covid-observatory-indonesia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/covid-observatory-indonesia/</guid><description>Challenge: Although there is a widespread awareness of the pandemic, there is a lack of understanding from citizens’ perspective, especially behaviors it triggers, sentiments towards government as well as rising concerns.</description></item><item><title>A Light Primer to Spark / Databricks</title><link>/light-primer-to-spark-databricks-1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/light-primer-to-spark-databricks-1/</guid><description>Databricks is a powerful platform for using Spark, a powerful data technology.
If you&amp;rsquo;re reading this, you&amp;rsquo;re likely a Python or R developer who begins their Spark journey to process large datasets.</description></item><item><title>Estimating High-speed Broadband Coverage in Ukraine</title><link>/broadband-coverage-in-ukraine/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/broadband-coverage-in-ukraine/</guid><description>Challenge: Ukraine, Europe’s biggest country, has over 1,192 operators and providers, of which close to three quarters operate under a special preferential tax regime, allowing them not to report their coverage/subscription data to the national telecom regulatory authority.</description></item><item><title>2020 Inspire Challenge Finalist - The ClimaCell Locust Project</title><link>/2020-inspire-challenge-finalist-locust-project/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/2020-inspire-challenge-finalist-locust-project/</guid><description>Ag Observatory in collaboration with the World Bank Data Lab guided and facilitated Climacell&amp;rsquo;s entry into the CGIAR Big Data Inspire Challenge 2020.</description></item><item><title>Economic Anxiety and COVID-19 in Southeast Asia</title><link>/economic-anxiety-covid19-se-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/economic-anxiety-covid19-se-asia/</guid><description>Challenge: The COVID-19 pandemic has affected the global economy through lockdowns, disrupted supply chains and uncertain economic outlooks. Swift reaction by policy makers are required to prevent a deep recession.</description></item><item><title>Analyzing Spatial Accessibility of Health Facilities in Indonesia and Philippines</title><link>/planning-for-equitable-access-to-health-infrastructure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/planning-for-equitable-access-to-health-infrastructure/</guid><description>Challenge: Indonesia and the Philippines are archipelagos, where geographic and administrative boundaries are similar. The collection of islands is home to different concentrations of ethnic, cultural, linguistic, and socioeconomic groups, with an imbalanced distribution of health facilities and physicians.</description></item><item><title>Mapbox Releases a New Movement Dataset for Mobility Insights</title><link>/introducing-mapbox-movement-data/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/introducing-mapbox-movement-data/</guid><description>Following the Development Data Partnership launch event at the World Bank-IMF Annual Meetings, Mapbox announces a new dataset on movement data for mobility insights.</description></item><item><title>Data Partnership: Bridging the Data Gap for Public Good</title><link>/annualmeetings2020/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/annualmeetings2020/</guid><description>Download Event Program High frequency, timely, and granular information &amp;ndash; which is routinely collected by the private sector&amp;ndash;can help inform public policy and service delivery.</description></item><item><title>Tackling COVID-19 Second Wave using Facebook Mobility Data in Vietnam</title><link>/updates/tackling-covid19-second-wave-using-facebook-mobility-data-in-vietnam/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/tackling-covid19-second-wave-using-facebook-mobility-data-in-vietnam/</guid><description>Challenge: On July 24, after 99 days of zero community-transmitted COVID-19 infections, a 57 year-old man tested positive in Danang, a major city in central Vietnam with close to 1.</description></item><item><title>Assessing Social Inequality and Lockdown Policies using Mobile Location Data in Indonesia</title><link>/updates/social-inequality-and-lockdown-policies/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 13:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/social-inequality-and-lockdown-policies/</guid><description>Challenge: Lockdown policies such as stay-at-home orders and non-essential business closures are central to fighting the novel coronavirus. However, policy makers are having a hard time answering key questions about their efficacy.</description></item><item><title>Introducing the Data Partnership on GitHub</title><link>/updates/introducing-the-data-partnership-hub/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/introducing-the-data-partnership-hub/</guid><description>After launching in 2019, when the Inter-American Development Bank and the International Monetary Fund joined the initiave, the Development Data Partnership has scaled up fast, with more than 100 projects having been brought to life supported by partnerships with more than 20 companies.</description></item><item><title>Leveraging New Data Methods to Address an Ancient Challenge: Locusts</title><link>/updates/climacell-24-hour-hackathon-to-help-address-the-locust-spread-in-africa-and-beyond/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 13:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/climacell-24-hour-hackathon-to-help-address-the-locust-spread-in-africa-and-beyond/</guid><description>Challenge: The worst locust upsurge in at least 25 years is hitting parts of Africa, the Arabian Peninsula and Western Asia, and over 40 million people who are already food insecure find their food supply and livelihoods threatened.</description></item><item><title>How to Find Population Movement Data for Your Country: The Mobile Location Data Inventory</title><link>/updates/find-population-movement-data-for-your-country/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/find-population-movement-data-for-your-country/</guid><description>As the COVID-19 pandemic continues, so have measures to mitigate its spread. Physical distancing and movement restrictions – such as school and workplace closures, public event cancellations, stay-at-home orders, and international and domestic travel bans – vary considerably across countries.</description></item><item><title>Mobile Location Data Inventory</title><link>/pages/mobility-data-dashboard-by-country/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/pages/mobility-data-dashboard-by-country/</guid><description>var divElement = document.getElementById('viz1593018616750'); var vizElement = divElement.getElementsByTagName('object')[0]; if(divElement.offsetWidth 800) { vizElement.style.width = '1100px'; vizElement.</description></item><item><title>Mobile Location Data Inventory</title><link>/pages/mobility-data-dashboard-main/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/pages/mobility-data-dashboard-main/</guid><description>var divElement = document.getElementById('viz1593016125962'); var vizElement = divElement.getElementsByTagName('object')[0]; if(divElement.offsetWidth 800) { vizElement.style.width = '1100px'; vizElement.</description></item><item><title>Google, Apple, and Facebook: Understanding Mobility during Social Distancing with Private Sector Data</title><link>/updates/understanding-mobility-during-social-distancing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/understanding-mobility-during-social-distancing/</guid><description>As countries around the world work to contain the spread and impact of COVID-19, the World Bank Group is moving quickly to provide fast, flexible responses to help developing countries strengthen their pandemic response and health care systems.</description></item><item><title>Addressing COVID-19 through Public-Private Data Partnerships -- Where Do We Put New Testing Facilities?</title><link>/updates/covid19-and-public-private-data-partnerships/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 20:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/covid19-and-public-private-data-partnerships/</guid><description>Background
As the COVID-19 pandemic evolves, the World Bank is ramping up its response to help countries around the world. The Bank recently announced $14 billion emergency support program, for which a key pillar is to help countries strengthen their capacity to monitor and respond to the spread of the virus.</description></item><item><title>A New Predictive Model for More Accurate Electrical Grid Mapping</title><link>/updates/more-accurate-electrical-grid-mapping/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 21:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/more-accurate-electrical-grid-mapping/</guid><description>Challenge: When planning connectivity deployments in emerging markets, it is important to have a clear picture of where existing power lines are placed.</description></item><item><title>Estimating Access to Employment Opportunities in Dhaka, Bangladesh</title><link>/updates/employment-opportunities-in-bangladesh/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 21:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/employment-opportunities-in-bangladesh/</guid><description>Challenge: Poor transport facilities and infrastructure are a major hindrance to Bangladesh’s economic development. The road network in Dhaka is severely congested.</description></item><item><title>Tackling the Global Profitarchy–Gender and the Choice of Business Sector</title><link>/updates/tackling-the-global-profitarchy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 21:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/tackling-the-global-profitarchy/</guid><description>Challenge: Despite significant progress in women’s educational attainment and higher female labor force participation rates in many countries, progress in closing the gender pay gap, which takes the ratio of median earnings of all women to all men, has been slow.</description></item><item><title>Why Data Partnership?</title><link>/updates/why-datacollaboratives/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/why-datacollaboratives/</guid><description>Should the private sector ever share data with the public sector, even if for public good? Well, it depends.
Most of us are in agreement that when companies collect our data as a natural by-product of providing a service – like our movement data or spending patterns – the company shouldn’t sell these data to a third party for profit, especially without transparency.</description></item><item><title>Improving Road Safety in Nairobi</title><link>/updates/improving-road-safety-in-nairobi/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 20:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/improving-road-safety-in-nairobi/</guid><description>Challenge: Kenya has one of the highest estimated crash fatality rates worldwide but is challenged to address the problem without adequate data.</description></item><item><title>On Responsible Data Use</title><link>/updates/responsible-data-use/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 21:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/responsible-data-use/</guid><description>As we develop the Data Partnership, we have a responsibility to the people impacted by our initiative &amp;ndash; to local governments and partners, and to our own organizations &amp;ndash; to think about how we are collecting, using, storing, and sharing information.</description></item><item><title>Mapping Freetown Transit for Resiliency</title><link>/updates/mapping-freetown-transit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 20:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/mapping-freetown-transit/</guid><description>Challenge: The resiliency of a transport network is a critical component to the stability and prosperity of a city. Freetown, prone to flooding and landslides, struggles to maintain services throughout the year.</description></item><item><title>Building Urban Resilience by Mapping Formal/Informal Transit for Freetown, Sierra Leone.</title><link>/projects/wmt-freetown/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 21:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/projects/wmt-freetown/</guid><description>The team is receiving pro-bono data collection and processing and support from Where Is My Transport, for creating the first complete map of the Freetown transit system.</description></item><item><title>Closing the Data Gap in Bicycle Planning and Evaluation Efforts: Toolkit for Mexico City.</title><link>/projects/mobike-mexico-city/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 21:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/projects/mobike-mexico-city/</guid><description>The team has received dockless bikeshare trip data from Mobike, which they are integrating with multiple data sources to improve planning cycling and pedestrian infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Data Fusion for Outbreak Prediction</title><link>/projects/google-health-trend-api-data-fusion/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 21:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/projects/google-health-trend-api-data-fusion/</guid><description>The team is using the Google Health Trends API, combined with data from Twitter and news APIs (Data Collaboratives covers the Google partnership) to improve prediction of outbreaks in fragile states.</description></item><item><title>Identifying Crash Hotspots in Nairobi</title><link>/projects/waze-nairobi/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 21:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/projects/waze-nairobi/</guid><description>The team is using the Waze API to analyse user-reported crash data in Nairobi and comparing these data to official records as part of a road safety investment program.</description></item><item><title>Informing Emissions Mitigation and Livlihoods Enhancement Work in Fiji with Remote Sensing</title><link>/projects/digital-globe-remote-sensing-fiji/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 21:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/projects/digital-globe-remote-sensing-fiji/</guid><description>The team is using Digital Globe data on Fiji from 2006 to 2016 to assess land use change and forestation levels.</description></item><item><title>Data Partner Lightning Talks</title><link>/updates/data-day/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 21:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/data-day/</guid><description>On February 13, 2019, the Data Partnership (formerly Data Collaboratives), for the first time, brought together Partners and staff. More than 200 colleagues joined the standing-room-only event, in person and online, learning about how private data partnerships can be made to work for public good.</description></item><item><title>Carto</title><link>/partners/carto/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/carto/</guid><description/></item><item><title>ClimaCell</title><link>/partners/climacell/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/climacell/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Cuebiq</title><link>/partners/cuebiq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/cuebiq/</guid><description/></item><item><title>ESA</title><link>/partners/esa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/esa/</guid><description/></item><item><title>ESRI</title><link>/partners/esri/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/esri/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Facebook</title><link>/partners/facebook/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/facebook/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Google</title><link>/partners/google/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/google/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Indigo</title><link>/partners/indigo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/indigo/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Khalti</title><link>/partners/khalti/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/khalti/</guid><description/></item><item><title>LinkedIn</title><link>/partners/linkedin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/linkedin/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Mapbox</title><link>/partners/mapbox/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/mapbox/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Mapillary</title><link>/partners/mapillary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/mapillary/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Ola Cabs</title><link>/partners/ola/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/ola/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Ookla</title><link>/partners/ookla/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/ookla/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Orbital Insight</title><link>/partners/orbitalinsight/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/orbitalinsight/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Premise</title><link>/partners/premise/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/premise/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Safegraph</title><link>/partners/safegraph/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/safegraph/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Twitter</title><link>/partners/twitter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/twitter/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Unacast</title><link>/partners/unacast/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/unacast/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Veraset</title><link>/partners/veraset/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/veraset/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Waze</title><link>/partners/waze/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/waze/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Where Is My Transport</title><link>/partners/whereismytranspost/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/whereismytranspost/</guid><description/></item><item><title>X-Mode</title><link>/partners/x-mode/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/x-mode/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>