<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Digital Development on Development Data Partnership</title><link>/tags/digital-development/</link><description>Recent content in Digital Development on Development Data Partnership</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/digital-development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Assessing Internet Quality in the Eastern Partnership (EaP) Countries</title><link>/updates/assessing-internet-quality-in-the-eastern-partnership-countries/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/assessing-internet-quality-in-the-eastern-partnership-countries/</guid><description>Reliable internet is essential for inclusive public service delivery, enabling digital learning in schools, electronic health systems in clinics, and efficient government services.</description></item><item><title>Investing in the Future: Connecting Guatemala’s Schools to the Internet</title><link>/updates/investing-in-the-future-connecting-guatemala-schools-to-the-internet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/investing-in-the-future-connecting-guatemala-schools-to-the-internet/</guid><description>Access to the internet is essential for quality education and opportunities, especially in low-income countries. The Inter-American Development Bank (IDB) collaborated with the International Telecommunication Union (ITU) to bridge Guatemala’s school connectivity gap, with support from Ookla®.</description></item><item><title>Data for Impact: South-South Cooperation in Action</title><link>/updates/data-for-impact-south-south-cooperation-in-action/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/data-for-impact-south-south-cooperation-in-action/</guid><description>On September 12, the International Day for South-South Cooperation, we celebrate how countries across the Global South are working together to solve shared development challenges.</description></item><item><title>Enhancing E-Health Accessibility: Bridging the Digital Divide in Healthcare Services in Least Developed Countries</title><link>/updates/enhancing-e-health-accessibility-bridging-the-digital-divide-in-healthcare-services-in-least-developed-countries/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/enhancing-e-health-accessibility-bridging-the-digital-divide-in-healthcare-services-in-least-developed-countries/</guid><description>The imperative to enhance equitable access to healthcare through e-health services has never been more pronounced, especially in light of crises such as the COVID-19 pandemic.</description></item><item><title>Mobile Internet Connectivity and Household Wealth in the Philippines</title><link>/updates/mobile-internet-connectivity-and-household-wealth-in-the-philippines/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/mobile-internet-connectivity-and-household-wealth-in-the-philippines/</guid><description>The rapid expansion of mobile internet has resulted in significant economic and social impacts. Therefore, it is essential to comprehend how policymakers can maximize the economic benefits of internet accessibility.</description></item><item><title>How to Leverage Data for Better Transport, Digital Connectivity, and Sustainable Development in the Amazon</title><link>/updates/how-to-leverage-data-for-better-transport-digital-connectivity-and-sustainable-development-in-the-amazon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/how-to-leverage-data-for-better-transport-digital-connectivity-and-sustainable-development-in-the-amazon/</guid><description>The World Bank Transport team used data from Google, Mapbox, Meta, and Ookla to identify infrastructure gaps in the Amazon areas of Brazil, Colombia and Peru.</description></item><item><title>Impact of the Availability of ChatGPT on Software Development Activity</title><link>/updates/impact-of-the-availability-of-chatgpt-on-software-development/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/impact-of-the-availability-of-chatgpt-on-software-development/</guid><description>Advancements in Artificial Intelligence, especially with ChatGPT, have greatly influenced software development. Leveraging novel data from GitHub Innovation Graph, the World Bank’s Data Lab hypothesized that ChatGPT improves the efficiency of software production.</description></item><item><title>Assessing Flood Risks in Peru</title><link>/updates/assessing-flood-risks-in-peru/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/assessing-flood-risks-in-peru/</guid><description>The Inter-American Development Bank (IDB) Water and Sanitation division leveraged data from JBA&amp;rsquo;s Global Flood Maps as supporting information to identify areas of exposure to flooding risk prior to the implementation of &amp;ldquo;Proyecto Para la Ampliación Y Mejoramiento de Los Servicios de Agua Potable Y Alcantarillado de la Ciudad de Juliaca-Puno&amp;rdquo; (in Spanish) to design and build a resilient water and sanitation infrastructure in Peru’s Puno region.</description></item><item><title>Understanding Internet Connectivity to Tackle the Digital Divide</title><link>/updates/understanding-internet-connectivity-to-tackle-the-digital-divide/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/understanding-internet-connectivity-to-tackle-the-digital-divide/</guid><description>The Internet offers great potential for contributing to more prosperous societies. For instance, it enables small businesses to overcome the challenges of entering worldwide markets.</description></item><item><title>Monitoring and Simulating Trade Disruptions through Satellite-Based Vessel Data and Big Data Analytics</title><link>/updates/monitoring-and-simulating-trade-disruptions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/monitoring-and-simulating-trade-disruptions/</guid><description>Global supply chains are increasingly vulnerable to the impacts of climate change, natural hazards and geopolitical trade tensions. The International Monetary Fund and the Environmental Change Instituteat the University of Oxford established PortWatch to help people assess the domestic and international trade impact of actual and future disruptions.</description></item><item><title>Uncovering the Digital Divide in Brazil: Data Reveals Internet Inequality Across Income Groups</title><link>/updates/uncovering-digital-divide-in-brazil/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/uncovering-digital-divide-in-brazil/</guid><description>Leveraging data from Ookla for Good™, the World Bank&amp;rsquo;s Digital Development Global Practice has analyzed the relationship between internet speed and income inequality within a sample of Brazilian cities.</description></item><item><title>How Digitalization Can Enhance Economic Resilience</title><link>/updates/how-digitalization-can-enhance-resilience/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/how-digitalization-can-enhance-resilience/</guid><description>The COVID-19 crisis has opened deep economic scars, leading to significant output losses. Can digitalization improve economic resilience to shocks such as the pandemic?</description></item><item><title>Maldives Development Update (April 2021): A Digital Dawn</title><link>/updates/maldives-development-update/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/maldives-development-update/</guid><description>Authors for the special focus topic (Part B) on digital development: Gohar Malumyan, Junko Narimatsu and Pui Shen Yoong, with guidance from Siddhartha Raja and Fernando Im.</description></item><item><title>Why We Should Accelerate the Use of Digital Technologies in Africa</title><link>/updates/africa-digital-transformation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/africa-digital-transformation/</guid><description>As Africa’s population grows, digital technologies are becoming increasingly important for the continent’s economic transformation and job creation. From computers to apps to machine learning, digital technologies offer new opportunities for people and businesses across Africa.</description></item><item><title>Reaching Digital Deserts – Extending Access to Broadband Has Never Been So Important</title><link>/updates/reaching-digital-deserts/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/reaching-digital-deserts/</guid><description>The internet is crucial for us to access information, services, job opportunities, education, and more. However, while urban communities flourish in the online world, many rural communities have been left behind when it comes to ensuring fast and reliable internet access.</description></item><item><title>For Reduced Exposure to COVID-19, the Quality of Your Internet Matters</title><link>/updates/covid19-internet-speed-impact/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/covid19-internet-speed-impact/</guid><description>During the height of the COVID-19 pandemic, governments-imposed movement restrictions to curb the spread of the disease. With access to the internet, people could work or study remotely, therefore making it easier for them to adhere to pandemic-related movement restrictions.</description></item><item><title>Digitalization and Resilience to COVID-19 Shocks: Evidence from Sub-Saharan Africa</title><link>/updates/imf-digitalization-in-sub-saharan-africa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/imf-digitalization-in-sub-saharan-africa/</guid><description>Challenge The COVID-19 pandemic has brought major disruption to economic activities and human welfare across the world. Despite the pandemic&amp;rsquo;s late arrival, Sub-Saharan African countries were faced with unprecedented challenges to contain the spread of the pandemic and mitigate the damage to the economy.</description></item><item><title>The Effect of COVID-19 Lockdown Measures on Internet Speed</title><link>/updates/covid-19-digital-divide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/covid-19-digital-divide/</guid><description>COVID-19 and the related lockdown measures to prevent the virus’ spread have highlighted how important it is for everyone to have access to reliable and resilient digital infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Estimating High-speed Broadband Coverage in Ukraine</title><link>/updates/estimating-high-speed-broadband-coverage-in-ukraine/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/estimating-high-speed-broadband-coverage-in-ukraine/</guid><description>Challenge Ukraine, Europe’s biggest country, has over 1,192 operators and providers, of which close to three quarters operate under a special preferential tax regime, allowing them not to report their coverage/subscription data to the national telecom regulatory authority.</description></item></channel></rss>