<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>COVID-19 on Development Data Partnership</title><link>/tags/covid-19/</link><description>Recent content in COVID-19 on Development Data Partnership</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 13:02:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/covid-19/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Understanding the Post COVID-19 Labor Market in Latin America and the Caribbean</title><link>/updates/covid_19_labor_markets_observatory/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 13:02:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/covid_19_labor_markets_observatory/</guid><description>Challenge The Covid-19 Labor Markets Observatory, managed by the Inter-American Development Bank Labor Markets Division, aimed to understand how COVID-19 has affected labor markets in Latin America and the Caribbean.</description></item><item><title>Facebook’s Covid-19 Trends and Impact Survey</title><link>/updates/facebook-covid-19-trends-and-impact-survey/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/facebook-covid-19-trends-and-impact-survey/</guid><description>With as many as 8 vaccines approved for use around the world the most urgent need now to control the spread of the novel coronavirus is increasing vaccination rates.</description></item><item><title>Improving Public Space and Market Design During COVID-19</title><link>/updates/improving-public-space-and-market-design-during-covid-19/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 13:02:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/improving-public-space-and-market-design-during-covid-19/</guid><description>Lima’s Central Market has always been one of the busiest and liveliest in Lima, Peru. Before the pandemic, some hundreds of people gathered there to buy and sell groceries, clothes, electronics&amp;ndash;you name it.</description></item><item><title>Mapping entrepreneurs' response to COVID-19 in Latin America and the Caribbean</title><link>/updates/mapping-entrepreneurs-response-to-covid-19-in-latin-america-and-the-caribbean/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 13:02:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/mapping-entrepreneurs-response-to-covid-19-in-latin-america-and-the-caribbean/</guid><description>Challenge: The social and economic disruption caused by Covid-19 led to numerous challenges to conduct businesses, provide essential services, and attend to the most basic well-being needs around the globe.</description></item><item><title>The Effect of COVID-19 Lockdown Measures on Internet Speed</title><link>/updates/covid-19-digital-divide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/covid-19-digital-divide/</guid><description>COVID-19 and the related lockdown measures to prevent the virus’ spread have highlighted how important it is for everyone to have access to reliable and resilient digital infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Examining the Economic Impact of COVID-19 in India through Daily Electricity Consumption and Nighttime Light Intensity</title><link>/updates/examining-the-economic-impact-of-covid-19-in-india-through-daily-electricity-consumption-and-nighttime-light-intensity-1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/examining-the-economic-impact-of-covid-19-in-india-through-daily-electricity-consumption-and-nighttime-light-intensity-1/</guid><description>Challenge: The COVID-19 pandemic has disrupted economic activity in India. When COVID-19 started to spread in India through domestic contagion, the authorities enacted a series of measures to combat the pandemic, including a strict national lockdown from March 25 to May 4 that strongly disrupted economic activity.</description></item><item><title>Examining the Economic Impact of India’s Zone Classification to contain COVID-19</title><link>/updates/examining-the-economic-impact-of-covid-19-in-india-through-daily-electricity-consumption-and-nighttime-light-intensity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/examining-the-economic-impact-of-covid-19-in-india-through-daily-electricity-consumption-and-nighttime-light-intensity/</guid><description>Challenge: The COVID-19 pandemic has disrupted economic activity in India. When COVID-19 started to spread in India through domestic contagion, the Indian authorities enacted a series of measures to combat the pandemic, including a strict national lockdown from March 25 to May 4.</description></item><item><title>Economic Anxiety and COVID-19 in Southeast Asia</title><link>/updates/economic-anxiety-and-covid-19-in-southeast-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/economic-anxiety-and-covid-19-in-southeast-asia/</guid><description>Challenge: The COVID-19 pandemic has affected the global economy through lockdowns, disrupted supply chains and uncertain economic outlooks. Swift reaction by policy makers are required to prevent a deep recession.</description></item><item><title>Tackling COVID-19 Second Wave using Facebook Mobility Data in Vietnam</title><link>/updates/tackling-covid19-second-wave-using-facebook-mobility-data-in-vietnam/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/tackling-covid19-second-wave-using-facebook-mobility-data-in-vietnam/</guid><description>Challenge: On July 24, after 99 days of zero community-transmitted COVID-19 infections, a 57 year-old man tested positive in Danang, a major city in central Vietnam with close to 1.</description></item><item><title>Addressing COVID-19 through Public-Private Data Partnerships: Where Do We Put New Testing Facilities?</title><link>/updates/covid19-and-public-private-data-partnerships/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 20:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/covid19-and-public-private-data-partnerships/</guid><description>Background
As the COVID-19 pandemic evolves, the World Bank is ramping up its response to help countries around the world. The Bank recently announced $14 billion emergency support program, for which a key pillar is to help countries strengthen their capacity to monitor and respond to the spread of the virus.</description></item></channel></rss>