<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Case Study on Development Data Partnership</title><link>/categories/case-study/</link><description>Recent content in Case Study on Development Data Partnership</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/case-study/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Examining Gender Disparities in Skills within the Energy Sector: Insights from LinkedIn Data</title><link>/updates/examining-gender-disparities-in-skills-within-the-energy-sector-insights-from-linkedin-data/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/examining-gender-disparities-in-skills-within-the-energy-sector-insights-from-linkedin-data/</guid><description>Analyzing gender differences in skills in the energy sector offers insights into disparities and facilitates better future planning. The International Energy Agency (IEA), a sister entity to the Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development, utilized LinkedIn data for the Gender and Energy Data Explorer, a platform which provides information on gender gaps in the energy sector related to employment, wages, senior management, entrepreneurship, and innovation.</description></item><item><title>Leveraging Satellite Data to Understand the Economic Implications of Sri Lanka’s Fertilizer Import Ban in 2021</title><link>/updates/leveraging-satellite-data-to-understand-the-economic-implications-of-sri-lanka-fertilizer-import-ban-in-2021/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/leveraging-satellite-data-to-understand-the-economic-implications-of-sri-lanka-fertilizer-import-ban-in-2021/</guid><description>In May 2021, Sri Lanka’s government imposed a sudden ban on imports of chemical fertilizers. The World Bank’s Trade and International Integration Unit of the Development Research Group utilized satellite data, including Planet, to quantify the changes in tea yield since the ban, as part of a study aimed at understanding how the ban affected the country’s agricultural production and trade.</description></item><item><title>Mapping Vulnerability and Mobility: Leveraging Digital Data to Inform Flood Displacement and Resilience Planning</title><link>/updates/mapping-vulnerability-and-mobility-leveraging-digital-data-to-inform-flood-displacement-and-resilience-planning/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/mapping-vulnerability-and-mobility-leveraging-digital-data-to-inform-flood-displacement-and-resilience-planning/</guid><description>The climate crisis is a growing factor influencing human mobility, especially in developing countries. The Asian Development Bank utilized JBA’s Global Flood Maps to analyze how flood exposure and patterns of displacement differ among income groups.</description></item><item><title>Bridging the Gap Between Plans and Reality: A Data-Driven Look at Urban Land Use in Amman</title><link>/updates/bridging-the-gap-between-plans-an-reality-a-data-driven-look-at-urban-lan-use-in-amman/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/bridging-the-gap-between-plans-an-reality-a-data-driven-look-at-urban-lan-use-in-amman/</guid><description>Urban landscapes are transforming rapidly, often outpacing the capabilities of traditional planning tools. In Amman, Jordan—a city shaped by swift population growth and complex migration flows—this challenge is particularly acute.</description></item><item><title>Mobile Internet Connectivity and Household Wealth in the Philippines</title><link>/updates/mobile-internet-connectivity-and-household-wealth-in-the-philippines/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/mobile-internet-connectivity-and-household-wealth-in-the-philippines/</guid><description>The rapid expansion of mobile internet has resulted in significant economic and social impacts. Therefore, it is essential to comprehend how policymakers can maximize the economic benefits of internet accessibility.</description></item><item><title>Unlocking Mapbox Data: Enhancing People’s Daily Lives through Data-Driven Urban Planning</title><link>/updates/unlocking-mapbox-data-enhancing-people-daily-lives-through-data-driven-urban-planning/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/unlocking-mapbox-data-enhancing-people-daily-lives-through-data-driven-urban-planning/</guid><description>Cities around the globe confront significant challenges in providing infrastructure, essential services, and access to public transportation. In response, many urban areas are striving to enhance their infrastructure to improve the daily lives of their citizens.</description></item><item><title>Health Planning in the Philippines</title><link>/updates/health-planning-in-the-philippines/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/health-planning-in-the-philippines/</guid><description>Access to health services is essential. However, in the Philippines, the delivery of health services is highly fragmented across different levels of administration.</description></item><item><title>Strengthening Climate Resilience of the Tajikistan Road Network</title><link>/updates/strengthening_climate_resilience_tajikistan_road_network/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/strengthening_climate_resilience_tajikistan_road_network/</guid><description>Using data from JBA&amp;rsquo;s Global Flood Maps, the transport team at the Asian Development Bank (ADB) examined flood risk and its economic impacts in Tajikistan.</description></item><item><title>Harnessing Data to Transform City Planning and Management</title><link>/updates/harnessing-data-to-transform-city-planning-and-management/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/harnessing-data-to-transform-city-planning-and-management/</guid><description>With the ongoing growth of the global population, cities are increasingly emerging as hubs of economic activity and innovation. However, if urbanization is not well-planned, it can result in a wide range of problems, such as traffic jams.</description></item><item><title>Assessing How Floods Affect Economic Growth – The Case of the Western Balkans</title><link>/updates/assessing-how-floods-affect-economic-growththe-case-of-the-western-balkans/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/assessing-how-floods-affect-economic-growththe-case-of-the-western-balkans/</guid><description>The World Bank published the Western Balkans regional Country Climate and Development Report (CCDR) that assesses natural hazard risks (linked to climate change and seismic activity) across people and places and provides specific and prioritized actions to enhance the region&amp;rsquo;s climate resilience and to stimulate economic growth.</description></item><item><title>Leveraging LinkedIn Data to Understand the Green and Digital Transformations in the Labor Market and the Future of Work</title><link>/updates/leveraging-linkedin-data-to-understand-the-green-and-digital-transformations-in-the-labor-market-and-the-future-of-work/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/leveraging-linkedin-data-to-understand-the-green-and-digital-transformations-in-the-labor-market-and-the-future-of-work/</guid><description>The economy and the labor market have evolved due to digital and green transitions. New technologies and new forms of work stemming from digitalization, climate change, and ongoing efforts to shift to a low-carbon economy have been changing jobs and skills at a rapid pace.</description></item><item><title>How to Leverage Data for Better Transport, Digital Connectivity, and Sustainable Development in the Amazon</title><link>/updates/how-to-leverage-data-for-better-transport-digital-connectivity-and-sustainable-development-in-the-amazon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/how-to-leverage-data-for-better-transport-digital-connectivity-and-sustainable-development-in-the-amazon/</guid><description>The World Bank Transport team used data from Google, Mapbox, Meta, and Ookla to identify infrastructure gaps in the Amazon areas of Brazil, Colombia and Peru.</description></item><item><title>Can private management of African protected areas improve socioeconomic and wildlife outcomes?</title><link>/updates/can-private-management-of-african-protected-areas-improve-socioeconomic-and-wildlife-outcomes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/can-private-management-of-african-protected-areas-improve-socioeconomic-and-wildlife-outcomes/</guid><description>African governments increasingly entrust the management of protected areas to private, nongovernmental organizations, with the hope that the significant resources and technical capacities of private organizations will help realize the potential of these areas.</description></item><item><title>Advancing Women’s Empowerment Through Data</title><link>/updates/advancing-women-s-empowerment-through-data/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/advancing-women-s-empowerment-through-data/</guid><description>Data plays a fundamental role in identifying the challenges women are facing and in allowing policymakers and businesses to make informed decisions that improve women’s well-being and access to economic opportunities and overall development outcomes.</description></item><item><title>Unleashing the Power of Data to Tackle Traffic Congestion and Promote Road Safety</title><link>/updates/unleashing-the-power-of-data-to-tackle-traffic-congestion-and-promote-road-safety/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/unleashing-the-power-of-data-to-tackle-traffic-congestion-and-promote-road-safety/</guid><description>As the global population is constantly increasing, building modern and sustainable cities to accommodate everyone is crucial. This is enshrined in the 2030 Agenda for Sustainable Development, in which the Sustainable Development Goal 11 aims to make cities more inclusive, safe, resilient and sustainable.</description></item><item><title>Leveraging Social Media Data to Map Road Traffic Crashes</title><link>/updates/leveraging-social-media-data-to-map-road-traffic-crashes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/leveraging-social-media-data-to-map-road-traffic-crashes/</guid><description>Challenge Road traffic crashes are among the world’s most pressing public health challenges. Crashes are the leading cause of death for those 5-29 years old and are the 8th leading cause of death considering all ages.</description></item><item><title>Impact of the Availability of ChatGPT on Software Development Activity</title><link>/updates/impact-of-the-availability-of-chatgpt-on-software-development/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/impact-of-the-availability-of-chatgpt-on-software-development/</guid><description>Advancements in Artificial Intelligence, especially with ChatGPT, have greatly influenced software development. Leveraging novel data from GitHub Innovation Graph, the World Bank’s Data Lab hypothesized that ChatGPT improves the efficiency of software production.</description></item><item><title>Analyzing the Adoption of Artificial Intelligence in Capital Market Activities</title><link>/updates/analyzing-the-adoption-of-artificial-intelligence-in-capital-market-activities/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/analyzing-the-adoption-of-artificial-intelligence-in-capital-market-activities/</guid><description>The analytical chapter (Chapter 3) of the October 2024 Global Financial Stability Report aims to assess the potential impact of Artificial Intelligence (AI) on capital markets.</description></item><item><title>Facilitating Inter-Municipal Cooperation in Lithuania to Provide Better Access to Healthcare and Long-Term Care Services to Citizens</title><link>/updates/facilitating-inter-municipal-cooperation-in-lithuania/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/facilitating-inter-municipal-cooperation-in-lithuania/</guid><description>Lithuania is experiencing rapid demographic change, with the population both aging and significantly shrinking in recent decades. This trend has put pressure on the provision of public services such as health care, especially at the municipal level, and is expected to continue in the coming years.</description></item><item><title>Assessing Flood Risks in Peru</title><link>/updates/assessing-flood-risks-in-peru/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/assessing-flood-risks-in-peru/</guid><description>The Inter-American Development Bank (IDB) Water and Sanitation division leveraged data from JBA&amp;rsquo;s Global Flood Maps as supporting information to identify areas of exposure to flooding risk prior to the implementation of &amp;ldquo;Proyecto Para la Ampliación Y Mejoramiento de Los Servicios de Agua Potable Y Alcantarillado de la Ciudad de Juliaca-Puno&amp;rdquo; (in Spanish) to design and build a resilient water and sanitation infrastructure in Peru’s Puno region.</description></item><item><title>Understanding Internet Connectivity to Tackle the Digital Divide</title><link>/updates/understanding-internet-connectivity-to-tackle-the-digital-divide/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/understanding-internet-connectivity-to-tackle-the-digital-divide/</guid><description>The Internet offers great potential for contributing to more prosperous societies. For instance, it enables small businesses to overcome the challenges of entering worldwide markets.</description></item><item><title>Understanding Socioeconomic Disparities in Mobility Behavior During the COVID-19 Pandemic in Developing Countries</title><link>/updates/understanding-socioeconomic-disparities-in-mobility-behavior-during-covid-in-developing-countries/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/understanding-socioeconomic-disparities-in-mobility-behavior-during-covid-in-developing-countries/</guid><description>The COVID-19 pandemic profoundly disrupted global mobility, but how did it affect different socioeconomic groups, particularly in developing and middle-income countries?</description></item><item><title>Nature-Based Solutions for Climate-Resilient Urban Development in Itahari, Nepal</title><link>/updates/nbs-for-climate-resilient-urban-development-in-nepal/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/nbs-for-climate-resilient-urban-development-in-nepal/</guid><description>Cities across Nepal are increasingly vulnerable to natural disasters and climate change impacts. Rapid, unplanned urbanization and the country&amp;rsquo;s unique topography make major cities particularly prone to floods, landslides, and heat stress.</description></item><item><title>Examining the Prevalence of Technology Skills in Central America and the Dominican Republic</title><link>/updates/prevalence-of-technology-skills-in-cadr/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/prevalence-of-technology-skills-in-cadr/</guid><description>Technological advancements like artificial intelligence (AI) have the potential to shape labor markets in Central America and the Dominican Republic (CADR).</description></item><item><title>Using Mobility Data for Resilient Transport Planning and Investments</title><link>/updates/using-mobility-data-for-resilient-transport-planning-and-investments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/using-mobility-data-for-resilient-transport-planning-and-investments/</guid><description>Chennai has been facing various challenges like changes in land use patterns and urban population stress, and a growing risk from events like floods and heavy rains, which all put pressure on its transport infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Examining the Impact of Social Distancing on Household-Level Economic Performances in Vietnam</title><link>/updates/social-distancing-on-household-level-economic-performances-in-vietnam/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/social-distancing-on-household-level-economic-performances-in-vietnam/</guid><description>During the COVID-19 pandemic, governments implemented social distancing measures to curb the spread of the virus. However, these measures also impacted people’s socioeconomic well-being.</description></item><item><title>Exploring the crucial role of traffic-related emissions on air pollution in Tbilisi</title><link>/updates/role-of-traffic-related-emissions-on-air-pollution-in-tbilisi/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/role-of-traffic-related-emissions-on-air-pollution-in-tbilisi/</guid><description>With financial support from Sweden, the World Bank’s Poverty and Equity Team working in the South Caucasus was seeking to understand how exposure to pollution varies within Tbilisi, Georgia across income groups and occupations to aid policy makers in developing solutions that benefit those who are most vulnerable to pollution.</description></item><item><title>Studying Service Accessibility in Towns and Villages</title><link>/updates/studying-service-accessibility-in-towns-and-villages/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/studying-service-accessibility-in-towns-and-villages/</guid><description>Settlements – cities, towns and villages – provide jobs and access to services for their own residents and other people living nearby.</description></item><item><title>Assessing the Impact of Extreme Temperatures on Sentiments through Social Media Data in Argentina</title><link>/updates/assessing-the-impact-of-extreme-temperatures-on-sentiments-through-social-media-in-argentina/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/assessing-the-impact-of-extreme-temperatures-on-sentiments-through-social-media-in-argentina/</guid><description>How do extreme weather events affect people&amp;rsquo;s sentiments? Leveraging X (formerly known as Twitter) data, the World Bank&amp;rsquo;s Regional Direction of Sustainable Development for Latin America and the Caribbean worked with researchers from Argentina universities to study how extreme temperatures impact people&amp;rsquo;s moods in Argentina.</description></item><item><title>Evaluar El Impacto De Las Temperaturas Extremas En Los Sentimientos a Través De Datos De Redes Sociales En Argentina</title><link>/updates/impacto_temperaturas_argentina_redes_sociales/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/impacto_temperaturas_argentina_redes_sociales/</guid><description>¿Cómo afectan los fenómenos meteorológicos extremos a los sentimientos de las personas? A partir de los datos de la red social X (antes conocido como Twitter), la Dirección Regional de Desarrollo Sostenible para América Latina y el Caribe del Banco Mundial trabajó con investigadores de universidades argentinas para estudiar cómo las temperaturas extremas impactan sobre el estado de ánimo de las personas en Argentina.</description></item><item><title>Cultivating Human Capital and Skills in Argentina for Sustainable Long-Term Economic Growth</title><link>/updates/cultivating-human-capital-and-skills-in-argentina/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/cultivating-human-capital-and-skills-in-argentina/</guid><description>Argentina holds immense potential to achieve sustained and inclusive economic growth. However, the country is facing structural challenges to growth, including the gradually declining quality of human capital.</description></item><item><title>Monitoring and Simulating Trade Disruptions through Satellite-Based Vessel Data and Big Data Analytics</title><link>/updates/monitoring-and-simulating-trade-disruptions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/monitoring-and-simulating-trade-disruptions/</guid><description>Global supply chains are increasingly vulnerable to the impacts of climate change, natural hazards and geopolitical trade tensions. The International Monetary Fund and the Environmental Change Instituteat the University of Oxford established PortWatch to help people assess the domestic and international trade impact of actual and future disruptions.</description></item><item><title>Uncovering the Digital Divide in Brazil: Data Reveals Internet Inequality Across Income Groups</title><link>/updates/uncovering-digital-divide-in-brazil/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/uncovering-digital-divide-in-brazil/</guid><description>Leveraging data from Ookla for Good™, the World Bank&amp;rsquo;s Digital Development Global Practice has analyzed the relationship between internet speed and income inequality within a sample of Brazilian cities.</description></item><item><title>Macroeconomic Monitoring with Google Trends</title><link>/updates/macroeconomic-monitoring-with-google-trends/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/macroeconomic-monitoring-with-google-trends/</guid><description>Challenges such as a lack of timely high-frequency data make it difficult to monitor and evaluate changing economic situations. Google&amp;rsquo;s weekly search volume index (SVI) helped the International Monetary Fund provide more timely response and assessment of economic activity especially in Labor Markets and Tourism.</description></item><item><title>Understanding people mobility in Amazonia</title><link>/updates/understanding-people-mobility-in-amazonia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/understanding-people-mobility-in-amazonia/</guid><description>Amazonia has many small and remote communities but also some big and influential urban centers. At the Inter-American Development Bank (IDB), in our efforts towards a sustainable development in Amazonia through the Amazonia Forever program, we leveraged movement data from Meta to shed light on the relationships between cities in each country within Amazonia, as well as the connection between the region&amp;rsquo;s urban areas and other parts of the countries as we understand that there is a constant movement of people and merchandise between areas.</description></item><item><title>Implications of the Green Transition for the Labor Market</title><link>/updates/implications-of-the-green-transition/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/implications-of-the-green-transition/</guid><description>The global shift towards a low-carbon economy is essential to address environmental challenges but will leave no area of economic and social life untouched.</description></item><item><title>A Greener Labor Market: Employment, Policies, and Economic Transformation</title><link>/updates/greener-labor-market/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/greener-labor-market/</guid><description>How green is the labor market? Do workers have the skills needed for greener employment? The International Monetary Fund&amp;rsquo;s Research Department utilized LinkedIn data to analyze global green employment trends.</description></item><item><title> Understanding the Impact of Digitalization During COVID-19</title><link>/updates/impact-of-digitalization-during-covid/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/impact-of-digitalization-during-covid/</guid><description>COVID-19 has disrupted almost every aspect of people&amp;rsquo;s work activities, inducing a digitalization push in the demand for certain types of skills and labor.</description></item><item><title>How Digitalization Can Enhance Economic Resilience</title><link>/updates/how-digitalization-can-enhance-resilience/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/how-digitalization-can-enhance-resilience/</guid><description>The COVID-19 crisis has opened deep economic scars, leading to significant output losses. Can digitalization improve economic resilience to shocks such as the pandemic?</description></item><item><title>Using Mobility Data to Improve Lives in Lima</title><link>/updates/mobility-data-lima/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/mobility-data-lima/</guid><description>Improving traffic flow and enhancing road safety are critical to Lima which was ranked the fourth most congested metropolitan area in the world in 2022.</description></item><item><title> Assessing Traffic Congestion and Accessibility to Jobs Using Waze for Cities and Mapbox Data</title><link>/updates/traffic-congestion-argentina/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/traffic-congestion-argentina/</guid><description>Traffic congestion and suburbanization are becoming increasingly significant factors affecting urban mobility and limiting access to jobs and opportunities in most mid-sized cities worldwide.</description></item><item><title>Assessing Digital Transformation in Firms in Latin America and the Caribbean</title><link>/updates/digital-transformation-lac/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/digital-transformation-lac/</guid><description>Are firms in Latin America and the Caribbean lagging in terms of their adoption of digital technologies? The Inter-American Development Bank&amp;rsquo;s Competitiveness, Technology, and Innovation Division leveraged LinkedIn data on the penetration of digital skills as part of an assessment on the adoption of technologies in the region.</description></item><item><title>Analyzing Digital Skills Gap in MENA Countries to Inform An Upskilling Initiative</title><link>/updates/digital-skills-gap-mena/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/digital-skills-gap-mena/</guid><description>Digital technologies are reshaping work and traditional jobs. It is essential for workers across all sectors to acquire and strengthen their digital skills to stay competitive in the job market.</description></item><item><title>Inferring COVID-19 Vaccine Attitudes from X</title><link>/updates/inferring-covid-attitudes-from-x/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/inferring-covid-attitudes-from-x/</guid><description>Social media has become a platform for the public to openly advocate and express their opinions on various issues including health.</description></item><item><title>Understanding Informal Trade Dynamics in Benin</title><link>/updates/understanding-informal-trade-dynamics-in-benin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/understanding-informal-trade-dynamics-in-benin/</guid><description>Benin&amp;rsquo;s trade performance has been improving gradually in the past decade. Notably, informal trade, smuggling and small-scale cross border trade (SSCBT) are part of the large unrecorded trade dynamics in this African country.</description></item><item><title>Understanding the Economic Impact of Vaccination</title><link>/updates/economic-impact-vaccination/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/economic-impact-vaccination/</guid><description>The World Bank East Asia and the Pacific Economic Update April 2022 analyzed challenges and opportunities facing the East Asia and the Pacific (EAP) region.</description></item><item><title>Maldives Development Update (April 2021): A Digital Dawn</title><link>/updates/maldives-development-update/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/maldives-development-update/</guid><description>Authors for the special focus topic (Part B) on digital development: Gohar Malumyan, Junko Narimatsu and Pui Shen Yoong, with guidance from Siddhartha Raja and Fernando Im.</description></item><item><title>Is El Salvador's health care system ready for telemedicine?</title><link>/updates/el-salvador-telemedicine/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/el-salvador-telemedicine/</guid><description>The World Bank&amp;rsquo;s Digital Economy for Latin America (DE4LAC) initiative leveraged data from Ookla for Good™ to analyze El Salvador&amp;rsquo;s telecommunication network to understand to what extent the national healthcare system could leverage the existing digital infrastructure and develop e-health applications.</description></item><item><title>LinkedIn Data Reveals How Labor Markets Have Been Changing in Latin America and the Caribbean Since the Pandemic</title><link>/updates/labor-markets-lac/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/labor-markets-lac/</guid><description>Despite the devastating economic impacts of the COVID-19 pandemic, labor markets in Latin America and the Caribbean (LAC) are on the verge of recovery.</description></item><item><title>Analyzing the Evolution of Telework Adoption in Latin America and the Caribbean</title><link>/updates/telework-adoption-in-lac/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/telework-adoption-in-lac/</guid><description>Due to the COVID pandemic, the use of telework increased rapidly in Latin America and the Caribbean (LAC) region, as it did globally.</description></item><item><title>How Big Data and Machine Learning Can Strengthen Road Safety</title><link>/updates/detecting-urban-clues-for-road-safety/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/detecting-urban-clues-for-road-safety/</guid><description>High-quality and reliable data is necessary to gain useful, actionable insights and enhance road safety conditions. However, collecting data on road safety through manual detection can be expensive, time-consuming, and complex.</description></item><item><title>Why We Should Accelerate the Use of Digital Technologies in Africa</title><link>/updates/africa-digital-transformation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/africa-digital-transformation/</guid><description>As Africa’s population grows, digital technologies are becoming increasingly important for the continent’s economic transformation and job creation. From computers to apps to machine learning, digital technologies offer new opportunities for people and businesses across Africa.</description></item><item><title>Reaching Digital Deserts – Extending Access to Broadband Has Never Been So Important</title><link>/updates/reaching-digital-deserts/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/reaching-digital-deserts/</guid><description>The internet is crucial for us to access information, services, job opportunities, education, and more. However, while urban communities flourish in the online world, many rural communities have been left behind when it comes to ensuring fast and reliable internet access.</description></item><item><title>The Effects of City Growth on Traffic and Urban Mobility</title><link>/updates/city-growth-on-traffic-and-urban-mobility/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/city-growth-on-traffic-and-urban-mobility/</guid><description>The Romanian city of Cluj-Napoca has been deeply affected by urban sprawl, which has strained the city’s traffic system and caused increased congestion on roadways.</description></item><item><title>Social Norms and Gender Equality in South Asia</title><link>/social-norms-and-gender-equality/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/social-norms-and-gender-equality/</guid><description>This blog highlights recent work from a larger body of research on gender equality carried out at the World Bank. The blog itself relies on Chapter 3 of this report South Asia Economic Focus Reshaping Norms: A New Way Forward.</description></item><item><title>Buenos Aires Transport Demand Planning</title><link>/updates/buenos-aires-transport-demand-planning/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/buenos-aires-transport-demand-planning/</guid><description>Challenge The COVID-19 pandemic and the lockdown measures implemented in 2020 had a significant impact on mobility in the Metropolitan Area of Buenos Aires (AMBA), adding new constrains to the travel behaviours of residents and businesses.</description></item><item><title>Where Did Everyone Go? Potential of Digital Movement Data for Natural Hazards Management</title><link>/updates/potential-of-digital-movement-data-for-natural-hazards-management/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/potential-of-digital-movement-data-for-natural-hazards-management/</guid><description>Every September 19th since the great earthquake of 1985, Mexico City conducts a major drill: people filing out of buildings in an orderly fashion.</description></item><item><title>A Data-Driven Framework to Support Bogota’s Barrios Vitales Project</title><link>/updates/framework-to-support-bogota-barrios-vitales-project/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/framework-to-support-bogota-barrios-vitales-project/</guid><description>A data-driven framework to support the design, implementation, and evaluation of a superblock model in Bogotá from a speed management perspective and inform street design alternatives in the urban space.</description></item><item><title>Communicating for Health: How Did Indians Get Informed about COVID-19 during the Pandemic?</title><link>/updates/communicating-for-health-in-india.md/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/communicating-for-health-in-india.md/</guid><description>The COVID-19 pandemic saw an unprecedented amount of scientific information disseminated: throughout 2020, 11 research articles on COVID-19 were published every hour.</description></item><item><title>Understanding Societal Responses to Policies Undertaken During Emergencies: Lessons from COVID-19’s Second Wave in Maharashtra</title><link>/updates/lessons-from-covid-19-second-wave-in-maharashtra/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/lessons-from-covid-19-second-wave-in-maharashtra/</guid><description>Maharashtra, one of the wealthiest states in India, was among the worst hit by COVID-19, registering nearly 140,000 COVID-19 deaths since the start of the pandemic.</description></item></channel></rss>