<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Case Study on Development Data Partnership</title><link>/categories/case-study/</link><description>Recent content in Case Study on Development Data Partnership</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/case-study/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Where did everyone go? Potential of digital movement data for natural hazards management</title><link>/updates/potential-of-digital-movement-data-for-natural-hazards-management/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/potential-of-digital-movement-data-for-natural-hazards-management/</guid><description>Taking the 2017 earthquake as a case study, recent work by our team at the Global Facility for Disaster Reduction and Recovery (GFDRR)/World Bank is uncovering valuable applications for this digital movement data and building open-source tools to bring these methods into the mainstream of disaster risk management.</description></item><item><title>A Data-Driven Framework to Support Bogota’s Barrios Vitales Project</title><link>/updates/barrios_vitales_bogota/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/barrios_vitales_bogota/</guid><description>A data-driven framework to support the design, implementation, and evaluation of a superblock model in Bogotá from a speed management perspective and inform street design alternatives in the urban space.</description></item><item><title>Communicating for Health: How Did Indians Get Informed about COVID-19 during the Pandemic?</title><link>/updates/communicating-for-health-indian-covid-19/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/communicating-for-health-indian-covid-19/</guid><description>The COVID-19 pandemic saw an unprecedented amount of scientific information disseminated: throughout 2020, 11 research articles on COVID-19 were published every hour.</description></item><item><title>Understanding Societal Responses to Policies Undertaken During Emergencies: Lessons from COVID-19’s Second Wave in Maharashtra</title><link>/updates/lessons-from-covid-19-second-wave-in-maharashtra/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/lessons-from-covid-19-second-wave-in-maharashtra/</guid><description>Maharashtra, one of the wealthiest states in India, was among the worst hit by COVID-19, registering nearly 140,000 COVID-19 deaths since the start of the pandemic.</description></item></channel></rss>