<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Article on Development Data Partnership</title><link>//datapartnership.org/post_type/article/</link><description>Recent content in Article on Development Data Partnership</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//datapartnership.org/post_type/article/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mapbox Releases a New Movement Dataset for Mobility Insights</title><link>//datapartnership.org/introducing-mapbox-movement-data/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//datapartnership.org/introducing-mapbox-movement-data/</guid><description>Following the Development Data Partnership launch event at the World Bank-IMF Annual Meetings, Mapbox announces a new dataset on movement data for mobility insights.
The World Bank teams have been using Mapbox data across different sectors through the Development Data Partnership.</description></item><item><title>Introducing the Data Partnership on GitHub</title><link>//datapartnership.org/updates/introducing-the-data-partnership-hub/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//datapartnership.org/updates/introducing-the-data-partnership-hub/</guid><description>After launching in 2019, when the Inter-American Development Bank and the International Monetary Fund joined the initiave, the Development Data Partnership has scaled up fast, with more than 100 projects having been brought to life supported by partnerships with more than 20 companies.</description></item><item><title>How to Find Population Movement Data for Your Country: The Mobile Location Data Inventory</title><link>//datapartnership.org/updates/find-population-movement-data-for-your-country/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//datapartnership.org/updates/find-population-movement-data-for-your-country/</guid><description>As the COVID-19 pandemic continues, so have measures to mitigate its spread. Physical distancing and movement restrictions – such as school and workplace closures, public event cancellations, stay-at-home orders, and international and domestic travel bans – vary considerably across countries.</description></item><item><title>Google, Apple, and Facebook: Understanding Mobility during Social Distancing with Private Sector Data</title><link>//datapartnership.org/updates/understanding-mobility-during-social-distancing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//datapartnership.org/updates/understanding-mobility-during-social-distancing/</guid><description>As countries around the world work to contain the spread and impact of COVID-19, the World Bank Group is moving quickly to provide fast, flexible responses to help developing countries strengthen their pandemic response and health care systems.</description></item><item><title>Why Data Partnership?</title><link>//datapartnership.org/updates/why-datacollaboratives/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//datapartnership.org/updates/why-datacollaboratives/</guid><description>Should the private sector ever share data with the public sector, even if for public good? Well, it depends.
Most of us are in agreement that when companies collect our data as a natural by-product of providing a service – like our movement data or spending patterns – the company shouldn’t sell these data to a third party for profit, especially without transparency.</description></item><item><title>On Responsible Data Use</title><link>//datapartnership.org/updates/responsible-data-use/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 21:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>//datapartnership.org/updates/responsible-data-use/</guid><description>As we develop the Data Partnership, we have a responsibility to the people impacted by our initiative &amp;ndash; to local governments and partners, and to our own organizations &amp;ndash; to think about how we are collecting, using, storing, and sharing information.</description></item></channel></rss>