<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Transport on Development Data Partnership</title><link>/tags/transport/</link><description>Recent content in Transport on Development Data Partnership</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/transport/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Visualizing Millions of Waze Traffic Alerts with Big Query, H3 and Dask</title><link>/updates/visualizing-millions-of-waze-traffic-alerts-with-google-bigquery-and-dask/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/visualizing-millions-of-waze-traffic-alerts-with-google-bigquery-and-dask/</guid><description>Waze for Cities, a Data Partner of the Development Data Partnership, connects government partners to high quality, frequent and granular traffic data extremely valuable in informing public sector, transport and urban planning as well as addressing the United Nations&amp;rsquo;s Sustainable Development Goals.</description></item><item><title>Unlocking Mobility: TapTap Maps in Cap-Haïtien</title><link>/updates/unlocking-mobility-taptap-maps-in-cap-haitien/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 13:02:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/unlocking-mobility-taptap-maps-in-cap-haitien/</guid><description>Challenge Haitian cities suffer from poor transportation services, and the lack of data from existing services limits improvement efforts. Tap Taps are the most popular motorized transportation mode employed across Haiti, yet there is not enough data on them as they are informal, private, and marginally regulated.</description></item><item><title>Optimizing Tourism Investments: Identifying Chokepoints and Underperforming Minor Roads in Sri Lanka</title><link>/updates/optimizing-tourism-investments-identifying-chokepoints-and-underperforming-minor-roads-in-sri-lanka/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/optimizing-tourism-investments-identifying-chokepoints-and-underperforming-minor-roads-in-sri-lanka/</guid><description>Challenge: Connected and maintained transportation infrastructure are critical to sustainable economic development, but most current estimation methods of road quality are labor, time, and cost intensive.</description></item><item><title>Analyzing Spatial Accessibility of Health Facilities in Indonesia and Philippines</title><link>/planning-for-equitable-access-to-health-infrastructure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/planning-for-equitable-access-to-health-infrastructure/</guid><description>Challenge: Indonesia and the Philippines are archipelagos, where geographic and administrative boundaries are similar. The collection of islands is home to different concentrations of ethnic, cultural, linguistic, and socioeconomic groups, with an imbalanced distribution of health facilities and physicians.</description></item><item><title>Tackling COVID-19 Second Wave using Facebook Mobility Data in Vietnam</title><link>/updates/tackling-covid19-second-wave-using-facebook-mobility-data-in-vietnam/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/tackling-covid19-second-wave-using-facebook-mobility-data-in-vietnam/</guid><description>Challenge: On July 24, after 99 days of zero community-transmitted COVID-19 infections, a 57 year-old man tested positive in Danang, a major city in central Vietnam with close to 1.</description></item><item><title>Google, Apple, and Facebook: Understanding Mobility during Social Distancing with Private Sector Data</title><link>/updates/mobility-during-social-distancing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/mobility-during-social-distancing/</guid><description>As countries around the world work to contain the spread and impact of COVID-19, the World Bank Group is moving quickly to provide fast, flexible responses to help developing countries strengthen their pandemic response and health care systems.</description></item><item><title>Improving Road Safety in Nairobi</title><link>/updates/improving-road-safety-in-nairobi/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 20:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/improving-road-safety-in-nairobi/</guid><description>Challenge: Kenya has one of the highest estimated crash fatality rates worldwide but is challenged to address the problem without adequate data.</description></item><item><title>Mapping Freetown Transit for Resiliency</title><link>/updates/mapping-freetown-transit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 20:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/mapping-freetown-transit/</guid><description>Challenge: The resiliency of a transport network is a critical component to the stability and prosperity of a city. Freetown, prone to flooding and landslides, struggles to maintain services throughout the year.</description></item></channel></rss>