<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>JBA on Development Data Partnership</title><link>/partner/jba/</link><description>Recent content in JBA on Development Data Partnership</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/partner/jba/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mapping Vulnerability and Mobility: Leveraging Digital Data to Inform Flood Displacement and Resilience Planning</title><link>/updates/mapping-vulnerability-and-mobility-leveraging-digital-data-to-inform-flood-displacement-and-resilience-planning/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/mapping-vulnerability-and-mobility-leveraging-digital-data-to-inform-flood-displacement-and-resilience-planning/</guid><description>The climate crisis is a growing factor influencing human mobility, especially in developing countries. The Asian Development Bank utilized JBA’s Global Flood Maps to analyze how flood exposure and patterns of displacement differ among income groups.</description></item><item><title>Strengthening Climate Resilience of the Tajikistan Road Network</title><link>/updates/strengthening_climate_resilience_tajikistan_road_network/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/strengthening_climate_resilience_tajikistan_road_network/</guid><description>Using data from JBA&amp;rsquo;s Global Flood Maps, the transport team at the Asian Development Bank (ADB) examined flood risk and its economic impacts in Tajikistan.</description></item><item><title>Assessing How Floods Affect Economic Growth – The Case of the Western Balkans</title><link>/updates/assessing-how-floods-affect-economic-growththe-case-of-the-western-balkans/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/assessing-how-floods-affect-economic-growththe-case-of-the-western-balkans/</guid><description>The World Bank published the Western Balkans regional Country Climate and Development Report (CCDR) that assesses natural hazard risks (linked to climate change and seismic activity) across people and places and provides specific and prioritized actions to enhance the region&amp;rsquo;s climate resilience and to stimulate economic growth.</description></item><item><title>Assessing Flood Risks in Peru</title><link>/updates/assessing-flood-risks-in-peru/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/assessing-flood-risks-in-peru/</guid><description>The Inter-American Development Bank (IDB) Water and Sanitation division leveraged data from JBA&amp;rsquo;s Global Flood Maps as supporting information to identify areas of exposure to flooding risk prior to the implementation of &amp;ldquo;Proyecto Para la Ampliación Y Mejoramiento de Los Servicios de Agua Potable Y Alcantarillado de la Ciudad de Juliaca-Puno&amp;rdquo; (in Spanish) to design and build a resilient water and sanitation infrastructure in Peru’s Puno region.</description></item><item><title>Nature-Based Solutions for Climate-Resilient Urban Development in Itahari, Nepal</title><link>/updates/nbs-for-climate-resilient-urban-development-in-nepal/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/nbs-for-climate-resilient-urban-development-in-nepal/</guid><description>Cities across Nepal are increasingly vulnerable to natural disasters and climate change impacts. Rapid, unplanned urbanization and the country&amp;rsquo;s unique topography make major cities particularly prone to floods, landslides, and heat stress.</description></item></channel></rss>