<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Agriculture and Food on Development Data Partnership</title><link>/tags/agriculture-and-food/</link><description>Recent content in Agriculture and Food on Development Data Partnership</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/agriculture-and-food/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Leveraging Satellite Data to Understand the Economic Implications of Sri Lanka’s Fertilizer Import Ban in 2021</title><link>/updates/leveraging-satellite-data-to-understand-the-economic-implications-of-sri-lanka-fertilizer-import-ban-in-2021/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/leveraging-satellite-data-to-understand-the-economic-implications-of-sri-lanka-fertilizer-import-ban-in-2021/</guid><description>In May 2021, Sri Lanka’s government imposed a sudden ban on imports of chemical fertilizers. The World Bank’s Trade and International Integration Unit of the Development Research Group utilized satellite data, including Planet, to quantify the changes in tea yield since the ban, as part of a study aimed at understanding how the ban affected the country’s agricultural production and trade.</description></item><item><title>2020 Inspire Challenge Finalist - The ClimaCell Locust Project</title><link>/updates/inspire-challenge-finalist-the-climacell-locust-project/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/inspire-challenge-finalist-the-climacell-locust-project/</guid><description>Ag Observatory in collaboration with the World Bank Data Lab guided and facilitated Climacell&amp;rsquo;s entry into the CGIAR Big Data Inspire Challenge 2020.</description></item><item><title>Leveraging New Data Methods to Address an Ancient Challenge: Locusts</title><link>/updates/climacell-24-hour-hackathon-to-help-address-the-locust-spread-in-africa-and-beyond/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 13:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/climacell-24-hour-hackathon-to-help-address-the-locust-spread-in-africa-and-beyond/</guid><description>Challenge: The worst locust upsurge in at least 25 years is hitting parts of Africa, the Arabian Peninsula and Western Asia, and over 40 million people who are already food insecure find their food supply and livelihoods threatened.</description></item></channel></rss>