<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Social Protection on Development Data Partnership</title><link>/tags/social-protection/</link><description>Recent content in Social Protection on Development Data Partnership</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/social-protection/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The IMF's New Climate Change Indicators Dashboard: Experimental Data for Economic and Financial Analysis</title><link>/updates/imf-climate-change-dashboard/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/imf-climate-change-dashboard/</guid><description>To develop the right measures to tackle climate change, governments need robust and comparable data. The new IMF Dashboard will help fill data gaps, so policymakers can undertake the macroeconomic and financial analysis that underpins effective policies</description></item><item><title>Mapping Entrepreneurs' Response to COVID-19 in Latin America and the Caribbean</title><link>/updates/mapping-entrepreneurs-response-to-covid-19-in-latin-america-and-the-caribbean/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 13:02:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/mapping-entrepreneurs-response-to-covid-19-in-latin-america-and-the-caribbean/</guid><description>Challenge: The social and economic disruption caused by Covid-19 led to numerous challenges to conduct businesses, provide essential services, and attend to the most basic well-being needs around the globe.</description></item><item><title>Examining the Economic Impact of COVID-19 in India through Daily Electricity Consumption and Nighttime Light Intensity</title><link>/updates/examining-the-economic-impact-of-covid-19-in-india-through-daily-electricity-consumption-and-nighttime-light-intensity-1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/examining-the-economic-impact-of-covid-19-in-india-through-daily-electricity-consumption-and-nighttime-light-intensity-1/</guid><description>Challenge: The COVID-19 pandemic has disrupted economic activity in India. When COVID-19 started to spread in India through domestic contagion, the authorities enacted a series of measures to combat the pandemic, including a strict national lockdown from March 25 to May 4 that strongly disrupted economic activity.</description></item><item><title>Examining the Economic Impact of India’s Zone Classification to contain COVID-19</title><link>/updates/examining-the-economic-impact-of-covid-19-in-india-through-daily-electricity-consumption-and-nighttime-light-intensity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/examining-the-economic-impact-of-covid-19-in-india-through-daily-electricity-consumption-and-nighttime-light-intensity/</guid><description>Challenge: The COVID-19 pandemic has disrupted economic activity in India. When COVID-19 started to spread in India through domestic contagion, the Indian authorities enacted a series of measures to combat the pandemic, including a strict national lockdown from March 25 to May 4.</description></item><item><title>Economic Anxiety and COVID-19 in Southeast Asia</title><link>/updates/economic-anxiety-and-covid-19-in-southeast-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/economic-anxiety-and-covid-19-in-southeast-asia/</guid><description>Challenge: The COVID-19 pandemic has affected the global economy through lockdowns, disrupted supply chains and uncertain economic outlooks. Swift reaction by policy makers are required to prevent a deep recession.</description></item><item><title>Assessing Social Inequality and Lockdown Policies using Mobile Location Data in Indonesia</title><link>/updates/social-inequality-and-lockdown-policies/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 13:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/social-inequality-and-lockdown-policies/</guid><description>Challenge Lockdown policies such as stay-at-home orders and non-essential business closures are central to fighting the novel coronavirus. However, policy makers are having a hard time answering key questions about their efficacy.</description></item></channel></rss>