<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Disaster Risk Management on Development Data Partnership</title><link>/tags/disaster-risk-management/</link><description>Recent content in Disaster Risk Management on Development Data Partnership</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/disaster-risk-management/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mapping Vulnerability and Mobility: Leveraging Digital Data to Inform Flood Displacement and Resilience Planning</title><link>/updates/mapping-vulnerability-and-mobility-leveraging-digital-data-to-inform-flood-displacement-and-resilience-planning/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/mapping-vulnerability-and-mobility-leveraging-digital-data-to-inform-flood-displacement-and-resilience-planning/</guid><description>The climate crisis is a growing factor influencing human mobility, especially in developing countries. The Asian Development Bank utilized JBA’s Global Flood Maps to analyze how flood exposure and patterns of displacement differ among income groups.</description></item><item><title>Assessing How Floods Affect Economic Growth – The Case of the Western Balkans</title><link>/updates/assessing-how-floods-affect-economic-growththe-case-of-the-western-balkans/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/assessing-how-floods-affect-economic-growththe-case-of-the-western-balkans/</guid><description>The World Bank published the Western Balkans regional Country Climate and Development Report (CCDR) that assesses natural hazard risks (linked to climate change and seismic activity) across people and places and provides specific and prioritized actions to enhance the region&amp;rsquo;s climate resilience and to stimulate economic growth.</description></item><item><title>Nature-Based Solutions for Climate-Resilient Urban Development in Itahari, Nepal</title><link>/updates/nbs-for-climate-resilient-urban-development-in-nepal/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/nbs-for-climate-resilient-urban-development-in-nepal/</guid><description>Cities across Nepal are increasingly vulnerable to natural disasters and climate change impacts. Rapid, unplanned urbanization and the country&amp;rsquo;s unique topography make major cities particularly prone to floods, landslides, and heat stress.</description></item><item><title>The Effects of City Growth on Traffic and Urban Mobility</title><link>/updates/city-growth-on-traffic-and-urban-mobility/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/city-growth-on-traffic-and-urban-mobility/</guid><description>The Romanian city of Cluj-Napoca has been deeply affected by urban sprawl, which has strained the city’s traffic system and caused increased congestion on roadways.</description></item><item><title>Where Did Everyone Go? Potential of Digital Movement Data for Natural Hazards Management</title><link>/updates/potential-of-digital-movement-data-for-natural-hazards-management/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/potential-of-digital-movement-data-for-natural-hazards-management/</guid><description>Every September 19th since the great earthquake of 1985, Mexico City conducts a major drill: people filing out of buildings in an orderly fashion.</description></item><item><title>Understanding Societal Responses to Policies Undertaken During Emergencies: Lessons from COVID-19’s Second Wave in Maharashtra</title><link>/updates/lessons-from-covid-19-second-wave-in-maharashtra/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/lessons-from-covid-19-second-wave-in-maharashtra/</guid><description>Maharashtra, one of the wealthiest states in India, was among the worst hit by COVID-19, registering nearly 140,000 COVID-19 deaths since the start of the pandemic.</description></item><item><title>Mapping Freetown Transit for Resiliency</title><link>/updates/mapping-freetown-transit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 20:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/mapping-freetown-transit/</guid><description>Challenge: The resiliency of a transport network is a critical component to the stability and prosperity of a city. Freetown, prone to flooding and landslides, struggles to maintain services throughout the year.</description></item></channel></rss>