<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Disaster Risk Management on Development Data Partnership</title><link>/tags/disaster-risk-management/</link><description>Recent content in Disaster Risk Management on Development Data Partnership</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/disaster-risk-management/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Effects of City Growth on Traffic and Urban Mobility</title><link>/updates/city-growth-on-traffic-and-urban-mobility/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/city-growth-on-traffic-and-urban-mobility/</guid><description>The Romanian city of Cluj-Napoca has been deeply affected by urban sprawl, which has strained the city’s traffic system and caused increased congestion on roadways.</description></item><item><title>Where Did Everyone Go? Potential of Digital Movement Data for Natural Hazards Management</title><link>/updates/potential-of-digital-movement-data-for-natural-hazards-management/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/potential-of-digital-movement-data-for-natural-hazards-management/</guid><description>Every September 19th since the great earthquake of 1985, Mexico City conducts a major drill: people filing out of buildings in an orderly fashion.</description></item><item><title>Understanding Societal Responses to Policies Undertaken During Emergencies: Lessons from COVID-19’s Second Wave in Maharashtra</title><link>/updates/lessons-from-covid-19-second-wave-in-maharashtra/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/lessons-from-covid-19-second-wave-in-maharashtra/</guid><description>Maharashtra, one of the wealthiest states in India, was among the worst hit by COVID-19, registering nearly 140,000 COVID-19 deaths since the start of the pandemic.</description></item><item><title>Mapping Freetown Transit for Resiliency</title><link>/updates/mapping-freetown-transit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 20:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/mapping-freetown-transit/</guid><description>Challenge: The resiliency of a transport network is a critical component to the stability and prosperity of a city. Freetown, prone to flooding and landslides, struggles to maintain services throughout the year.</description></item></channel></rss>