<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Development Data Partnership</title><link>/authors/kwok-kin-lee/</link><description>Recent content on Development Data Partnership</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/authors/kwok-kin-lee/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Unleashing the Power of Data to Tackle Traffic Congestion and Promote Road Safety</title><link>/updates/unleashing-the-power-of-data-to-tackle-traffic-congestion-and-promote-road-safety/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/unleashing-the-power-of-data-to-tackle-traffic-congestion-and-promote-road-safety/</guid><description>As the global population is constantly increasing, building modern and sustainable cities to accommodate everyone is crucial. This is enshrined in the 2030 Agenda for Sustainable Development, in which the Sustainable Development Goal 11 aims to make cities more inclusive, safe, resilient and sustainable.</description></item><item><title>A Year in Review: Looking back on 2024</title><link>/updates/year-in-review-2024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/year-in-review-2024/</guid><description>This has proven to be a busy yet fulfilling year for the Development Data Partnership (the Partnership). As we bid farewell to 2024, we reflect on a year marked by impactful projects and fruitful partnerships.</description></item><item><title>Understanding Internet Connectivity to Tackle the Digital Divide</title><link>/updates/understanding-internet-connectivity-to-tackle-the-digital-divide/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/understanding-internet-connectivity-to-tackle-the-digital-divide/</guid><description>The Internet offers great potential for contributing to more prosperous societies. For instance, it enables small businesses to overcome the challenges of entering worldwide markets.</description></item><item><title>Using Mobility Data for Resilient Transport Planning and Investments</title><link>/updates/using-mobility-data-for-resilient-transport-planning-and-investments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/using-mobility-data-for-resilient-transport-planning-and-investments/</guid><description>Chennai has been facing various challenges like changes in land use patterns and urban population stress, and a growing risk from events like floods and heavy rains, which all put pressure on its transport infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Partnership Day 2024: Harnessing Data and Technology and Private-Public Sector Collaboration to Tackle Development Challenges</title><link>/updates/partnership_day_recap_2024/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/partnership_day_recap_2024/</guid><description>The Development Data Partnership Day shed light on the significant roles of technology and private-public sector collaboration in helping international organizations and countries address development challenges for a more sustainable future.</description></item><item><title>Development Data Partnership 2023 Year in Review</title><link>/updates/year-in-review-2023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/year-in-review-2023/</guid><description>It has been an extraordinary year for the Development Data Partnership. Before we start the new year, we wanted to take a moment to reflect and look back on what we have accomplished in 2023.</description></item></channel></rss>