<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>COVID19 on Development Data Partnership</title><link>/tags/covid19/</link><description>Recent content in COVID19 on Development Data Partnership</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 05:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/covid19/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Effect of COVID-19 Lockdown Measures on Internet Speed</title><link>/updates/covid-19-digital-divide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/covid-19-digital-divide/</guid><description>COVID-19 and the related lockdown measures to prevent the virus’ spread have highlighted how important it is for everyone to have access to reliable and resilient digital infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Examining the Economic Impact of COVID-19 in India through Daily Electricity Consumption and Nighttime Light Intensity</title><link>/updates/examining-the-economic-impact-of-covid-19-in-india-through-daily-electricity-consumption-and-nighttime-light-intensity-1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/examining-the-economic-impact-of-covid-19-in-india-through-daily-electricity-consumption-and-nighttime-light-intensity-1/</guid><description>Challenge: The COVID-19 pandemic has disrupted economic activity in India. When COVID-19 started to spread in India through domestic contagion, the authorities enacted a series of measures to combat the pandemic, including a strict national lockdown from March 25 to May 4 that strongly disrupted economic activity.</description></item><item><title>Examining the Economic Impact of India’s Zone Classification to contain COVID-19</title><link>/updates/examining-the-economic-impact-of-covid-19-in-india-through-daily-electricity-consumption-and-nighttime-light-intensity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/examining-the-economic-impact-of-covid-19-in-india-through-daily-electricity-consumption-and-nighttime-light-intensity/</guid><description>Challenge: The COVID-19 pandemic has disrupted economic activity in India. When COVID-19 started to spread in India through domestic contagion, the Indian authorities enacted a series of measures to combat the pandemic, including a strict national lockdown from March 25 to May 4.</description></item><item><title>Tackling COVID-19 Second Wave using Facebook Mobility Data in Vietnam</title><link>/updates/tackling-covid19-second-wave-using-facebook-mobility-data-in-vietnam/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/tackling-covid19-second-wave-using-facebook-mobility-data-in-vietnam/</guid><description>Challenge: On July 24, after 99 days of zero community-transmitted COVID-19 infections, a 57 year-old man tested positive in Danang, a major city in central Vietnam with close to 1.</description></item></channel></rss>