<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Announcement on Development Data Partnership</title><link>/categories/announcement/</link><description>Recent content in Announcement on Development Data Partnership</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/announcement/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Development Data Partnership Day 2023</title><link>/updates/partnership-day-2023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/partnership-day-2023/</guid><description>Join us for the Development Data Partnership Day on Wednesday, May 10, 2023, from 9:00 a.m. to 12:30 p.m. US ET in person at the World Bank HQ in Washington, DC.</description></item><item><title>Heatwaves Data Collaborative</title><link>/heatwavescollaborative/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/heatwavescollaborative/</guid><description>The Heatwaves Data Collaborative knits together efforts by international organizations, private firms, and researchers to develop standard datasets and methodologies for identifying and mitigating the urgent socio-economic impacts of heatwaves.</description></item><item><title>Development Data Partnership Day 2022</title><link>/updates/development-data-partnership-day-2022/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/development-data-partnership-day-2022/</guid><description>This day is dedicated to addressing global climate, health, and food security challenges through public-private data science collaboration. Speakers from LinkedIn, Google, Data for Good at Meta, Spectus (formerly Cuebiq), Ookla for Good, and Mapbox will share their latest experiences on data science collaboration for public good, while leadership and colleagues from the IDB, UNDP, IMF, and the World Bank will introduce project impacts.</description></item><item><title>Mapbox Releases a New Movement Dataset for Mobility Insights</title><link>/updates/introducing-mapbox-movement-data/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/introducing-mapbox-movement-data/</guid><description>Following the Development Data Partnership launch event at the World Bank-IMF Annual Meetings, Mapbox announced a new dataset on movement data for mobility insights.</description></item><item><title>Data Partnership: Bridging the Data Gap for Public Good</title><link>/annualmeetings2020/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/annualmeetings2020/</guid><description>Download Event Program High frequency, timely, and granular information &amp;ndash; which is routinely collected by the private sector&amp;ndash;can help inform public policy and service delivery.</description></item><item><title>Introducing the Data Partnership on GitHub</title><link>/updates/introducing-the-data-partnership-hub/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/introducing-the-data-partnership-hub/</guid><description>After launching in 2019, when the Inter-American Development Bank and the International Monetary Fund joined the initiave, the Development Data Partnership has scaled up fast, with more than 100 projects having been brought to life supported by partnerships with more than 20 companies.</description></item><item><title>How to Find Population Movement Data for Your Country: The Mobile Location Data Inventory</title><link>/updates/find-population-movement-data-for-your-country/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/find-population-movement-data-for-your-country/</guid><description>As the COVID-19 pandemic continues, so have measures to mitigate its spread. Physical distancing and movement restrictions – such as school and workplace closures, public event cancellations, stay-at-home orders, and international and domestic travel bans – vary considerably across countries.</description></item><item><title>Data Partner Lightning Talks</title><link>/updates/data-day/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 21:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/data-day/</guid><description>On February 13, 2019, the Data Partnership (formerly Data Collaboratives), for the first time, brought together Partners and staff. More than 200 colleagues joined the standing-room-only event, in person and online, learning about how private data partnerships can be made to work for public good.</description></item></channel></rss>