<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Authors on Development Data Partnership</title><link>/authors/</link><description>Recent content in Authors on Development Data Partnership</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>/authors/belen-rodriguez-martinez/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/belen-rodriguez-martinez/</guid><description>Belen Rodriguez Martinez is a Digital Analyst in the World Bank’s West and Central Africa team, where she supports the design and implementation of regional and national investment projects, as well as analytical initiatives across the region.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/henric-hansson/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/henric-hansson/</guid><description>Henric Hansson is a Digital Analyst, supporting investment and operations within digital infrastructure at the World Bank’s Europe and Central Asia team.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/mykhailo-koltsov/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/mykhailo-koltsov/</guid><description>Mykhailo Koltsov is a Senior Data Scientist in the Digital Development Department at the World Bank. His main areas of specialization are cybersecurity and big data analysis for social development, especially in expanding high-speed internet access.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/samuel-chicheportiche/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/samuel-chicheportiche/</guid><description>Samuel Chicheportiche is a Digital Advisor within the World Bank’s Europe and Central Asia team, supporting digital infrastructure and policy initiatives.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/hisham-osman/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/hisham-osman/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>/authors/ko-takeuchi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/ko-takeuchi/</guid><description>Ko Takeuchi joined the World Bank in 2013 and currently works as a Senior Specialist on Urban Development and Disaster Risk Management, leading the Community of Practice in the Urban, Resilience, and Land Department on Resilient Infrastructure and Buildings.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/ana-florina-pirlea/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/ana-florina-pirlea/</guid><description>Ana Florina Pirlea is a Statistician in the World Bank’s Development Data Group, where she works on the World Development Indicators and the creation of data-driven narratives.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/divyanshi-wadhwa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/divyanshi-wadhwa/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>/authors/enrique-iglesias/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/enrique-iglesias/</guid><description>Enrique Iglesias is a Telecommunications Specialist in the Connectivity, Markets, and Finance Division at the Inter-American Development Bank. His responsibilities include supporting governments in Latin America and the Caribbean in developing broadband and digital economy agendas through technical assistance and loan operations.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/sebastien-peytrignet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/sebastien-peytrignet/</guid><description>Sébastien Peytrignet is a Project Officer with the International Telecommunications Union. With a background in Economics and Data Science, he develops software tools to help connect the unconnected using geospatial data analysis.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/walid-mathlouthi/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/walid-mathlouthi/</guid><description>Dr. Walid Mathlouthi received a PhD in Optics, Photonics and Lasers. He spent his early career at Optical Research Laboratories in France, Italy, Canada and the US with Intel Corp where he worked, among other things, on the first Raman silicon laser.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/jun-rentschler/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/jun-rentschler/</guid><description>Jun Rentschler is a Senior Economist at the World Bank, working at the intersection of climate change, urbanization, and sustainable resilient development.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/neave-oclery/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/neave-oclery/</guid><description>Neave O&amp;rsquo;Clery is Professor of Cities and Networks, and Director of Research, at the Centre for Advanced Spatial Analysis (CASA) at University College London where she leads an inter-disciplinary research group focused on data-driven models for economic development and developing cities.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/paolo-avner/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/paolo-avner/</guid><description>Paolo Avner is a Senior Economist with the World Bank and the Global Facility for Disaster Reduction and Recovery (GFDRR), where he co-leads the Disaster Risk Analytics and Resilient Infrastructure thematic areas.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/shaun-hoang/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/shaun-hoang/</guid><description>Shaun Hoang is an urban mobility researcher at the University of Zurich, and University College London (UCL). His recent projects focus on transport resilience, transport inequality and open geospatial data challenges in developing economies.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/sukankana-chakraboty/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/sukankana-chakraboty/</guid><description>Dr. Sukankana Chakraborty is a Research Fellow at the Centre for Advanced Spatial Analysis (CASA) at University College London (UCL). Her research focuses on applying AI methodologies to support evidence-based policymaking.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/kwok-kin-lee/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/kwok-kin-lee/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>/authors/adam-mehl/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/adam-mehl/</guid><description>Adam Mehl is a Brazilian economist with experience in various levels of government, both nationally and internationally, where he utilizes quantitative and qualitative research methods to inform evidence-based policymaking.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/yves-lesenfants/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/yves-lesenfants/</guid><description>Yves Lesenfants is a Belgian ecologist with 30+ years of field experience in Latin America, focusing on the Andean and Amazon regions.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/aitor-franco-arana/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/aitor-franco-arana/</guid><description>Aitor Franco Arana, MSc, is a transport specialist with experience in sustainable mobility, resilient infrastructure, and public–private partnerships in Latin America and the Caribbean.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/ximena-velandia-villamil/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/ximena-velandia-villamil/</guid><description>Ximena Velandia Villamil, MSc, is a civil engineer and transport specialist with over 8 years of experience in sustainable mobility, traffic engineering, and resilient infrastructure planning across Latin America.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/john-barreda/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/john-barreda/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>/authors/mersedeh-tariverdi/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/mersedeh-tariverdi/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>/authors/miguel-nunez-del-prado/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/miguel-nunez-del-prado/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>/authors/konstantina-kalogianni/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/konstantina-kalogianni/</guid><description>Konstantina Kalogianni, PhD, is a data analyst with over a decade of experience working with complex datasets across multiple domains. Currently based at the International Energy Agency (IEA) in Paris, she leads data initiatives on gender, employment, and innovation in the energy sector.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/devaki-ghose/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/devaki-ghose/</guid><description>Devaki Ghose works at the Research Unit of the World Bank. She is a trade economist whose work focuses on the intersections of trade with infrastructure, migration, and the environment.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/macario-ii-o-cordel/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/macario-ii-o-cordel/</guid><description>Mac Cordel is a Data Scientist at the Asian Development Bank (ADB), where he works in the Data Division of the Economic Research and Development Impact Department.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/boyeong-hong/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/boyeong-hong/</guid><description>Boyeong Hong is a Data Engineer at MK Analytics with a decade of experience in civic analytics and consulting and she has worked for the World Bank as a short-term consultant.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/hogeun-park/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/hogeun-park/</guid><description>Hogeun Park is an Urban Specialist with the Middle East and North Africa (MENA) region of the World Bank’s Urban, Resilience, and Land Practice.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/neil-lee/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/neil-lee/</guid><description>Neil Lee is an Associate Professor in Economic Geography at the LSE and Director of the MSc in Local Economic Development.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/yohan-iddawela/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/yohan-iddawela/</guid><description>Yohan is an economist and geospatial data scientist with over ten years of expertise in international development, geographical information systems (GIS), and economic policy.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/zhiwu-wei/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/zhiwu-wei/</guid><description>Zhiwu Wei is a Leverhulme Trust and Issac Newton Trust Early Career Fellow at the Department of Land Economy, University of Cambridge where he received his Ph.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/andres-chamorro/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/andres-chamorro/</guid><description>Andres is a geographer currently working for the World Bank’s Geospatial Operations Support Team. He is passionate about leveraging the unique data resources of today to tackle complex social and environmental issues.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/elco-koks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/elco-koks/</guid><description>Elco Koks is an Associate Professor at Vrije Universiteit Amsterdam, with extensive experience in infrastructure risk impacts and climate adaptation. He is supporting several national-scale transport risk &amp;amp; resilience studies for the Asian Development Bank and the World Bank.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/ian-greenwood/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/ian-greenwood/</guid><description>Dr. Ian Greenwood is a consulting engineer supporting the Asian Development Bank and the World Bank across a range of projects and policy work - predominantly in the transport sector.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/michael-anyala/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/michael-anyala/</guid><description>Dr. Michael Anyala serves as the Senior Transport Specialist (Road Asset Management) within the Emerging Areas Team at the Transport Sector Office of the Asian Development Bank’s Sectors Group.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/travis-waller/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/travis-waller/</guid><description>Travis Waller is Managing Director of Mobility Thinking Pty Ltd which engages with the Asian Development Bank on AI-driven rapid estimation of regional and national traffic network models.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/claudia-calderon/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/claudia-calderon/</guid><description>Claudia Calderon is a Partnerships Lead at the Development Data Partnership and the World Bank’s Development Economics Data Group. Claudia promotes collaboration and responsible data use among participating international organizations and companies in the Development Data Partnership.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/giuseppe-rossitti/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/giuseppe-rossitti/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>/authors/luc-marius-jacques-bonnafous/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/luc-marius-jacques-bonnafous/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>/authors/megha-mukim/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/megha-mukim/</guid><description>Megha Mukim is a senior economist at the World Bank Group, author of several flagship reports, including, most recently ‘Thriving – Making Cities Green, Resilient and Inclusive in a Changing Climate’ and ‘Competitive Cities for Jobs and Growth’.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/solene-dengler/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/solene-dengler/</guid><description>Solene Dengler has been an Operations Analyst in the World Bank’s Urban, Disaster Risk Management, Resilience and Land Global Practice since July 2017.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/ellin-ivarsson/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/ellin-ivarsson/</guid><description>Ellin Ivarsson is a Transport Specialist from the World Bank. She is a civil engineer with a Master in Transport and Business Management from Imperial College London.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/liljana-sekerinska/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/liljana-sekerinska/</guid><description>Liljana Sekerinska is a Senior Transport Specialist in the Latin America and Caribbean (LAC) region. She leads the Amazon Infrastructure Gap analytical initiative within the LAC Infrastructure Practice Group, integrating transport, energy, and digital sectors.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/arianna-legovini/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/arianna-legovini/</guid><description>Arianna Legovini is the Director of the Development Impact Evaluation (DIME) department at the World Bank. She created the DIME model to transform the way data and impact evaluation evidence is generated and channeled into policy action.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/guadalupe-bedoya/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/guadalupe-bedoya/</guid><description>Guadalupe (Lupe) Bedoya is a Senior Economist in the Development Impact Evaluation Department (DIME) at the World Bank. Her research focuses on the role of accountability mechanisms to reduce market failures and improve development outcomes such as quality of healthcare, patient safety and road safety, and multifaceted interventions to reduce poverty and improve gender equality.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/robert-marty/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/robert-marty/</guid><description>Robert Marty is a Research Analyst in the Development Impact Evaluation unit at the World Bank where his work focuses on impact evaluations of transport corridors and road safety.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/sveta-milusheva/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/sveta-milusheva/</guid><description>Sveta Milusheva is a Senior Economist in the Development Impact (DIME) department at the World Bank. She leads the ieConnect program of impact evaluations focused on transport investments and within this program leads the work on urban mobility.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/alexander-quispe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/alexander-quispe/</guid><description>Alexander Quispe works in the Data Lab at the World Bank and holds a Master&amp;rsquo;s in Quantitative Economics from the University of Munich.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/rodrigo-grijalba/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/rodrigo-grijalba/</guid><description>Rodrigo Grijalba is a specialist in data science, who has taught in the National Institute of Statistics of Peru, and the Peruvian Social and Economic Research Consortium; and has conducted research with the Artificial Intelligence Laboratory for Social Sciences in the Pontifical Catholic University of Peru.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/mohamed-diaby/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/mohamed-diaby/</guid><description>Mohamed Diaby is an economist in the Financial Supervision and Regulation division of the Monetary and Capital Market Department at the IMF.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/xiang-li-lim/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/xiang-li-lim/</guid><description>Xiang-li is a Financial Sector Expert within the Global Markets Analysis Division of the IMF’s Monetary and Capital Market Department. The division is responsible for high-frequency market surveillance and asses conjunctural market developments for the Global Financial Stability Report.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/antti-moisio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/antti-moisio/</guid><description>Mr. Antti Moisio is a Senior Economist at the OECD Centre for Entrepreneurship, SMEs, Regions and Cities. His work encompasses various topics related to decentralisation, multi-level governance, and regional development, including municipal and territorial reforms, subnational government finance, subnational government fiscal data, inter-municipal cooperation, inter-governmental grant systems, municipal mergers, and regionalisation.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/margaux-vincent/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/margaux-vincent/</guid><description>Ms. Margaux Vincent is a Policy Analyst at the Decentralisation, Public Investment and Subnational Finance Unit of the OECD&amp;rsquo;s Centre for Entrepreneurship, SMEs, Regions and Cities.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/adriana-zambrano-barreto/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/adriana-zambrano-barreto/</guid><description>Adriana Zambrano Barreto is a Disaster Risk and Climate Change consultant at the Environmental and Social Solutions Unit (ESG) of the IDB, focusing on strengthening resilience and reducing vulnerability throughout the lifecycle of infrastructure projects.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/lorena-cano/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/lorena-cano/</guid><description>Innovation Specialist at the Inter-American Development Bank (IDB), leading the Open Innovation practice and the Development Data Partnership. Former Fellow at the World Economic Forum’s Centre for the Fourth Industrial Revolution, and technical advisor for the IDB Digital Economy Initiative and Broadband Program.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/melissa-barandiaran/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/melissa-barandiaran/</guid><description>Melissa Barandiaran, of Peruvian nationality, is a Senior Environmental Specialist for the Environmental and Social Risk Unit (RMG/ESR) of the Inter-American Development Bank, currently on a work assignment at the Water and Sanitation Division.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/lorenzo-lucchini/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/lorenzo-lucchini/</guid><description>Lorenzo Lucchini is a postdoctoral research fellow at Bocconi University and a research fellow at the Center for Health Emergencies (Bruno Kessler Foundation).</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/nancy-lozano-gracia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/nancy-lozano-gracia/</guid><description>Nancy Lozano Gracia is the Lead Economist for Sustainable Development in Latin America and the Caribbean, with over 20 years of experience in economic policy and research.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/ollin-langle-chimal/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/ollin-langle-chimal/</guid><description>Ollin is a Postdoctoral Researcher at the University of California, Berkeley. He earned his PhD in Complex Systems and Data Science from the University of Vermont (UVM).</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/samuel-paul-fraiberger/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/samuel-paul-fraiberger/</guid><description>Samuel is a data scientist and program lead for DIME AI at the World Bank, where he focuses on cutting-edge research and analytical tools to scale development impact using AI and machine learning.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/abebaw-alemayehu/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/abebaw-alemayehu/</guid><description>Abebaw Alemayehu has been with the World Bank for over 25 years working in the design and implementation supervision of complex development projects in multiple countries.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/jeny-shrestha/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/jeny-shrestha/</guid><description>Jeny Shrestha is an architect and urban planner with over 10 years of experience in urban and regional planning. She works for the World Bank Group as an Urban Development Consultant.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/harry-moroz/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/harry-moroz/</guid><description>Harry Moroz is a senior economist in the Social Protection and Labor Global Practice of the Latin America and Caribbean region at the World Bank.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/mariana-viollaz/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/mariana-viollaz/</guid><description>Mariana Viollaz completed her Ph.D. in Economics from the Universidad Nacional de La Plata (UNLP), Argentina. She is a Senior Researcher at the Center for Distributive, Labor and Social Studies (CEDLAS) at UNLP which specializes in the development of empirical evidence based on micro-data from household surveys of Latin American countries.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/gerald-ollivier/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/gerald-ollivier/</guid><description>Gerald Ollivier is a Lead Transport Specialist for the World Bank in India. He focuses on developing solutions to enhance electric mobility and urban mobility, achieve sustainable economic integration through multimodal transport, and achieve safer transport to better serve the needs of India.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/satish-ukkusuri/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/satish-ukkusuri/</guid><description>Dr. Satish V. Ukkusuri is a Professor in the Lyles School of Civil Engineering at Purdue University since July 2014 where he teaches courses in transportation systems and freight and logistics planning.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/daisuke-fukuzawa/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/daisuke-fukuzawa/</guid><description>Daisuke Fukuzawa is an Economist at the East Asia and Pacific Chief Economist Office, where he monitors and analyzes macro-economic conditions of the EAP region and co-authors East Asia and Pacific Economic Update reports.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/dao-le-van/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/dao-le-van/</guid><description>Dao Le-Van is a lecturer at Vietnam National University Hanoi&amp;rsquo;s International School. He works for the World Bank Group as a data consultant.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/duong-trung-le/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/duong-trung-le/</guid><description>Duong Trung Le is an Economist in the Office of the Chief Economist for East Asia and the Pacific at the World Bank.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/alan-fuchs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/alan-fuchs/</guid><description>Alan Fuchs is a Lead Economist in the Poverty and Equity Global Practice of the World Bank. He has led operations and analytical work on fiscal incidence, social inclusion, risk management and gender in Latin America and the Caribbean, Europe and Central Asia and in the Middle East and North Africa region.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/natsuko-nozaki/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/natsuko-nozaki/</guid><description>Natsuko Kiso Nozaki is an Economist in the Europe and Central Asia Poverty and Equity Global Practice at the World Bank.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/patrick-behrer/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/patrick-behrer/</guid><description>Patrick Behrer is an Economist in the Sustainability and Infrastructure team of the World Bank&amp;rsquo;s Development Research Group. Behrer&amp;rsquo;s work focuses on the economics of air pollution, climate change, and climate adaptation.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/sandra-baquie/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/sandra-baquie/</guid><description>Sandra Baquie is an Economist (Young Professional) at the World Bank, specializing in development, environment, climate, and health economics. Her research combines economics and natural sciences to study human-environment interactions, from antibiotic resistance to resilience to natural disasters to forest degradation, to inform policymaking.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/xinming-du/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/xinming-du/</guid><description>Xinming Du is an environmental economist and an assistant professor at the National University of Singapore Department of Economics. Her ongoing research covers three topics: 1) how trade affects pollution and natural resource depletion; 2) the impacts and adaptation to emerging pollution sources; 3) methane leakage and greenwashing activities of fossil fuel companies.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/alison-weingarden/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/alison-weingarden/</guid><description>Alison Weingarden is an economist and project manager in the OECD&amp;rsquo;s Centre for Entrepreneurship, SMEs, Regions and Cities (CFE). She has led quantitative, policy-focused projects on the geography of economic development and demographic change across the rural-urban continuum.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/carsten-dolle/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/carsten-dolle/</guid><description>Carsten Dolle is a statistician at the OECD in Paris. He joined the organisation in 2022 and supported the Centre for Entrepreneurship, SMEs, Regions and cities before joining the Directorate for Education and Skills in 2024.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/claire-hoffmann/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/claire-hoffmann/</guid><description>Claire Hoffmann is a statistician at the OECD&amp;rsquo;s Centre for Entrepreneurship, SMEs, Regions and Cities (CFE). She specializes in geospatial analysis, with recent work focusing on accessibility to services indicators.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/nikos-patias/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/nikos-patias/</guid><description>Nikos Patias is a Data Analyst at ABN AMRO. Before joining ABN AMRO, Nikos worked as a Policy Analyst at the OECD in Paris.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/jose-daniel-aromi/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/jose-daniel-aromi/</guid><description>Daniel Aromi hold a Ph.D. in Economics from University of Maryland. He is presently a researcher at the University of Buenos Aires and the Catholic University of Argentina.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/julie-rozenberg/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/julie-rozenberg/</guid><description>Julie Rozenberg has a rich educational background with a PhD in Economics from Ecole des Hautes Etudes en Sciences Sociales (France) and is now a Senior Economist at the World Bank Group&amp;rsquo;s SCADR unit.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/mariana-conte-grand/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/mariana-conte-grand/</guid><description>Mariana Conte Grand holds a Ph.D. in Economics from UCLA, serves as a Senior Economist in Sustainable Development at the World Bank, and teaches at Universidad del CEMA.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/mariano-rabassa/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/mariano-rabassa/</guid><description>Mariano Rabassa specializes in the design and evaluation of environmental policies. He holds a Ph.D. In Agricultural and Resource Economics from the University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/daniel-reyes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/daniel-reyes/</guid><description>Daniel Reyes is the World Bank Senior Country Economist for Argentina. He has more than 10 years of research and policy experience, working on issues macroeconomics, international trade, foreign direct investment, and globalization.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/sonia-araujo/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/sonia-araujo/</guid><description>Sonia Araujo is a senior economist at The World Bank Economic Policy Global Practice. She has worked on economic analysis and policy advice in multilateral institutions for nearly 20 years, covering global, regional and country specific themes.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/alessandra-sozzi/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/alessandra-sozzi/</guid><description>Alessandra Sozzi is responsible for developing the PortWatch online platform, visuals and the backend data production and automation flow. She is a Data Scientist in the IMF&amp;rsquo;s Statistics Department.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/jasper-verschuur/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/jasper-verschuur/</guid><description>Jasper Verschuur is an assistant professor in engineering systems and climate security at Delft University of Technology in the Netherlands. Jasper&amp;rsquo;s main research interests encompass quantifying the systemic risks that climate and non-climatic shocks pose to infrastructure systems and the essential services they provide to society.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/mario-saraiva/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/mario-saraiva/</guid><description>Mario Saraiva is a data scientist and development practitioner with extensive experience collaborating with global organizations. Passionate about evidence-based policy, he currently serves as a Data Management Officer at the International Monetary Fund&amp;rsquo;s Statistics Department in Washington, DC.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/matt-mcketty/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/matt-mcketty/</guid><description>Matt McKetty is a 5th year doctoral student in Applied Economics at the University of Wisconsin – Madison. Matt&amp;rsquo;s primary areas of research interest are development, trade, and structural change, with a particular focus on the Caribbean and Western Africa.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/parisa-kamali/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/parisa-kamali/</guid><description>Parisa Kamali is responsible for the content and design of the email notification system of the PortWatch platform. She is an Economist in the External Policy Division of the Strategy Policy and Review Department of the IMF.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/robin-koepke/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/robin-koepke/</guid><description>Robin Koepke plays a leading role in developing the strategy and managing the implementation of PortWatch, with a particular focus on macroeconomic applications, stakeholder management, and external communications.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/serkan-arslanalp/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/serkan-arslanalp/</guid><description>Serkan Arslanalp is an Advisor in the Office of the Managing Director. He has worked in several departments of the Fund on a wide range of countries and policy areas.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/niccolo-comini/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/niccolo-comini/</guid><description>Niccolò Comini is a Digital Devleopment Specialist with the Digital Development Global Practice at the World Bank Group. He focuses on competition and regulatory issues in the ICT and digital industries in emerging countries.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/nicola-perra/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/nicola-perra/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>/authors/nicolo-gozzi/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/nicolo-gozzi/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>/authors/lamya-kejji/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/lamya-kejji/</guid><description>Lamya Keiji, Data Analytics Officer, Data Governance and Services Division, IMF</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/roberto-prato/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/roberto-prato/</guid><description>Roberto Prato Ochoa is a Venezuelan geographer with vast experience in Geographic Information System (GIS) techniques, geographical data management and visualization, regional analysis and planning, and cartography.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/victor-osorio/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/victor-osorio/</guid><description>Victor Osorio is a Peruvian IT engineer with a passion for data analysis with 15+ years of experience in design and development of digital solutions for different sectors like health, development, telecommunications and others.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/cagatay-bircan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/cagatay-bircan/</guid><description>Çağatay Bircan is a Lead Research Economist at the EBRD and Industrial Professor at the Institute for Finance and Technology at University College London (UCL).</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/lucas-kitzmuller/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/lucas-kitzmuller/</guid><description>Lucas Kitzmüller is an Associate Economist at the Office of the Chief Economist. He applies machine learning methods in the context of economics research, works on microeconometric impact evaluations, and contributes to policy publications such as the Transition Report.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/niharika-satish/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/niharika-satish/</guid><description>Niharika Satish is a Research Analyst at the EBRD Office of the Chief Economist.
Her research is centred on environmental and development economics in LMICs, leveraging spatial and big data in combination with traditional methods.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/sehar-noor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/sehar-noor/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>/authors/diaa-noureldin/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/diaa-noureldin/</guid><description>Diaa Noureldin is an economist in the World Economic Studies Division of the IMF�s Research Department. He contributes to the chapters of the World Economic Outlook report.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/ippei-shibata/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/ippei-shibata/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>/authors/john-bluedorn/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/john-bluedorn/</guid><description>John Bluedorn is a Deputy Division Chief in the Regional Analytics and Strategy Division of the Middle East and Central Asia Department.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/jorge-alvarez/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/jorge-alvarez/</guid><description>Jorge Alvarez is an economist in the World Economic Studies division of the IMF&amp;rsquo;s Research Department. Prior to this position, he worked in the Development Macroeconomics division and as an economist covering Canada, Mexico and Colombia at the Western Hemisphere Department</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/marina-mendes-tavares/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/marina-mendes-tavares/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>/authors/niels-jakob-hansen/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/niels-jakob-hansen/</guid><description>Niels-Jakob H. Hansen is an economist in the World Economic Studies Division of the IMF�s Research Department, where he contributes to chapters of the World Economic Outlook.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/andrea-medici/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/andrea-medici/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>/authors/carlo-pizzinelli/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/carlo-pizzinelli/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>/authors/florence-jaumotte/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/florence-jaumotte/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>/authors/jiaming-soh/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/jiaming-soh/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>/authors/longji-li/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/longji-li/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>/authors/myrto-oikonomou/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/myrto-oikonomou/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>/authors/alexander-copestake/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/alexander-copestake/</guid><description>Alexander Copestake is an Economist in the Research Department at the International Monetary Fund. His research focuses on the relationships between technology, finance, trade and development.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/davide-furceri/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/davide-furceri/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>/authors/julia-estefania-flores/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/julia-estefania-flores/</guid><description>Julia Estefania Flores is a research analyst at the Asia and Pacific Department of the International Monetary Fund (IMF). She previously worked as a research officer in the Research Department of the IMF.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/aiga-stokenberga/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/aiga-stokenberga/</guid><description>Aiga Stokenberga is an economist in the Transport Global Practice, where she leads economic and spatial analyses that inform urban transport and regional transport corridor planning strategies in Sub-Saharan Africa and South Asia.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/felipe-targa/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/felipe-targa/</guid><description>Felipe Targa is a Senior Urban Transport Specialist working at the World Bank. Former Colombia’s Deputy Transport Minister, university-based CityLab Director, and 20 years of experience in the public sector, multilateral development institutions, and research from academia.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/alejandro-sicra/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/alejandro-sicra/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>/authors/javier-morales-sarriera/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/javier-morales-sarriera/</guid><description>Javier Morales Sarriera is an Economist in the World Bank’s Transport &amp;amp; ICT Global Practice. Javier is working on the implementation and coordination of transport impact evaluation in the World Bank.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/maria-sol-tadeo/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/maria-sol-tadeo/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>/authors/alison-cathles/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/alison-cathles/</guid><description>Alison Cathles is a Senior Specialist in the Competitiveness, Technology, and Innovation Division (CTI) at the Inter-American Development Bank (IDB). She is also an affiliated researcher at UNU-MERIT.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/claudia-suaznabar/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/claudia-suaznabar/</guid><description>Claudia Suaznabar is the Operations Advisor for the Vice President of Sectors at the Inter-American Development Bank (IDB). She has worked in the Bank for 20 over years and her areas of expertise include innovation, competitiveness, digital transformation and business development.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/fernando-vargas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/fernando-vargas/</guid><description>Fernando Vargas is a Senior Specialist in the Competitiveness, Technology, and Innovation Division (CTI) at the Inter-American Development Bank (IDB). He has extensive experience advising national agencies and multilateral organizations in the design of science and innovation policies.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/angela-elzir-assy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/angela-elzir-assy/</guid><description>Angela Elzir is a Labor Market Specialist at the World Bank Lebanon office, part of the Jobs Group global department. She joined the World Bank in 2010 as a Research Analyst based in the Lebanon Office, and in 2015, she joined the Jobs Group as a Junior Professional Associate based in Washington D.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/fadi-daouk/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/fadi-daouk/</guid><description>Fadi Daouk</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/sabine-habibian/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/sabine-habibian/</guid><description>Sabine Habibian is an EdTech consultant at the World Bank where she supports digital and technology projects in the Mashreq region, aiming to improve the future for learners.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/roy-van-der-weide/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/roy-van-der-weide/</guid><description>Roy van der Weide is a Senior Economist in the Poverty and Inequality Research team in the Development Research Group of the World Bank.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/jakob-engel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/jakob-engel/</guid><description>Jakob Engel is a senior economist in the Macroeconomics, Trade, and Investment Global Practice at the World Bank, based in Malawi.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/mathilde-lebrand/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/mathilde-lebrand/</guid><description>Mathilde Lebrand is an Economist in the World Bank�s Transport Global Practice. Currently she is working on the Belt and Road Initiative, economic corridor development, and connectivity.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/nathalie-picarelli/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/nathalie-picarelli/</guid><description>Nathalie Picarelli is the World Bank Senior Economist covering Cote d�Ivoire and Benin in the Macroeconomics, Trade &amp;amp; Investment (MTI) Global Practice.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/xun-yan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/xun-yan/</guid><description>Xun Yan is a World Bank economist who has worked for the Africa Chief Economist Office, the Governance GP, DECRG and MTI.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/aaditya-mattoo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/aaditya-mattoo/</guid><description>Aaditya Mattoo</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/duong-le/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/duong-le/</guid><description>Duong Le</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/ergys-islamaj/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/ergys-islamaj/</guid><description>Ergys Islamaj</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/fernando-im/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/fernando-im/</guid><description>Fernando Im</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/gohar-malumyan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/gohar-malumyan/</guid><description>Gohar Malumyan</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/junko-narimatsu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/junko-narimatsu/</guid><description>Junko Narimatsu</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/pui-shen-yoong/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/pui-shen-yoong/</guid><description>Pui Shen Yoong</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/siddhartha-raja/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/siddhartha-raja/</guid><description>Siddhartha Raja</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/eric-torres/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/eric-torres/</guid><description>Eric Torres, Consultant at the Labor Markers Division at Inter-American Development Bank.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/mauricio-mondragon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/mauricio-mondragon/</guid><description>Mauricio Mondragón, Consultant at the Labor Markers Division at Inter-American Development Bank in Mexico.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/oliver-azuara/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/oliver-azuara/</guid><description>Oliver Azuara, Senior Economist at Inter-American Development Bank.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/fabiola-saavedra-caballero/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/fabiola-saavedra-caballero/</guid><description>Fabiola Saavedra Caballero currently works as consultant in the Labor Markets and Social Security Division at the Inter-American Development Bank (IDB) where she is actively involved in projects and research focused on the design, implementation, and evaluation of initiatives aimed at fostering skills development.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/graciana-rucci/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/graciana-rucci/</guid><description>Graciana Rucci is a Lead Specialist in the Labor Markets and Social Security Division at the IDB, an institution she joined in 2005 as a junior professional.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/maria-fernanda-prada/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/maria-fernanda-prada/</guid><description>María Fernanda Prada is an economist who has been working in the Education Division of the Inter-American Development Bank (IDB) since May 2016.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/africa-gender-innovation-lab/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/africa-gender-innovation-lab/</guid><description>The World Bank Africa Gender Innovation Lab</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/east-asia-and-pacific-gender-innovation-lab/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/east-asia-and-pacific-gender-innovation-lab/</guid><description>The World Bank East Asia and Pacific Gender Innovation Lab</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/latin-america-and-the-caribbean-gender-innovation-lab/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/latin-america-and-the-caribbean-gender-innovation-lab/</guid><description>The World Bank Latin America and the Caribbean Gender Innovation Lab</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/agustina-suaya/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/agustina-suaya/</guid><description>Agustina Suaya is a consultant in the IDB&amp;rsquo;s Gender and Diversity Division, collaborating in conducting research and impact evaluations. She is a political scientist from the University of Buenos Aires (Argentina), and has a master&amp;rsquo;s degree in Public Policy from The George Washington University, USA and in Public Administration from the University of San Andrés, Argentina.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/karen-martinez/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/karen-martinez/</guid><description>Karen Martínez is a consultant in the Gender and Diversity Division at the Inter-American Development Bank (IDB). She holds a bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in economics from the Catholic University of Bolivia and a master&amp;rsquo;s degree in Economic Sciences with a specialization in econometrics from the University of Geneva.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/monserrat-bustelo/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/monserrat-bustelo/</guid><description>Monserrat Bustelo is a Senior Specialist in the Gender and Diversity Division of the Inter-American Development Bank (IDB). Since joining the Bank in 2011, Monserrat has led research projects in the area of women&amp;rsquo;s economic empowerment, related to the provision of integrated services, active parenting, transmission of intergenerational violence, female participation at work and the future of work (among others).</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/sofia-gonzalez-prieto/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/sofia-gonzalez-prieto/</guid><description>Sofia Gonzalez Prieto is a Senior Program Specialist at PACT&amp;rsquo;s Latin America and Caribbean department. She coordinates and supports several development projects in countries of the LAC region.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/luis-jan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/luis-jan/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>/authors/sarah-antos/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/sarah-antos/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>/authors/clara-stinshoff/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/clara-stinshoff/</guid><description>Clara Stinshoff is a Digital Development Specialist at the World Bank’s Digital Development Global Knowledge and Expertise Unit. She focuses her analytical work on broadband connectivity, access, and use, as well as the ICT industry and digital jobs.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/tania-begazo/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/tania-begazo/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>/authors/kathy-macdonald/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/kathy-macdonald/</guid><description>Katherine Macdonald is Senior Director of Ookla for Good at Ookla, the company behind Speedtest® and Downdetector®. She developed and leads the Ookla for Good program in support of Ookla&amp;rsquo;s mission to help make the internet better, faster, and more accessible for everyone.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/maria-paula-caldas/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/maria-paula-caldas/</guid><description>Maria Paula Caldas is a Junior Policy Analyst at the Economic Analysis, Data and Statistics Division of the Centre for Entrepreneurship, SMEs, Regions and Cities (CFE) where she supports the CFE Smart Data Strategy to develop new metrics and innovative digital tools to address emerging policy issues through timely and geographically granular empirical evidence.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/michelle-marshalian/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/michelle-marshalian/</guid><description>Michelle Marshalian, Economist &amp;amp; Project Manager, OECD</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/cal-poly/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/cal-poly/</guid><description>The Cal Poly Digital Transformation Hub (DxHub) is a strategic relationship with Amazon Web Services (AWS) and is the world’s first cloud innovation center supported by AWS on a University campus.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/gabriel-vicente/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/gabriel-vicente/</guid><description> Gabriel Stefanini Vicente, Data Scientist, Development Data Partnership</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/holly-krambeck/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/holly-krambeck/</guid><description>Holly Krambeck is a Program Manager in the World Bank’s Development Economics Data Group. She founded the Development Data Partnership, a partnership between international organizations and companies, created to facilitate the responsible use of third-party data in international development.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/ana-maria-munoz-boudet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/ana-maria-munoz-boudet/</guid><description>Ana Maria Munoz Boudet is a senior social scientist in the World Bank’s Poverty and Equity Global Practice with the Mind, Behavior, and Development Unit (eMBeD).</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/anaise-williams/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/anaise-williams/</guid><description>Anaise Williams is a consultant at the South Asia Gender Innovation Lab and a PhD Candidate at the Johns Hopkins Bloomberg School of Public Health.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/jessy-amarachi-ezebuihe/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/jessy-amarachi-ezebuihe/</guid><description>Jessy Amarachi is a consultant at the Office of the Chief Economist, South Asia Region at the World Bank. She has a master&amp;rsquo;s degree in Development Economics from The University of Göttingen.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/maurizio-bussolo/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/maurizio-bussolo/</guid><description>Maurizio Bussolo, lead economist in the Chief Economist Office for South Asia, has been working on quantitative analyses of economic policy and development with research interests spanning both micro and macroeconomic topics.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/nele-charlotte-a-warrinnier/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/nele-charlotte-a-warrinnier/</guid><description>Nele is currently working as an Economist for the World Bank&amp;rsquo;s Office of the Chief Economist, South Asia Region. They are also a senior research fellow at the LICOS Centre for Institutions and Economic Performance at KU Leuven.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/s-anukriti/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/s-anukriti/</guid><description>S Anukriti is an Economist in the Development Research Group (Human Development Team) of the World Bank. She is an applied micro-economist, with interests in the fields of development economics, economics of gender and the family, and political economy.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/tasmia-rahman/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/tasmia-rahman/</guid><description>Tasmia Rahman is an Economist at the World Bank’s Mind, Behavior &amp;amp; Development Unit (eMBeD), within the Poverty and Equity Global Practice.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/javier-bastidas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/javier-bastidas/</guid><description>Javier Rodrigo Pena Bastidas is a consultant with the Transport unit at the World Bank.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/nicholas-jones/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/nicholas-jones/</guid><description>Nicholas Jones is a Data Scientist based at GFDRR’s Tokyo Disaster Risk Management Hub. Since joining the World Bank in 2011, he has been stationed at the Brussels, New York and Washington DC offices, and has contributed to technical assistance and lending operations for disaster risk management in Caribbean, Pacific and African regions.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/takahiro-yabe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/takahiro-yabe/</guid><description>Takahiro ‘Taka’ Yabe is a Postdoctoral Associate at the MIT Institute for Data, Systems, and Society (IDSS) and Media Lab working with Alex ‘Sandy’ Pentland and Esteban Moro.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/david-uniman/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/david-uniman/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>/authors/javier-pena/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/javier-pena/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>/authors/sofia-imad/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/sofia-imad/</guid><description>Sofia is a Junior Fellow at Artha Global, where she works on public health. She is also a founding member of the Women’s Indian Chamber of Commerce and Industry India-EU Business Council and on the editorial board of Public Health Open Access.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/harsh-pachisia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/harsh-pachisia/</guid><description>Harsh Vardhan Pachisia is Development Data Partnership Data Fellow. He is heading for an MSc in Computational Analysis and Public Policy (MS-CAPP) at the University of Chicago in Fall 2022.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/eugenia-valdez-tamayo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 13:02:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/eugenia-valdez-tamayo/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>/authors/pedro-gagliardi/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 13:02:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/pedro-gagliardi/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>/authors/ruifan-shi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/ruifan-shi/</guid><description>Ruifan Shi, IMF</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/stefani-soto/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/stefani-soto/</guid><description>Stefani Darinka Guevara Soto, DECAT, World Bank</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/ludovic-cartigny/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 13:02:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/ludovic-cartigny/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>/authors/xavier-espinet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 13:02:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/xavier-espinet/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>/authors/antonio-vazquez/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 13:02:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/antonio-vazquez/</guid><description>Antonio Vazquez Brust, Consultant, Data Analysis Consultant, IDB</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/patricio-zambrano/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 13:02:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/patricio-zambrano/</guid><description>Patricio Xavier Zambrano-Barragan, Housing and Urban Development Senior Specialist, IDB</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/cristina-nolasco/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 13:02:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/cristina-nolasco/</guid><description>Cristina Nolasco, Innovation &amp;amp; Outreach Consultant, IDB Lab</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/julien-collaer/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 13:02:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/julien-collaer/</guid><description>Julien Collaer, Data Scientist, IDB Lab</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/robert-beyer/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/robert-beyer/</guid><description>Robert C. M. Beyer, Senior Economist, World Bank</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/johanna-belanger/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/johanna-belanger/</guid><description>Johanna Belanger, Consultant, World Bank</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/walker-kosmidou-bradley/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/walker-kosmidou-bradley/</guid><description>Walker Kosmidou-Bradley is a Geographer in the World Bank’s Poverty and Inequality Global Practice. He covers issues related to poverty, inequality, and displacement in Afghanistan, and remote sensing worldwide.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/laura-ralston/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/laura-ralston/</guid><description>Laura Ralston, Senior Economist, World Bank</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/maksim-pecherskiy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/maksim-pecherskiy/</guid><description>Maksim Pecherskiy, Data Engineer (Development Data Partnership), World Bank</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/natalija-garcia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/natalija-garcia/</guid><description>Ms. Natalija Gelvanovska-Garcia has joined the Bank in 2012 as Senior ICT Policy Specialist and a secondee from the Communications Regulatory Authority of the Republic of Lithuania (RRT).</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/dieter-wang/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/dieter-wang/</guid><description>Dieter Wang, Consultant, World Bank</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/rajee-kanagavel/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/rajee-kanagavel/</guid><description>Rajee Kanagavel, Development Data Partnership</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/afeefah-syed/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/afeefah-syed/</guid><description>Afeefah Khazi-Syed, Consultant, GGSCE, World Bank</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/jacques-morisset/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/jacques-morisset/</guid><description>Jacques Morisset is the World Bank Lead Economist and Program Leader for Vietnam.
After receiving his PhD in economics from the University of Geneva, he has held various positions at the World Bank and IFC, while collaborating with the World Economic Forum.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/kai-kaiser/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/kai-kaiser/</guid><description>Kai Kaiser has been Senior Economist with the World Bank in Hanoi, Vietnam since early 2016, where his engagement has focused primarily on issues of public finance and public sector governance reform.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/maham-khan/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/maham-khan/</guid><description>Maham Faisal Khan is a Data Scientist at the Global Facility for Disaster Relief and Recovery (GFDRR) and the Vietnam COVID-19 Big Data Observatory (https://covid-19observatory.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/bruno-nuno/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/bruno-nuno/</guid><description>Bruno Sanchez-Andrade Nuno _Lead Data Science Advisor, Development Data Partnership</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/omari-sefu/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 21:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/omari-sefu/</guid><description>Omari Sefu, Associate Research Manager, Facebook</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/sreelakshmi-papineni/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 21:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/sreelakshmi-papineni/</guid><description>Sreelakshmi Papineni is an economist working at the Gender Innovation Lab, within the World Bank’s Africa Chief Economist Office. Her current research focuses on identifying and addressing gender-based constraints through the analysis of development project impacts primarily for entrepreneurship, social protection and agriculture projects.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/fatima-arroyo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 20:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/fatima-arroyo/</guid><description>Fatima Arroyo-Arroyo works in the Transport Global Practice, supporting the transportation agenda in Africa. Fatima is an enthusiast of integrating multidisciplinary dimensions in transport projects, such as fragility considerations, climate adaptation and technology.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/alejandro-sicra/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/alejandro-sicra/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>/authors/ca%C4%9Fatay-bircan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/ca%C4%9Fatay-bircan/</guid><description>Çağatay Bircan is a Lead Research Economist at the EBRD and Industrial Professor at the Institute for Finance and Technology at University College London (UCL).</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/ergys_islamaj/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/ergys_islamaj/</guid><description>Ergys Islamaj</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/eric-dunand/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/eric-dunand/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>/authors/fatimah-alotaibi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/fatimah-alotaibi/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>/authors/lucas-kitzm%C3%BCller/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/lucas-kitzm%C3%BCller/</guid><description>Lucas Kitzmüller is an Associate Economist at the Office of the Chief Economist. He applies machine learning methods in the context of economics research, works on microeconometric impact evaluations, and contributes to policy publications such as the Transition Report.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/mar%C3%ADa-fernanda-prada/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/mar%C3%ADa-fernanda-prada/</guid><description>María Fernanda Prada is an economist who has been working in the Education Division of the Inter-American Development Bank (IDB) since May 2016.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/mauricio-mondrag%C3%B3n/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/mauricio-mondrag%C3%B3n/</guid><description>Mauricio Mondragón, Consultant at the Labor Markers Division at Inter-American Development Bank.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/michelle-marshalian/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/michelle-marshalian/</guid><description>Michelle Marshalian is an Economist at the Regional Development and Multi-level Governance division of the Centre for Entrepreneurship, SMEs, Regions and Cities (CFE) where she manages the OECD project on Enhancing Innovation in Rural Regions.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/nancy-lozano-gracia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/nancy-lozano-gracia/</guid><description>Nancy Lozano Gracia is the Lead Economist for Sustainable Development in Latin America and the Caribbean, with over 20 years of experience in economic policy and research.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/nele-warrinnier/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/nele-warrinnier/</guid><description>Nele is currently working as an Economist for the World Bank&amp;rsquo;s Office of the Chief Economist, South Asia Region. They are also a senior research fellow at the LICOS Centre for Institutions and Economic Performance at KU Leuven.</description></item></channel></rss>