<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Jobs and Development on Development Data Partnership</title><link>/tags/jobs-and-development/</link><description>Recent content in Jobs and Development on Development Data Partnership</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 13:02:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/jobs-and-development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Understanding the Post COVID-19 Labor Market in Latin America and the Caribbean</title><link>/updates/covid_19_labor_markets_observatory/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 13:02:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/covid_19_labor_markets_observatory/</guid><description>Challenge The Covid-19 Labor Markets Observatory, managed by the Inter-American Development Bank Labor Markets Division, aimed to understand how COVID-19 has affected labor markets in Latin America and the Caribbean.</description></item><item><title>Mapping Entrepreneurs' Response to COVID-19 in Latin America and the Caribbean</title><link>/updates/mapping-entrepreneurs-response-to-covid-19-in-latin-america-and-the-caribbean/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 13:02:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/mapping-entrepreneurs-response-to-covid-19-in-latin-america-and-the-caribbean/</guid><description>Challenge: The social and economic disruption caused by Covid-19 led to numerous challenges to conduct businesses, provide essential services, and attend to the most basic well-being needs around the globe.</description></item><item><title>Estimating Access to Employment Opportunities in Dhaka, Bangladesh</title><link>/updates/employment-opportunities-in-bangladesh/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 21:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/employment-opportunities-in-bangladesh/</guid><description>Challenge: Poor transport facilities and infrastructure are a major hindrance to Bangladesh’s economic development. The road network in Dhaka is severely congested.</description></item><item><title>Tackling the Global Profitarchy–Gender and the Choice of Business Sector</title><link>/updates/tackling-the-global-profitarchy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 21:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/tackling-the-global-profitarchy/</guid><description>Challenge: Despite significant progress in women’s educational attainment and higher female labor force participation rates in many countries, progress in closing the gender pay gap, which takes the ratio of median earnings of all women to all men, has been slow.</description></item></channel></rss>