<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Jobs and Development on Development Data Partnership</title><link>/tags/jobs-and-development/</link><description>Recent content in Jobs and Development on Development Data Partnership</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/jobs-and-development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title> Understanding the Impact of Digitalization During COVID-19</title><link>/updates/impact-of-digitalization-during-covid/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/impact-of-digitalization-during-covid/</guid><description>COVID-19 has disrupted almost every aspect of people&amp;rsquo;s work activities, inducing a digitalization push in the demand for certain types of skills and labor.</description></item><item><title>How Digitalization Can Enhance Economic Resilience</title><link>/updates/how-digitalization-can-enhance-resilience/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/how-digitalization-can-enhance-resilience/</guid><description>The COVID-19 crisis has opened deep economic scars, leading to significant output losses. Can digitalization improve economic resilience to shocks such as the pandemic?</description></item><item><title>Assessing Digital Transformation in Firms in Latin America and the Caribbean</title><link>/updates/digital-transformation-lac/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/digital-transformation-lac/</guid><description>Are firms in Latin America and the Caribbean lagging in terms of their adoption of digital technologies? The Inter-American Development Bank&amp;rsquo;s Competitiveness, Technology, and Innovation Division leveraged LinkedIn data on the penetration of digital skills as part of an assessment on the adoption of technologies in the region.</description></item><item><title>Analyzing Digital Skills Gap in MENA Countries to Inform An Upskilling Initiative</title><link>/updates/digital-skills-gap-mena/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/digital-skills-gap-mena/</guid><description>Digital technologies are reshaping work and traditional jobs. It is essential for workers across all sectors to acquire and strengthen their digital skills to stay competitive in the job market.</description></item><item><title>LinkedIn Data Reveals How Labor Markets Have Been Changing in Latin America and the Caribbean Since the Pandemic</title><link>/updates/labor-markets-lac/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/labor-markets-lac/</guid><description>Despite the devastating economic impacts of the COVID-19 pandemic, labor markets in Latin America and the Caribbean (LAC) are on the verge of recovery.</description></item><item><title>Analyzing the Evolution of Telework Adoption in Latin America and the Caribbean</title><link>/updates/telework-adoption-in-lac/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/telework-adoption-in-lac/</guid><description>Due to the COVID pandemic, the use of telework increased rapidly in Latin America and the Caribbean (LAC) region, as it did globally.</description></item><item><title>Empowering Female Entrepreneurs to Cross Over into Male-Dominated Sectors</title><link>/updates/empowering-female-entrepreneurs-to-cross-over-into-male-dominated-sectors/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/empowering-female-entrepreneurs-to-cross-over-into-male-dominated-sectors/</guid><description>Female entrepreneurship is on the rise globally. However, factors such as social norms and unconscious biases are holding women back from entering more profitable male-dominated sectors.</description></item><item><title>Green Jobs for Women and Diverse Groups Help Promote Equality and Climate Resilience</title><link>/updates/green-jobs-for-women-and-diverse-groups-help-promote-equality-and-climate-resilience/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/green-jobs-for-women-and-diverse-groups-help-promote-equality-and-climate-resilience/</guid><description>The role of women and diverse populations, including indigenous peoples, persons of African descent, persons with disabilities, and LGBTQ+ persons, is crucial in driving the decarbonization process and developing climate change resilience strategies.</description></item><item><title>Understanding the Post COVID-19 Labor Market in Latin America and the Caribbean</title><link>/updates/covid19-labor-markets-observatory/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 13:02:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/covid19-labor-markets-observatory/</guid><description>Challenge The Covid-19 Labor Markets Observatory, managed by the Inter-American Development Bank Labor Markets Division, aimed to understand how COVID-19 has affected labor markets in Latin America and the Caribbean.</description></item><item><title>Mapping Entrepreneurs' Response to COVID-19 in Latin America and the Caribbean</title><link>/updates/mapping-entrepreneurs-response-to-covid-19-in-latin-america-and-the-caribbean/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 13:02:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/mapping-entrepreneurs-response-to-covid-19-in-latin-america-and-the-caribbean/</guid><description>Challenge The social and economic disruption caused by Covid-19 led to numerous challenges to conduct businesses, provide essential services, and attend to the most basic well-being needs around the globe.</description></item><item><title>Estimating Access to Employment Opportunities in Dhaka, Bangladesh</title><link>/updates/employment-opportunities-in-bangladesh/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 21:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/employment-opportunities-in-bangladesh/</guid><description>Challenge: Poor transport facilities and infrastructure are a major hindrance to Bangladesh’s economic development. The road network in Dhaka is severely congested.</description></item><item><title>Tackling the Global Profitarchy–Gender and the Choice of Business Sector</title><link>/updates/tackling-the-global-profitarchy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 21:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/tackling-the-global-profitarchy/</guid><description>Challenge: Despite significant progress in women’s educational attainment and higher female labor force participation rates in many countries, progress in closing the gender pay gap, which takes the ratio of median earnings of all women to all men, has been slow.</description></item></channel></rss>