<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Urban Development on Development Data Partnership</title><link>/tags/urban-development/</link><description>Recent content in Urban Development on Development Data Partnership</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/urban-development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Buenos Aires Transport Demand Planning</title><link>/updates/buenos-aires-transport-demand-planning/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/buenos-aires-transport-demand-planning/</guid><description>Challenge The COVID-19 pandemic and the lockdown measures implemented in 2020 had a significant impact on mobility in the Metropolitan Area of Buenos Aires (AMBA), adding new constrains to the travel behaviours of residents and businesses.</description></item><item><title>Enhancing Health Planning in the Philippines</title><link>/updates/enhancing-health-planning-in-the-philippines/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/enhancing-health-planning-in-the-philippines/</guid><description>Challenge The delivery of health services in the Philippines is highly fragmented across different levels of administration. Health systems are autonomously run by local government units (LGUs), whether they are barangays (the most local level), cities, municipalities, or provinces.</description></item><item><title>Understanding Societal Responses to Policies Undertaken During Emergencies: Lessons from COVID-19’s Second Wave in Maharashtra</title><link>/updates/lessons-from-covid-19-second-wave-in-maharashtra/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/lessons-from-covid-19-second-wave-in-maharashtra/</guid><description>Maharashtra, one of the wealthiest states in India, was among the worst hit by COVID-19, registering nearly 140,000 COVID-19 deaths since the start of the pandemic.</description></item><item><title>Visualizing Millions of Waze Traffic Alerts with BigQuery, H3 and Dask</title><link>/updates/visualizing-millions-of-waze-traffic-alerts-with-google-bigquery-and-dask/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/visualizing-millions-of-waze-traffic-alerts-with-google-bigquery-and-dask/</guid><description>Waze for Cities, a Data Partner of the Development Data Partnership, connects government partners to high quality, frequent and granular traffic data extremely valuable in informing public sector, transport and urban planning as well as addressing the United Nations&amp;rsquo;s Sustainable Development Goals.</description></item><item><title>Improving Public Space and Market Design During COVID-19</title><link>/updates/improving-public-space-and-market-design-during-covid-19/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 13:02:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/improving-public-space-and-market-design-during-covid-19/</guid><description>Lima’s Central Market has always been one of the busiest and liveliest in Lima, Peru. Before the pandemic, some hundreds of people gathered there to buy and sell groceries, clothes, electronics&amp;ndash;you name it.</description></item></channel></rss>