<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Urban Development on Development Data Partnership</title><link>/tags/urban-development/</link><description>Recent content in Urban Development on Development Data Partnership</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/urban-development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bridging the Gap Between Plans and Reality: A Data-Driven Look at Urban Land Use in Amman</title><link>/updates/bridging-the-gap-between-plans-an-reality-a-data-driven-look-at-urban-lan-use-in-amman/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/bridging-the-gap-between-plans-an-reality-a-data-driven-look-at-urban-lan-use-in-amman/</guid><description>Urban landscapes are transforming rapidly, often outpacing the capabilities of traditional planning tools. In Amman, Jordan—a city shaped by swift population growth and complex migration flows—this challenge is particularly acute.</description></item><item><title>Unlocking Mapbox Data: Enhancing People’s Daily Lives through Data-Driven Urban Planning</title><link>/updates/unlocking-mapbox-data-enhancing-people-daily-lives-through-data-driven-urban-planning/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/unlocking-mapbox-data-enhancing-people-daily-lives-through-data-driven-urban-planning/</guid><description>Cities around the globe confront significant challenges in providing infrastructure, essential services, and access to public transportation. In response, many urban areas are striving to enhance their infrastructure to improve the daily lives of their citizens.</description></item><item><title>Harnessing Data to Transform City Planning and Management</title><link>/updates/harnessing-data-to-transform-city-planning-and-management/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/harnessing-data-to-transform-city-planning-and-management/</guid><description>With the ongoing growth of the global population, cities are increasingly emerging as hubs of economic activity and innovation. However, if urbanization is not well-planned, it can result in a wide range of problems, such as traffic jams.</description></item><item><title>Studying Service Accessibility in Towns and Villages</title><link>/updates/studying-service-accessibility-in-towns-and-villages/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/studying-service-accessibility-in-towns-and-villages/</guid><description>Settlements – cities, towns and villages – provide jobs and access to services for their own residents and other people living nearby.</description></item><item><title>Understanding people mobility in Amazonia</title><link>/updates/understanding-people-mobility-in-amazonia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/understanding-people-mobility-in-amazonia/</guid><description>Amazonia has many small and remote communities but also some big and influential urban centers. At the Inter-American Development Bank (IDB), in our efforts towards a sustainable development in Amazonia through the Amazonia Forever program, we leveraged movement data from Meta to shed light on the relationships between cities in each country within Amazonia, as well as the connection between the region&amp;rsquo;s urban areas and other parts of the countries as we understand that there is a constant movement of people and merchandise between areas.</description></item><item><title>Using Mobility Data to Improve Lives in Lima</title><link>/updates/mobility-data-lima/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/mobility-data-lima/</guid><description>Improving traffic flow and enhancing road safety are critical to Lima which was ranked the fourth most congested metropolitan area in the world in 2022.</description></item><item><title> Assessing Traffic Congestion and Accessibility to Jobs Using Waze for Cities and Mapbox Data</title><link>/updates/traffic-congestion-argentina/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/traffic-congestion-argentina/</guid><description>Traffic congestion and suburbanization are becoming increasingly significant factors affecting urban mobility and limiting access to jobs and opportunities in most mid-sized cities worldwide.</description></item><item><title>Buenos Aires Transport Demand Planning</title><link>/updates/buenos-aires-transport-demand-planning/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/buenos-aires-transport-demand-planning/</guid><description>Challenge The COVID-19 pandemic and the lockdown measures implemented in 2020 had a significant impact on mobility in the Metropolitan Area of Buenos Aires (AMBA), adding new constrains to the travel behaviours of residents and businesses.</description></item><item><title>Understanding Societal Responses to Policies Undertaken During Emergencies: Lessons from COVID-19’s Second Wave in Maharashtra</title><link>/updates/lessons-from-covid-19-second-wave-in-maharashtra/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/lessons-from-covid-19-second-wave-in-maharashtra/</guid><description>Maharashtra, one of the wealthiest states in India, was among the worst hit by COVID-19, registering nearly 140,000 COVID-19 deaths since the start of the pandemic.</description></item><item><title>Visualizing Millions of Waze Traffic Alerts with BigQuery, H3 and Dask</title><link>/updates/visualizing-millions-of-waze-traffic-alerts-with-google-bigquery-and-dask/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/visualizing-millions-of-waze-traffic-alerts-with-google-bigquery-and-dask/</guid><description>Waze for Cities, a Data Partner of the Development Data Partnership, connects government partners to high quality, frequent and granular traffic data extremely valuable in informing public sector, transport and urban planning as well as addressing the United Nations&amp;rsquo;s Sustainable Development Goals.</description></item><item><title>Improving Public Space and Market Design During COVID-19</title><link>/updates/improving-public-space-and-market-design-during-covid-19/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 13:02:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/improving-public-space-and-market-design-during-covid-19/</guid><description>Lima’s Central Market has always been one of the busiest and liveliest in Lima, Peru. Before the pandemic, some hundreds of people gathered there to buy and sell groceries, clothes, electronics&amp;ndash;you name it.</description></item></channel></rss>