<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mapbox on Development Data Partnership</title><link>/partner/mapbox/</link><description>Recent content in Mapbox on Development Data Partnership</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 06:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/partner/mapbox/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Optimizing Tourism Investments: Identifying Chokepoints and Underperforming Minor Roads in Sri Lanka</title><link>/updates/optimizing-tourism-investments-identifying-chokepoints-and-underperforming-minor-roads-in-sri-lanka/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/optimizing-tourism-investments-identifying-chokepoints-and-underperforming-minor-roads-in-sri-lanka/</guid><description>Challenge: Connected and maintained transportation infrastructure are critical to sustainable economic development, but most current estimation methods of road quality are labor, time, and cost intensive.</description></item><item><title>Analyzing Spatial Accessibility of Health Facilities in Indonesia and Philippines</title><link>/planning-for-equitable-access-to-health-infrastructure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/planning-for-equitable-access-to-health-infrastructure/</guid><description>Challenge: Indonesia and the Philippines are archipelagos, where geographic and administrative boundaries are similar. The collection of islands is home to different concentrations of ethnic, cultural, linguistic, and socioeconomic groups, with an imbalanced distribution of health facilities and physicians.</description></item><item><title>Mapbox Releases a New Movement Dataset for Mobility Insights</title><link>/introducing-mapbox-movement-data/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/introducing-mapbox-movement-data/</guid><description>Following the Development Data Partnership launch event at the World Bank-IMF Annual Meetings, Mapbox announces a new dataset on movement data for mobility insights.</description></item><item><title>Addressing COVID-19 through Public-Private Data Partnerships -- Where Do We Put New Testing Facilities?</title><link>/updates/covid19-and-public-private-data-partnerships/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 20:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/covid19-and-public-private-data-partnerships/</guid><description>Background
As the COVID-19 pandemic evolves, the World Bank is ramping up its response to help countries around the world. The Bank recently announced $14 billion emergency support program, for which a key pillar is to help countries strengthen their capacity to monitor and respond to the spread of the virus.</description></item><item><title>Estimating Access to Employment Opportunities in Dhaka, Bangladesh</title><link>/updates/employment-opportunities-in-bangladesh/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 21:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/employment-opportunities-in-bangladesh/</guid><description>Challenge: Poor transport facilities and infrastructure are a major hindrance to Bangladesh’s economic development. The road network in Dhaka is severely congested.</description></item></channel></rss>