<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mapbox on Development Data Partnership</title><link>/partner/mapbox/</link><description>Recent content in Mapbox on Development Data Partnership</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/partner/mapbox/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to Leverage Data for Better Transport, Digital Connectivity, and Sustainable Development in the Amazon</title><link>/updates/how-to-leverage-data-for-better-transport-digital-connectivity-and-sustainable-development-in-the-amazon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/how-to-leverage-data-for-better-transport-digital-connectivity-and-sustainable-development-in-the-amazon/</guid><description>The World Bank Transport team used data from Google, Mapbox, Meta, and Ookla to identify infrastructure gaps in the Amazon areas of Brazil, Colombia and Peru.</description></item><item><title>Unleashing the Power of Data to Tackle Traffic Congestion and Promote Road Safety</title><link>/updates/unleashing-the-power-of-data-to-tackle-traffic-congestion-and-promote-road-safety/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/unleashing-the-power-of-data-to-tackle-traffic-congestion-and-promote-road-safety/</guid><description>As the global population is constantly increasing, building modern and sustainable cities to accommodate everyone is crucial. This is enshrined in the 2030 Agenda for Sustainable Development, in which the Sustainable Development Goal 11 aims to make cities more inclusive, safe, resilient and sustainable.</description></item><item><title>Facilitating Inter-Municipal Cooperation in Lithuania to Provide Better Access to Healthcare and Long-Term Care Services to Citizens</title><link>/updates/facilitating-inter-municipal-cooperation-in-lithuania/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/facilitating-inter-municipal-cooperation-in-lithuania/</guid><description>Lithuania is experiencing rapid demographic change, with the population both aging and significantly shrinking in recent decades. This trend has put pressure on the provision of public services such as health care, especially at the municipal level, and is expected to continue in the coming years.</description></item><item><title>Studying Service Accessibility in Towns and Villages</title><link>/updates/studying-service-accessibility-in-towns-and-villages/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/studying-service-accessibility-in-towns-and-villages/</guid><description>Settlements – cities, towns and villages – provide jobs and access to services for their own residents and other people living nearby.</description></item><item><title>Using Mobility Data to Improve Lives in Lima</title><link>/updates/mobility-data-lima/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/mobility-data-lima/</guid><description>Improving traffic flow and enhancing road safety are critical to Lima which was ranked the fourth most congested metropolitan area in the world in 2022.</description></item><item><title> Assessing Traffic Congestion and Accessibility to Jobs Using Waze for Cities and Mapbox Data</title><link>/updates/traffic-congestion-argentina/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/traffic-congestion-argentina/</guid><description>Traffic congestion and suburbanization are becoming increasingly significant factors affecting urban mobility and limiting access to jobs and opportunities in most mid-sized cities worldwide.</description></item><item><title>How Big Data and Machine Learning Can Strengthen Road Safety</title><link>/updates/detecting-urban-clues-for-road-safety/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/detecting-urban-clues-for-road-safety/</guid><description>High-quality and reliable data is necessary to gain useful, actionable insights and enhance road safety conditions. However, collecting data on road safety through manual detection can be expensive, time-consuming, and complex.</description></item><item><title>A Data-Driven Framework to Support Bogota’s Barrios Vitales Project</title><link>/updates/framework-to-support-bogota-barrios-vitales-project/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/framework-to-support-bogota-barrios-vitales-project/</guid><description>A data-driven framework to support the design, implementation, and evaluation of a superblock model in Bogotá from a speed management perspective and inform street design alternatives in the urban space.</description></item><item><title>Optimizing Tourism Investments: Identifying Chokepoints and Underperforming Minor Roads in Sri Lanka</title><link>/updates/optimizing-tourism-investments-identifying-chokepoints-and-underperforming-minor-roads-in-sri-lanka/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/optimizing-tourism-investments-identifying-chokepoints-and-underperforming-minor-roads-in-sri-lanka/</guid><description>Challenge Connected and maintained transportation infrastructure are critical to sustainable economic development, but most current estimation methods of road quality are labor, time, and cost intensive.</description></item><item><title>Analyzing Spatial Accessibility of Health Facilities in Indonesia and Philippines</title><link>/updates/planning-for-equitable-access-to-health-infrastructure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/planning-for-equitable-access-to-health-infrastructure/</guid><description>Challenge: Indonesia and the Philippines are archipelagos, where geographic and administrative boundaries are similar. The collection of islands is home to different concentrations of ethnic, cultural, linguistic, and socioeconomic groups, with an imbalanced distribution of health facilities and physicians.</description></item><item><title>Mapbox Releases a New Movement Dataset for Mobility Insights</title><link>/updates/introducing-mapbox-movement-data/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/introducing-mapbox-movement-data/</guid><description>Following the Development Data Partnership launch event at the World Bank-IMF Annual Meetings, Mapbox announced a new dataset on movement data for mobility insights.</description></item><item><title>Addressing COVID-19 through Public-Private Data Partnerships: Where Do We Put New Testing Facilities?</title><link>/updates/covid19-and-public-private-data-partnerships/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 20:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/covid19-and-public-private-data-partnerships/</guid><description>Background
As the COVID-19 pandemic evolves, the World Bank is ramping up its response to help countries around the world. The Bank recently announced $14 billion emergency support program, for which a key pillar is to help countries strengthen their capacity to monitor and respond to the spread of the virus.</description></item><item><title>Estimating Access to Employment Opportunities in Dhaka, Bangladesh</title><link>/updates/employment-opportunities-in-bangladesh/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 21:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/employment-opportunities-in-bangladesh/</guid><description>Challenge: Poor transport facilities and infrastructure are a major hindrance to Bangladesh’s economic development. The road network in Dhaka is severely congested.</description></item></channel></rss>