<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Development Data Partnership</title><link>/authors/holly-krambeck/</link><description>Recent content on Development Data Partnership</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/authors/holly-krambeck/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Data Partnership: Bridging the Data Gap for Public Good</title><link>/annualmeetings2020/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/annualmeetings2020/</guid><description>Download Event Program High frequency, timely, and granular information &amp;ndash; which is routinely collected by the private sector&amp;ndash;can help inform public policy and service delivery.</description></item><item><title>Improving Road Safety in Nairobi</title><link>/updates/improving-road-safety-in-nairobi/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 20:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/improving-road-safety-in-nairobi/</guid><description>“Data Partnership brings domain expertise. Google brings data expertise. Together we impact real world problems.”
&amp;ndash;Google’s Bailey-Galvis noted at a Data Partnership event in early February 2019</description></item><item><title>On Responsible Data Use</title><link>/updates/responsible-data-use/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 21:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/responsible-data-use/</guid><description>As we develop the Data Partnership, we have a responsibility to the people impacted by our initiative &amp;ndash; to local governments and partners, and to our own organizations &amp;ndash; to think about how we are collecting, using, storing, and sharing information.</description></item><item><title>Why Data Partnership?</title><link>/updates/why-datacollaboratives/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/why-datacollaboratives/</guid><description>Should the private sector ever share data with the public sector, even if for public good? Well, it depends.
Most of us are in agreement that when companies collect our data as a natural by-product of providing a service – like our movement data or spending patterns – the company shouldn’t sell these data to a third party for profit, especially without transparency.</description></item><item><title>Data Partner Lightning Talks</title><link>/updates/data-day/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 21:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/data-day/</guid><description>On February 13, 2019, the Data Partnership (formerly Data Collaboratives), for the first time, brought together Partners and staff. More than 200 colleagues joined the standing-room-only event, in person and online, learning about how private data partnerships can be made to work for public good.</description></item></channel></rss>