<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Inequality and Shared Prosperity on Development Data Partnership</title><link>/tags/inequality-and-shared-prosperity/</link><description>Recent content in Inequality and Shared Prosperity on Development Data Partnership</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/inequality-and-shared-prosperity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Data for Impact: South-South Cooperation in Action</title><link>/updates/data-for-impact-south-south-cooperation-in-action/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/data-for-impact-south-south-cooperation-in-action/</guid><description>On September 12, the International Day for South-South Cooperation, we celebrate how countries across the Global South are working together to solve shared development challenges.</description></item><item><title>Can private management of African protected areas improve socioeconomic and wildlife outcomes?</title><link>/updates/can-private-management-of-african-protected-areas-improve-socioeconomic-and-wildlife-outcomes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/can-private-management-of-african-protected-areas-improve-socioeconomic-and-wildlife-outcomes/</guid><description>African governments increasingly entrust the management of protected areas to private, nongovernmental organizations, with the hope that the significant resources and technical capacities of private organizations will help realize the potential of these areas.</description></item><item><title>Understanding Socioeconomic Disparities in Mobility Behavior During the COVID-19 Pandemic in Developing Countries</title><link>/updates/understanding-socioeconomic-disparities-in-mobility-behavior-during-covid-in-developing-countries/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/understanding-socioeconomic-disparities-in-mobility-behavior-during-covid-in-developing-countries/</guid><description>The COVID-19 pandemic profoundly disrupted global mobility, but how did it affect different socioeconomic groups, particularly in developing and middle-income countries?</description></item><item><title>Examining the Impact of Social Distancing on Household-Level Economic Performances in Vietnam</title><link>/updates/social-distancing-on-household-level-economic-performances-in-vietnam/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/social-distancing-on-household-level-economic-performances-in-vietnam/</guid><description>During the COVID-19 pandemic, governments implemented social distancing measures to curb the spread of the virus. However, these measures also impacted people’s socioeconomic well-being.</description></item><item><title>Understanding Informal Trade Dynamics in Benin</title><link>/updates/understanding-informal-trade-dynamics-in-benin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/understanding-informal-trade-dynamics-in-benin/</guid><description>Benin&amp;rsquo;s trade performance has been improving gradually in the past decade. Notably, informal trade, smuggling and small-scale cross border trade (SSCBT) are part of the large unrecorded trade dynamics in this African country.</description></item><item><title>Assessing Social Inequality and Lockdown Policies using Mobile Location Data in Indonesia</title><link>/updates/social-inequality-and-lockdown-policies/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 13:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/updates/social-inequality-and-lockdown-policies/</guid><description>Challenge Lockdown policies such as stay-at-home orders and non-essential business closures are central to fighting the novel coronavirus. However, policy makers are having a hard time answering key questions about their efficacy.</description></item></channel></rss>